[
  {
    "answer": "New New York",
    "category": "video-games",
    "choices": [
      "New Chicago",
      "New New York",
      "New San Francisco",
      "None of these"
    ],
    "newCategory": "Video Games",
    "question": "In what fictional city is the TV show Futurama set?",
    "questionId": "2d50cb6ec5d8fb32e71eb4de5b16f995",
    "questionType": "multiple-choice"
  },
  {
    "answer": "Grunt",
    "category": "video-games",
    "choices": [
      "Drone",
      "Brute",
      "Elite",
      "Grunt"
    ],
    "newCategory": "Video Games",
    "question": "What is the lowest ranking species in the Covenant hierarchy in the Halo series?",
    "questionId": "cc083c45e968ca3a7f4c6ec7fef1dadc",
    "questionType": "multiple-choice"
  },
  {
    "answer": "Gravemind",
    "category": "video-games",
    "choices": [
      "Gravemind",
      "The Prophet of Truth",
      "The Arbiter",
      "No one"
    ],
    "newCategory": "Video Games",
    "question": "Who controls the Flood in the Halo series?",
    "questionId": "9ac9c22a5cb2f7dc93f6336481357e08",
    "questionType": "multiple-choice"
  },
  {
    "answer": "All of these",
    "category": "video-games",
    "choices": [
      "A Genetically modified super soldier",
      "A higher ranking soldier than a ODST",
      "Troopers that went through military training at the age of five",
      "All of these"
    ],
    "newCategory": "Video Games",
    "question": "What is a SPARTAN in the Halo series?",
    "questionId": "98170a9258285c010e946068ab1659f1",
    "questionType": "multiple-choice"
  },
  {
    "answer": "Forerunner",
    "category": "video-games",
    "choices": [
      "Forerunner",
      "Precursor",
      "Promethean",
      "Yamne"
    ],
    "newCategory": "Video Games",
    "question": "What species is the Didact in the Halo series?",
    "questionId": "e76d9363b22285c2ca029920d4306f57",
    "questionType": "multiple-choice"
  },
  {
    "answer": "True",
    "category": "video-games",
    "newCategory": "Video Games",
    "question": "In the Halo series, Zealots use Energy Swords.",
    "questionId": "5a0a43f6ff7fb2089edd81f17306bad7",
    "questionType": "true-false"
  },
  {
    "answer": "Pelicans",
    "category": "video-games",
    "choices": [
      "Falcons",
      "Hornets",
      "Phantoms",
      "Pelicans"
    ],
    "newCategory": "Video Games",
    "question": "Which of the following does the UNSC use to transport troops in the halo series?",
    "questionId": "6a934009cf2b82a0f3b9320f348d2700",
    "questionType": "multiple-choice"
  },
  {
    "answer": "United Nations Space Command",
    "category": "video-games",
    "choices": [
      "None of the above",
      "United Nations Space Council",
      "United Nations Space Command",
      "Unified Nations Supreme Court"
    ],
    "newCategory": "Video Games",
    "question": "What does UNSC stand for in the Halo series?",
    "questionId": "36252fbfbfc6497e918d9f77be051ba6",
    "questionType": "multiple-choice"
  },
  {
    "answer": "UNSC Infinity",
    "category": "video-games",
    "choices": [
      "UNSC In Amber Clad",
      "UNSC Infinity",
      "UNSC Spirit of Fire",
      "UNSC Pillar of Autumn"
    ],
    "newCategory": "Video Games",
    "question": "What is the largest UNSC ship in the Halo series?",
    "questionId": "ced97643b5c7b440e509f623295b212f",
    "questionType": "multiple-choice"
  },
  {
    "answer": "New Mombasa",
    "category": "video-games",
    "choices": [
      "Voi",
      "New Mombasa",
      "Toronto",
      "New York"
    ],
    "newCategory": "Video Games",
    "question": "What city does Halo 3 ODST take place in?",
    "questionId": "11a383ae25136d9f8adfc48237c3c728",
    "questionType": "multiple-choice"
  },
  {
    "answer": "Hunter",
    "category": "video-games",
    "choices": [
      "Brute",
      "Hunter",
      "Jackal",
      "Elite"
    ],
    "newCategory": "Video Games",
    "question": "What is the largest species of the Covenant in the Halo series?",
    "questionId": "09e8704d3be6d724f10106992e91040f",
    "questionType": "multiple-choice"
  },
  {
    "answer": "The Chozo built her to be a organic Supercomputer.",
    "category": "video-games",
    "choices": [
      "The Galactic Federation built her as a next generation Aurora Unit.",
      "It is unknown who made her but she was made to control Zebes.",
      "The Space Pirates built her to be one of their generals.",
      "The Chozo built her to be a organic Supercomputer."
    ],
    "newCategory": "Video Games",
    "question": "Who made the fictional Mother Brain and for what purpose?",
    "questionId": "4f62b6fb46fb5eb6cf693ed38685fe8c",
    "questionType": "multiple-choice"
  },
  {
    "answer": "The entire species used up their life energy to imprison Gorea.",
    "category": "video-games",
    "choices": [
      "They discovered Phazon and developed Phazon Madness causing them to wipe each other out.",
      "Gorea wiped them out.",
      "The entire species used up their life energy to imprison Gorea.",
      "The Metroids wiped them out."
    ],
    "newCategory": "Video Games",
    "question": "How did the Alimbics become extinct in the Metroid series?",
    "questionId": "21ee74e4c5ebabae21f46dbee8ad1318",
    "questionType": "multiple-choice"
  },
  {
    "answer": "Hornoad",
    "category": "video-games",
    "choices": [
      "Metroid",
      "Space Pirate",
      "Kihunter",
      "Hornoad"
    ],
    "newCategory": "Video Games",
    "question": "What creature passes on the X Parasite to Samus in the Metroid series?",
    "questionId": "b3affb0288feb83ad2e095ccb998d1d4",
    "questionType": "multiple-choice"
  },
  {
    "answer": "James Pierce",
    "category": "video-games",
    "choices": [
      "Lyle Smithsonian",
      "Adam Malkovich",
      "K.G Misawa",
      "James Pierce"
    ],
    "newCategory": "Video Games",
    "question": "Who is the Deleter in the Metroid series?",
    "questionId": "5a31c971b6e32958dd362abaf336c724",
    "questionType": "multiple-choice"
  },
  {
    "answer": "False",
    "category": "video-games",
    "newCategory": "Video Games",
    "question": "Kraid is the only one of his species encountered in the Metroid game.",
    "questionId": "756bd4006a7419d903ebdb9d128af414",
    "questionType": "true-false"
  },
  {
    "answer": "Vaporwing",
    "category": "video-games",
    "choices": [
      "Steambot",
      "Warp Hound",
      "Steamspider",
      "Vaporwing"
    ],
    "newCategory": "Video Games",
    "question": "What do Steamlords keep as pets in the Metroid series of games?",
    "questionId": "89105a9fc112da3bf09a8f397989ec19",
    "questionType": "multiple-choice"
  },
  {
    "answer": "Worm",
    "category": "video-games",
    "choices": [
      "Worm",
      "Beast",
      "Destroyer",
      "Consumer"
    ],
    "newCategory": "Video Games",
    "question": "An ancient Chozo prophecy predicts the coming of Phazon and the Metroid Prime. In this prophecy the Metroid Prime is referred to as which of the following?",
    "questionId": "25cb6058480b1b7aa7f990e06ecb1bad",
    "questionType": "multiple-choice"
  },
  {
    "answer": "True",
    "category": "video-games",
    "newCategory": "Video Games",
    "question": "King Worm can be fought after Mother Brainin Metroid Zero Mission.",
    "questionId": "26e63cd7da6167e34d323746c817c9e8",
    "questionType": "true-false"
  },
  {
    "answer": "Unknown",
    "category": "video-games",
    "choices": [
      "Space Pirate Homeworld",
      "Unknown",
      "SR388",
      "Zebes"
    ],
    "newCategory": "Video Games",
    "question": "What planet are Kihunters from in the Metroid games?",
    "questionId": "646b08296d6b87a8d778b41f339474de",
    "questionType": "multiple-choice"
  },
  {
    "answer": "K-2L",
    "category": "video-games",
    "choices": [
      "It is unknown",
      "K-2L",
      "Norion",
      "Zebes"
    ],
    "newCategory": "Video Games",
    "question": "What planet is Samus from in the Metorid games?",
    "questionId": "955d7fb23c0e5280f0c2e96ee0a45a95",
    "questionType": "multiple-choice"
  },
  {
    "answer": "Xenos",
    "category": "video-games",
    "choices": [
      "Xenos",
      "Volterites",
      "Judgers",
      "The Dominion"
    ],
    "newCategory": "Video Games",
    "question": "What is the name of the enemy faction in the first N.O.V.A?",
    "questionId": "6c8031516045ce9a8603b69471004039",
    "questionType": "multiple-choice"
  },
  {
    "answer": "True",
    "category": "video-games",
    "newCategory": "Video Games",
    "question": "The N.O.V.A 3 Shotgun is both semi and fully automatic.",
    "questionId": "4f746fcc076024e1d17114e7ec4910c8",
    "questionType": "true-false"
  },
  {
    "answer": "Aquarius",
    "category": "video-games",
    "choices": [
      "Sagittarius",
      "Earth",
      "New Ceres",
      "Aquarius"
    ],
    "newCategory": "Video Games",
    "question": "On which planet does the first two missions in N.O.V.A 2 take place?",
    "questionId": "954977772fea9fd2d9c28fe717a74a9c",
    "questionType": "multiple-choice"
  },
  {
    "answer": "MazRah",
    "category": "video-games",
    "choices": [
      "Prometheus",
      "Yelena",
      "MazRah",
      "Rufus"
    ],
    "newCategory": "Video Games",
    "question": "Who helps Kal Wardin find the Judger artifact aboard Therrius in N.O.V.A?",
    "questionId": "1e2a3fbf44b39d2c46c6ffb098a7029b",
    "questionType": "multiple-choice"
  },
  {
    "answer": "True",
    "category": "video-games",
    "newCategory": "Video Games",
    "question": "In N.O.V.A, Kal Wardin is rewarded for finding out what happened aboard the Colonial Pride by almost being killed.",
    "questionId": "8752c5d7700660b7712ac35253236793",
    "questionType": "true-false"
  },
  {
    "answer": "The Overseer",
    "category": "video-games",
    "choices": [
      "MazRah",
      "None of the above",
      "Prometheus",
      "The Overseer"
    ],
    "newCategory": "Video Games",
    "question": "Who is the leader of the Volterites in N.O.V.A?",
    "questionId": "8dadcbefd15c7612d4ee3c552b8f85ee",
    "questionType": "multiple-choice"
  },
  {
    "answer": "Heavy Demon",
    "category": "video-games",
    "choices": [
      "Heavy Demon",
      "Red Demon",
      "Imp",
      "Fiend"
    ],
    "newCategory": "Video Games",
    "question": "Which Xeno is capable of teleporting in N.O.V.A?",
    "questionId": "c58a5bedcdcda6f070998267a8c26202",
    "questionType": "multiple-choice"
  },
  {
    "answer": "False",
    "category": "video-games",
    "newCategory": "Video Games",
    "question": "In N.O.V.A, President Folson is unarmed.",
    "questionId": "b0871003c30e5d4187b3457cf2fe1002",
    "questionType": "true-false"
  },
  {
    "answer": "False",
    "category": "video-games",
    "newCategory": "Video Games",
    "question": "Boreas is the only desert planet in the N.O.V.A series.",
    "questionId": "9e9ea768f410de808f8dee602068582f",
    "questionType": "true-false"
  },
  {
    "answer": "Pauline",
    "category": "video-games",
    "choices": [
      "Peach",
      "Daisy",
      "Pauline",
      "Dixie Kong"
    ],
    "newCategory": "Video Games",
    "question": "What is the name of the damsel you have to save in the classic arcade game Donkey Kong?",
    "questionId": "e2c59ecc1f507e6c749001d18df96a39",
    "questionType": "multiple-choice"
  },
  {
    "answer": "Jumpman",
    "category": "video-games",
    "choices": [
      "Koopa",
      "Plumberio",
      "Jumpman",
      "Luigi"
    ],
    "newCategory": "Video Games",
    "question": "Which of these was a name that game character, Mario, was once called?",
    "questionId": "8298d9a94d60a14e54c5f9f881b741e9",
    "questionType": "multiple-choice"
  },
  {
    "answer": "The black jewel",
    "category": "video-games",
    "choices": [
      "Kemmy Koopa",
      "Lemmy Koopa",
      "The black jewel",
      "Bowser"
    ],
    "newCategory": "Video Games",
    "question": "Who or what turned Warios treasure into monsters in the game, Wario World?",
    "questionId": "73e47bcb3beabd2c1debb1d886ce5ff9",
    "questionType": "multiple-choice"
  },
  {
    "answer": "A turtle",
    "category": "video-games",
    "choices": [
      "A bird",
      "A lizard",
      "A turtle",
      "A tiger"
    ],
    "newCategory": "Video Games",
    "question": "In the Mario games, what animal is a paratroopa?",
    "questionId": "343027004a91d6dfb8e7f7177c65555a",
    "questionType": "multiple-choice"
  },
  {
    "answer": "A boy",
    "category": "video-games",
    "choices": [
      "A dog",
      "A boy",
      "A girl",
      "A bird"
    ],
    "newCategory": "Video Games",
    "question": "When first created, Mario game character, Birdo, was what?",
    "questionId": "8f88fa95c207b925b0bf90000d17cd4d",
    "questionType": "multiple-choice"
  },
  {
    "answer": "false",
    "category": "video-games",
    "newCategory": "Video Games",
    "question": "In the video games of Mario, is Luigi Marios cousin?:removeme",
    "questionId": "4e9d31e8e4e05932486384ae92bebd8e",
    "questionType": "true-false"
  },
  {
    "answer": "Koopas",
    "category": "video-games",
    "choices": [
      "Bowsers",
      "The Jungle",
      "Mushroom Kingdom",
      "Koopas"
    ],
    "newCategory": "Video Games",
    "question": "In the Mario video games, Bowser is the king of what?",
    "questionId": "889310a2ed0da244924e4058349e6de3",
    "questionType": "multiple-choice"
  },
  {
    "answer": "Shadow Queen",
    "category": "video-games",
    "choices": [
      "Gloom Tail",
      "Bowser",
      "Shadow Queen",
      "Cackletta"
    ],
    "newCategory": "Video Games",
    "question": "Who is the last boss in video game Paper Mario 2?",
    "questionId": "614e9be0fa912fd3575f4f868484dab7",
    "questionType": "multiple-choice"
  },
  {
    "answer": "Cool Hand Luke",
    "category": "video-games",
    "choices": [
      "For a Fistful of Dollars",
      "Dirty Sanchez",
      "Cool Hand Luke",
      "Metal Man"
    ],
    "newCategory": "Video Games",
    "question": "Which movie is this Warcraft 3 quote from? Bandit: -What we have here is a failure to communicate.",
    "questionId": "3ada1d4f8a844afb5495711fb956c4a3",
    "questionType": "multiple-choice"
  },
  {
    "answer": "The Mushroom Kingdom",
    "category": "video-games",
    "choices": [
      "The Koopa Kingdom",
      "The Kingdom of Sarasaland",
      "The Mushroom Kingdom",
      "Yoshi Island"
    ],
    "newCategory": "Video Games",
    "question": "Where does the popular video game character Mario live?",
    "questionId": "e1320616a576798072ebeeab779b6c88",
    "questionType": "multiple-choice"
  },
  {
    "answer": "Italian",
    "category": "video-games",
    "choices": [
      "Italian",
      "American",
      "Mexican",
      "British"
    ],
    "newCategory": "Video Games",
    "question": "What is Marios nationality according to Nintendo video games?",
    "questionId": "bdfaaa6a8f538293272755aff12efdfd",
    "questionType": "multiple-choice"
  },
  {
    "answer": "true",
    "category": "video-games",
    "newCategory": "Video Games",
    "question": "Has the video game character Mario ever been in a TV show?:removeme",
    "questionId": "0a0bb7845fe90da1a67d1e34d4626f8b",
    "questionType": "true-false"
  },
  {
    "answer": "Donkey Kong",
    "category": "video-games",
    "choices": [
      "Mario",
      "The Mario Bros.",
      "Super Mario",
      "Donkey Kong"
    ],
    "newCategory": "Video Games",
    "question": "What was the first video game in which Mario appeared?",
    "questionId": "d196a0059da8451a095f28f68fc9b780",
    "questionType": "multiple-choice"
  },
  {
    "answer": "The creators didnt have the technology to animate his hair.",
    "category": "video-games",
    "choices": [
      "The creators didnt have the technology to animate his hair.",
      "He is bald.",
      "He cant make his hair neat.",
      "He likes his cap."
    ],
    "newCategory": "Video Games",
    "question": "Why does Mario wear a red cap in the Mario series of games?",
    "questionId": "fc16e2ee765148faf7793fd94efd281b",
    "questionType": "multiple-choice"
  },
  {
    "answer": "true",
    "category": "video-games",
    "newCategory": "Video Games",
    "question": "Has Nintendo character Mario ever been a bad guy?:removeme",
    "questionId": "6fe2660baeb52bf31e31fdfbdbe776e3",
    "questionType": "true-false"
  },
  {
    "answer": "Allows him to throw fire balls.",
    "category": "video-games",
    "choices": [
      "Allows him to breath fire.",
      "Nothing",
      "It makes him angry.",
      "Allows him to throw fire balls."
    ],
    "newCategory": "Video Games",
    "question": "What does the Fire Flower do to Mario in the Mario video games?",
    "questionId": "a72a1a38cf5f86be66f0487f3827bbaf",
    "questionType": "multiple-choice"
  },
  {
    "answer": "It makes him bigger.",
    "category": "video-games",
    "choices": [
      "It makes him bigger.",
      "None",
      "It makes him impervious to danger.",
      "It makes him smaller."
    ],
    "newCategory": "Video Games",
    "question": "What effect does the Super Mushroom have on Mario in the popular series of video games?",
    "questionId": "ecadc4792335c4e8b58cad8bca59683f",
    "questionType": "multiple-choice"
  },
  {
    "answer": "False",
    "category": "video-games",
    "newCategory": "Video Games",
    "question": "In the Mario series of video games, Mario never uses any weapons.",
    "questionId": "57617bd08973eea7c77f9ef983852c60",
    "questionType": "true-false"
  },
  {
    "answer": "plumber",
    "category": "video-games",
    "choices": [
      "engineer",
      "doctor",
      "plumber",
      "electrician"
    ],
    "newCategory": "Video Games",
    "question": "What is Marios occupation in the Mario series of games?",
    "questionId": "0be5a1d9b0d07cabe6a9f510bfbb7bc7",
    "questionType": "multiple-choice"
  },
  {
    "answer": "Hyrule",
    "category": "video-games",
    "choices": [
      "Hylia",
      "Hyrule",
      "Sacred Realm",
      "Termania"
    ],
    "newCategory": "Video Games",
    "question": "What is the name of the land where most of the Legend of Zelda games take place?",
    "questionId": "56c1c0b65cd87144a4d1e30c857a38ef",
    "questionType": "multiple-choice"
  },
  {
    "answer": "Chu-Chu",
    "category": "video-games",
    "choices": [
      "Chu-Chu",
      "Armos",
      "Keese",
      "Octorok"
    ],
    "newCategory": "Video Games",
    "question": "Which monster made its first appearance in the game The Legend of Zelda: Majoras Mask?",
    "questionId": "80c67d20b62d2f65a4cbfce29c5f9c7f",
    "questionType": "multiple-choice"
  },
  {
    "answer": "Wind Waker",
    "category": "video-games",
    "choices": [
      "Ocarina of Time",
      "Links Awakening",
      "Wind Waker",
      "Majoras Mask"
    ],
    "newCategory": "Video Games",
    "question": "Which one of the Legend of Zelda games does not feature the same Link as the others?",
    "questionId": "7d19a953a45ba49b27974a7c208cd5a9",
    "questionType": "multiple-choice"
  },
  {
    "answer": "A spear used for immobilizing enemies",
    "category": "video-games",
    "choices": [
      "A magical leaf used for flying",
      "A spear used for immobilizing enemies",
      "A jar that can suck stuff into it and shoot out gusts of wind",
      "A candle for shooting fire at enemies"
    ],
    "newCategory": "Video Games",
    "question": "Which of the following is not an item that Link uses in the Legend of Zelda series of games?",
    "questionId": "c5a1a3ce2c888f82edea11a83b5a3945",
    "questionType": "multiple-choice"
  },
  {
    "answer": "yellow",
    "category": "video-games",
    "choices": [
      "yellow",
      "blue",
      "red",
      "green"
    ],
    "newCategory": "Video Games",
    "question": "In the Legend of Zelda series of games Link has not worn a tunic in what colour?",
    "questionId": "ae3ab2171bdba9e73200c4d68c31f3f7",
    "questionType": "multiple-choice"
  },
  {
    "answer": "The Legend of Zelda, The Adventure of Link, Ocarina of Time, Majoras Mask",
    "category": "video-games",
    "choices": [
      "The Legenda of Zelda, The Adventure of Link, A Link to the Past, Ocarina of TIme",
      "Orcale of Seasons, Orcale of Ages, Links Awakening, and Minish Cap",
      "The Legend of Zelda, The Adventure of Link, Ocarina of Time, Majoras Mask",
      "A Link to the Past, Majoras Mask, Ocarina of Time, Wind Waker"
    ],
    "newCategory": "Video Games",
    "question": "Which games were included in the 2003 Legend of Zelda Collectors edition that became available on the Nintendo GameCube?",
    "questionId": "b80f5ad74081c2ca453cfc463a0b7737",
    "questionType": "multiple-choice"
  },
  {
    "answer": "Sabin",
    "category": "video-games",
    "choices": [
      "Edgar",
      "Setzer",
      "Locke",
      "Sabin"
    ],
    "newCategory": "Video Games",
    "question": "Which Final Fantasy 3 character is known for blitzes such as Bum Rush, Pummel, and Suplex?",
    "questionId": "13447f7cf8b71f4bef97cf9c38a65e17",
    "questionType": "multiple-choice"
  },
  {
    "answer": "Cloud Strife",
    "category": "video-games",
    "choices": [
      "Sephiroth",
      "Squall Leonhart",
      "Cloud Strife",
      "Seifer Almasy"
    ],
    "newCategory": "Video Games",
    "question": "What character from the Final Fantasy series used a weapon called the Buster Sword?",
    "questionId": "f4312f087e6f8ae88135c04265837787",
    "questionType": "multiple-choice"
  },
  {
    "answer": "Guardian Forces",
    "category": "video-games",
    "choices": [
      "Materia",
      "Summonings",
      "Espers",
      "Guardian Forces"
    ],
    "newCategory": "Video Games",
    "question": "What was the name of the summoned creatures that aided the characters in the Final Fantasy 8 game?",
    "questionId": "7dce0f2793daebb8214a4c7429f5c55e",
    "questionType": "multiple-choice"
  },
  {
    "answer": "Kefka",
    "category": "video-games",
    "choices": [
      "Sin",
      "Kefka",
      "Garland",
      "Sephiroth"
    ],
    "newCategory": "Video Games",
    "question": "Which character was the main villain in the American Final Fantasy 3 game?",
    "questionId": "b43bd7500412cc919d944123017b3a12",
    "questionType": "multiple-choice"
  },
  {
    "answer": "Final Fantasy 8",
    "category": "video-games",
    "choices": [
      "Final Fantasy 10",
      "Final Fantasy 9",
      "Final Fantasy 8",
      "Final Fantasy 7"
    ],
    "newCategory": "Video Games",
    "question": "Which Final Fantasy game was released in North America on 7 September 1999?",
    "questionId": "a85c8597287b71ac90a34796dc24cdbb",
    "questionType": "multiple-choice"
  },
  {
    "answer": "Rinoa Heartilly",
    "category": "video-games",
    "choices": [
      "Setzer Gabbiani",
      "Daryl",
      "Rinoa Heartilly",
      "Cid Highwind"
    ],
    "newCategory": "Video Games",
    "question": "Which one of these Final Fantasy characters didnt own an airship?",
    "questionId": "905fe0a21d5ad2b043e4ce76fd982a7b",
    "questionType": "multiple-choice"
  },
  {
    "answer": "1987",
    "category": "video-games",
    "choices": [
      "1989",
      "1988",
      "1990",
      "1987"
    ],
    "newCategory": "Video Games",
    "question": "What year was the first Final Fantasy game released in Japan?",
    "questionId": "dd7c8165b726d4813f3fa87f06cfab98",
    "questionType": "multiple-choice"
  },
  {
    "answer": "Cid",
    "category": "video-games",
    "choices": [
      "Edgar",
      "Cid",
      "Sabin",
      "Squall"
    ],
    "newCategory": "Video Games",
    "question": "This character, who has appeared in nearly every Final Fantasy game, usually provides transportation to the main characters.",
    "questionId": "ae4b2c70895575545096e47499dbde30",
    "questionType": "multiple-choice"
  },
  {
    "answer": "Final Fantasy Tactics",
    "category": "video-games",
    "choices": [
      "Final Fantasy Mystic Quest",
      "Final Fantasy Tactics Advance",
      "Kingdom Hearts",
      "Final Fantasy Tactics"
    ],
    "newCategory": "Video Games",
    "question": "In this Final Fantasy spin-off every new recruit starts out as a Squire or a Chemist.",
    "questionId": "54fdad96f8d5c82e1be8dc7ee826c32d",
    "questionType": "multiple-choice"
  },
  {
    "answer": "Blitzball",
    "category": "video-games",
    "choices": [
      "Snowboarding",
      "Blitzball",
      "Triple Triad",
      "Tetra Master"
    ],
    "newCategory": "Video Games",
    "question": "Final Fantasy X featured which mini-game?",
    "questionId": "ede3d33c2b990b5c287959f6d7073811",
    "questionType": "multiple-choice"
  },
  {
    "answer": "Escape from Monkey Island",
    "category": "video-games",
    "choices": [
      "Escape from Monkey Island",
      "Simon the Sorcerer 3D",
      "Grim Fandango",
      "Monkey Island 2: LeChucks Revenge"
    ],
    "newCategory": "Video Games",
    "question": "Which video game is the following quote from? Ive got muscles in places youve never even heard of.",
    "questionId": "7db436d675613623756b93dc95b50ed5",
    "questionType": "multiple-choice"
  },
  {
    "answer": "Call of Duty",
    "category": "video-games",
    "choices": [
      "Medal of Honor",
      "Call of Duty",
      "Hidden and Dangerous 2",
      "Battlefield 1942"
    ],
    "newCategory": "Video Games",
    "question": "Which video game are the following quotes from? A: Come on, comrades! Up to the rooftop! Go! B: Get that flag up! Berlin is ours!",
    "questionId": "f395c48bd67650e74ae71d961d7c1f8c",
    "questionType": "multiple-choice"
  },
  {
    "answer": "motherlode",
    "category": "video-games",
    "choices": [
      "kaching",
      "all of these",
      "motherlode",
      "simoleons_$$$"
    ],
    "newCategory": "Video Games",
    "question": "What is the cheat for getting 50 000 simoleans in the computer game The Sims 2?",
    "questionId": "bf22240c339f55035559fdbdbafa2160",
    "questionType": "multiple-choice"
  },
  {
    "answer": "University, Night Life, Family Fun, Open for Business",
    "category": "video-games",
    "choices": [
      "Odd Jobs, Pets",
      "All of these",
      "University, Night Life, Family Fun, Open for Business",
      "Makin Magic, Holiday, Party"
    ],
    "newCategory": "Video Games",
    "question": "What are the expansion packs available for The Sims 2 game?",
    "questionId": "32d8320ffe29d6147fa1fc4cbc61b51d",
    "questionType": "multiple-choice"
  },
  {
    "answer": "False",
    "category": "video-games",
    "newCategory": "Video Games",
    "question": "In the computer game The Sims 2, in order for a Sim to have a baby, you must select the woohoo option on a different Sim.",
    "questionId": "36c806c04f5edb271cbb2e6e4fd3fc03",
    "questionType": "true-false"
  },
  {
    "answer": "toga",
    "category": "video-games",
    "choices": [
      "hippie outfit",
      "toga",
      "mascot costume",
      "football equipment"
    ],
    "newCategory": "Video Games",
    "question": "On the cover of the Sims 2 University expansion pack there is a picture of two Sims, one male and one female. What is the male Sim wearing?",
    "questionId": "a5c651ffca78b111f07fc1124662c49f",
    "questionType": "multiple-choice"
  },
  {
    "answer": "True",
    "category": "video-games",
    "newCategory": "Video Games",
    "question": "Bella Goth is absent from the family when The Sims 2 begins.",
    "questionId": "d273c0f3e44b1de41768007aad03bed9",
    "questionType": "true-false"
  },
  {
    "answer": "True",
    "category": "video-games",
    "newCategory": "Video Games",
    "question": "In Open for Business, the third expansion pack for The Sims 2, Sims may earn 25 business perks.",
    "questionId": "1695052441454935389de285676d8918",
    "questionType": "true-false"
  },
  {
    "answer": "false",
    "category": "video-games",
    "newCategory": "Video Games",
    "question": "Was the computer game The Sims 2 made solely by EA games?:removeme",
    "questionId": "8137b003bb068a3b80f2c08e27286506",
    "questionType": "true-false"
  },
  {
    "answer": "False",
    "category": "video-games",
    "newCategory": "Video Games",
    "question": "The Sims 2 game is rated E (Everyone).",
    "questionId": "58a968ed3e366439a49dabac1ec29d92",
    "questionType": "true-false"
  },
  {
    "answer": "MunchieBot",
    "category": "video-games",
    "choices": [
      "HungryBot",
      "MunchieBot",
      "Bot",
      "FoodBot"
    ],
    "newCategory": "Video Games",
    "question": "What is the name of the robot in The Sims 2, that fetches take-away food?",
    "questionId": "2648899024c69d2e8287ceb5fe0962c4",
    "questionType": "multiple-choice"
  },
  {
    "answer": "True",
    "category": "video-games",
    "newCategory": "Video Games",
    "question": "In Nightlife, the second expansion pack for The Sims 2, Sims can have their own cars.",
    "questionId": "a04a32eaffa2f97187d54b8748c58284",
    "questionType": "true-false"
  },
  {
    "answer": "d18",
    "category": "video-games",
    "choices": [
      "d10",
      "d100",
      "d4",
      "d18"
    ],
    "newCategory": "Video Games",
    "question": "Which is not an actual die?",
    "questionId": "97b7d5632444a93f759c7a2cbe8926f7",
    "questionType": "multiple-choice"
  },
  {
    "answer": "Paladin",
    "category": "video-games",
    "choices": [
      "Rogue",
      "Paladin",
      "Ranger",
      "Sorcerer"
    ],
    "newCategory": "Video Games",
    "question": "This class has the ability to smite evil.",
    "questionId": "37c78369ec93f24d96ce4405f647b66c",
    "questionType": "multiple-choice"
  },
  {
    "answer": "Elf",
    "category": "video-games",
    "choices": [
      "Dwarf",
      "Elf",
      "Human",
      "Changeling"
    ],
    "newCategory": "Video Games",
    "question": "This race doesnt sleep, they meditate instead.",
    "questionId": "f0cb9e58c2ff48cd571ea06b0a3d508d",
    "questionType": "multiple-choice"
  },
  {
    "answer": "Knowledge Arcana",
    "category": "video-games",
    "choices": [
      "Quick Draw",
      "Knowledge Arcana",
      "Forge Ring",
      "Toughness"
    ],
    "newCategory": "Video Games",
    "question": "Which of these is not a feat?",
    "questionId": "3988532f99c5ed410284f48e256f9415",
    "questionType": "multiple-choice"
  },
  {
    "answer": "True",
    "category": "video-games",
    "newCategory": "Video Games",
    "question": "You roll a d20 for attack rolls (to see if you hit your opponent).",
    "questionId": "41501f8a0c4dd83bf4cfd4ade4bfc834",
    "questionType": "true-false"
  },
  {
    "answer": "Full Plate Mail",
    "category": "video-games",
    "choices": [
      "Whetstone",
      "Two-Bladed Sword",
      "Full Plate Mail",
      "Heavy Repeating Crossbow"
    ],
    "newCategory": "Video Games",
    "question": "Which item costs the most according to the Players Handbook?",
    "questionId": "ad8a4f077a2e9ccc403003074db72c90",
    "questionType": "multiple-choice"
  },
  {
    "answer": "30 feet",
    "category": "video-games",
    "choices": [
      "20 feet",
      "50 feet",
      "30 feet",
      "10 feet"
    ],
    "newCategory": "Video Games",
    "question": "How far can a medium sized, unencumbered creature walk in one round?",
    "questionId": "74f19a2394fb24a1bb1c3c73cc917dcf",
    "questionType": "multiple-choice"
  },
  {
    "answer": "Sorcerer",
    "category": "video-games",
    "choices": [
      "Ranger",
      "Cleric",
      "Wizard",
      "Sorcerer"
    ],
    "newCategory": "Video Games",
    "question": "Which class casts arcane magic innately?",
    "questionId": "f6b0dee761fa349774d491e42ff16e71",
    "questionType": "multiple-choice"
  },
  {
    "answer": "Wish",
    "category": "video-games",
    "choices": [
      "Power Word Kill",
      "Wish",
      "Imprisonment",
      "Gate"
    ],
    "newCategory": "Video Games",
    "question": "This 9th level wizard spell is sought after by many characters as a reward. Many wizards also strive to learn this spell.",
    "questionId": "0aaaa8231b8796fcfd6d9c9000ce6938",
    "questionType": "multiple-choice"
  },
  {
    "answer": "Ranger",
    "category": "video-games",
    "choices": [
      "Bard",
      "Cleric",
      "Ranger",
      "Fighter"
    ],
    "newCategory": "Video Games",
    "question": "This class must choose 2 weapon fighting or archery as their weapon style at 2nd level.",
    "questionId": "f831bdee1bbb0348776def546b9ce583",
    "questionType": "multiple-choice"
  },
  {
    "answer": "world 1-3",
    "category": "video-games",
    "choices": [
      "world 1-3",
      "world 1 fortress",
      "world 2-5",
      "world 1-4"
    ],
    "newCategory": "Video Games",
    "question": "Where is the first warp whistle located in the game Super Mario 3?",
    "questionId": "61caab6caec3ad0934683a3adf6d0da1",
    "questionType": "multiple-choice"
  },
  {
    "answer": "Parade car",
    "category": "video-games",
    "choices": [
      "Parade car",
      "Bullet car",
      "Super Mario car",
      "Ganondorf car"
    ],
    "newCategory": "Video Games",
    "question": "In Mario Kart: Double Dash, what is the last thing you unlock by getting gold in the all cup tour in mirror mode?",
    "questionId": "e4423d8d6ee55c9cb64b504f207e5280",
    "questionType": "multiple-choice"
  },
  {
    "answer": "Young Link",
    "category": "video-games",
    "choices": [
      "Luigi",
      "Ness",
      "Yoshi",
      "Young Link"
    ],
    "newCategory": "Video Games",
    "question": "Which of the following characters can bounce off walls in the game Super Smash Brothers Melee?",
    "questionId": "107159b1ac5d0c10a9eaab5d4abbba97",
    "questionType": "multiple-choice"
  },
  {
    "answer": "Marios belt",
    "category": "video-games",
    "choices": [
      "Marios shoe",
      "Marios hat",
      "Marios belt",
      "Marios star"
    ],
    "newCategory": "Video Games",
    "question": "In the game Luigis Mansion, which of these in not one of Marios lost items?",
    "questionId": "ce917186c6b64c66721a3003b34a9781",
    "questionType": "multiple-choice"
  },
  {
    "answer": "Clawgrip",
    "category": "video-games",
    "choices": [
      "Birdo",
      "Tryclide",
      "Bowser",
      "Clawgrip"
    ],
    "newCategory": "Video Games",
    "question": "Who is the boss at the end of world 5 in the game Super Mario 2?",
    "questionId": "7e9909a1f7af1ce4aa33e5cbc62ccbd6",
    "questionType": "multiple-choice"
  },
  {
    "answer": "7-2",
    "category": "video-games",
    "choices": [
      "7-1",
      "7-2",
      "7-4",
      "7-3"
    ],
    "newCategory": "Video Games",
    "question": "In the game Super Mario 1, which level in world 7 is a water level?",
    "questionId": "567c7f41abc142cf7d4de9ddf9cb948a",
    "questionType": "multiple-choice"
  },
  {
    "answer": "Yoshis Island",
    "category": "video-games",
    "choices": [
      "Toads Island",
      "Yoshis Island",
      "Peachs Island",
      "Bowsers Island"
    ],
    "newCategory": "Video Games",
    "question": "In Super Mario World, you start the game on which island?",
    "questionId": "15a30736ae616948ef9da187449624f8",
    "questionType": "multiple-choice"
  },
  {
    "answer": "Toad",
    "category": "video-games",
    "choices": [
      "Peach",
      "Donkey Kong",
      "Mario",
      "Toad"
    ],
    "newCategory": "Video Games",
    "question": "Which of these is not a playable character in the video game Mario Party 4?",
    "questionId": "d6263ff4eaed61a2ee22fb43916fedf2",
    "questionType": "multiple-choice"
  },
  {
    "answer": "in a hot tub",
    "category": "video-games",
    "choices": [
      "in his castle",
      "in a volcano",
      "in a hot tub",
      "in the windmill with Petey Piranha"
    ],
    "newCategory": "Video Games",
    "question": "In the game Super Mario Sunshine, where is Bowser when you fight him at the end?",
    "questionId": "4cf65ff1d6d5b292056fd9034c95340b",
    "questionType": "multiple-choice"
  },
  {
    "answer": "a hammer",
    "category": "video-games",
    "choices": [
      "a fiery racket",
      "a hammer",
      "a star",
      "a fire fist"
    ],
    "newCategory": "Video Games",
    "question": "What does Mario use for his power shot in the game Mario Power Tennis?",
    "questionId": "c3fe4841559c882c1de7a6d2420584c2",
    "questionType": "multiple-choice"
  },
  {
    "answer": "Arceus",
    "category": "video-games",
    "choices": [
      "Giratina",
      "Dialga",
      "Cresselia",
      "Arceus"
    ],
    "newCategory": "Video Games",
    "question": "What is the God Pokemon called in Pokemon Pearl and Diamond?",
    "questionId": "d9648c2fee4b84a9175a80639c8df923",
    "questionType": "multiple-choice"
  },
  {
    "answer": "Glalie Froslass",
    "category": "video-games",
    "choices": [
      "Glalie Snolie",
      "Glalie Froslass",
      "Glalie Galrunt",
      "Glalie Probopass"
    ],
    "newCategory": "Video Games",
    "question": "The Pokemon creature Snorunt can evolve in which of the following?",
    "questionId": "5c755432b3f76ba45b07fabc5b092edd",
    "questionType": "multiple-choice"
  },
  {
    "answer": "Pearl",
    "category": "video-games",
    "choices": [
      "Pearl",
      "Blue",
      "Diamond",
      "Red"
    ],
    "newCategory": "Video Games",
    "question": "In what Pokemon version can Palkia be obtained?",
    "questionId": "dd504d7c036d7d6afd8a535c50140112",
    "questionType": "multiple-choice"
  },
  {
    "answer": "Gengar",
    "category": "video-games",
    "choices": [
      "Misdreavus",
      "Gengar",
      "Ghastly",
      "Haunter"
    ],
    "newCategory": "Video Games",
    "question": "What was the first ever ghost Pokemon to appear in a Pokemon episiode?",
    "questionId": "62c42b3b5d8e2e5b96e7dcae00b32931",
    "questionType": "multiple-choice"
  },
  {
    "answer": "Unknown",
    "category": "video-games",
    "choices": [
      "Aipom",
      "Gengar",
      "Unknown",
      "Entei"
    ],
    "newCategory": "Video Games",
    "question": "What Pokemon abducted Professor Spencer Haled in the movie Pokemon 3?",
    "questionId": "32795a4d9d3654c9dbcb6fc73a3b5689",
    "questionType": "multiple-choice"
  },
  {
    "answer": "6 - Artanis, Arcturus Mengsk, Jim Raynor, Zeratul, Samir Duran, Sarah Kerrigan",
    "category": "video-games",
    "choices": [
      "6 - Artanis, Arcturus Mengsk, Jim Raynor, Zeratul, Samir Duran, Sarah Kerrigan",
      "7 - Aratnis, Arcturus Mengsk, Aldaris, Samir Duran, Sarah Kerrigan, Fenix, Zeratul",
      "5 - Fenix, Arcturus Mengsk, Edmund Duke, Samir Duran, Sarah Kerrigan",
      "7 - Aratnis, Arcturus Mengsk, Aldaris, Samir Duran, Sarah Kerrigan, Fenix, Jim Raynor"
    ],
    "newCategory": "Video Games",
    "question": "How many heroes are alive at the end of Startcraft: Brood War?",
    "questionId": "0bd7376d23c26cc596aa226bfdbcb7f7",
    "questionType": "multiple-choice"
  },
  {
    "answer": "Alpha Squadron",
    "category": "video-games",
    "choices": [
      "Alpha Squadron",
      "Beta Squadron",
      "Delta Squadron",
      "Omega Squadron"
    ],
    "newCategory": "Video Games",
    "question": "Edmund Duke leads which group of elite fighters?",
    "questionId": "a4177646d45001b5accb1df952a42b66",
    "questionType": "multiple-choice"
  },
  {
    "answer": "Dark Templar",
    "category": "video-games",
    "choices": [
      "Dark Archon",
      "High Templar",
      "Dark Templar",
      "Zealot"
    ],
    "newCategory": "Video Games",
    "question": "What type of unit is Zeratul?",
    "questionId": "5baed988db7b9607625cb89826a39e23",
    "questionType": "multiple-choice"
  },
  {
    "answer": "10 hit points and 350 plasma shield",
    "category": "video-games",
    "choices": [
      "10 hit points and 250 plasma shield",
      "20 hit points and 250 plasma shield",
      "10 hit points and 350 plasma shield",
      "20 hit points and 300 plasma shield"
    ],
    "newCategory": "Video Games",
    "question": "What are characteristics of the Archon unit?",
    "questionId": "fda8c102187ebbbc2f5a9f08e0a6f5c3",
    "questionType": "multiple-choice"
  },
  {
    "answer": "Dark Templar",
    "category": "video-games",
    "choices": [
      "Zealot",
      "Scout",
      "Dark Templar",
      "Zealot"
    ],
    "newCategory": "Video Games",
    "question": "What unit says that in the game?",
    "questionId": "cd8bd08bdcac75358a548bb263106bdf",
    "questionType": "multiple-choice"
  },
  {
    "answer": "Vice Admiral",
    "category": "video-games",
    "choices": [
      "General",
      "Admiral",
      "Vice Admiral",
      "Corporal"
    ],
    "newCategory": "Video Games",
    "question": "What is Alexei Stukovs rank?",
    "questionId": "97b315fb83e5ae81bf641a3a62cc0077",
    "questionType": "multiple-choice"
  },
  {
    "answer": "True colors",
    "category": "video-games",
    "choices": [
      "True colors",
      "Omega station",
      "Day of lightning",
      "Hammer falls"
    ],
    "newCategory": "Video Games",
    "question": "During which mission do Edmund Duke and Fenix die?",
    "questionId": "16efae68b50a53d160d5df4d19b1942e",
    "questionType": "multiple-choice"
  },
  {
    "answer": "Gerard DuGalle",
    "category": "video-games",
    "choices": [
      "Samir Duran",
      "Gerard DuGalle",
      "Jim Raynor",
      "Alexei Stukov"
    ],
    "newCategory": "Video Games",
    "question": "Who leads the UED (United Earth Directorate forces)?",
    "questionId": "d0483b087af72c4bb6895d96f09af15e",
    "questionType": "multiple-choice"
  },
  {
    "answer": "Fenix",
    "category": "video-games",
    "choices": [
      "Zeratul",
      "Edmund Duke",
      "Fenix",
      "Artanis"
    ],
    "newCategory": "Video Games",
    "question": "Who is Kerrigan talking to?",
    "questionId": "b38c9e1b828645be97c6086f610e1502",
    "questionType": "multiple-choice"
  },
  {
    "answer": "Mario",
    "category": "video-games",
    "choices": [
      "Luigi",
      "Donkey Kong",
      "Sonic",
      "Mario"
    ],
    "newCategory": "Video Games",
    "question": "What is the name of the Italian plumber, thats also the mascot of Nintendo?",
    "questionId": "1fd8d046d4a5ef2a2236539f1a73097f",
    "questionType": "multiple-choice"
  },
  {
    "answer": "Knights of the Old Republic",
    "category": "video-games",
    "choices": [
      "Kings Of The Old Realm",
      "Know One Tells Our Ruses",
      "Kin Of Time Or Rain",
      "Knights of the Old Republic"
    ],
    "newCategory": "Video Games",
    "question": "What does KOTOR stand for?",
    "questionId": "442e3240c2b6a3ea70ba5bb95d82cc16",
    "questionType": "multiple-choice"
  },
  {
    "answer": "True",
    "category": "video-games",
    "newCategory": "Video Games",
    "question": "In the video game Rock Band you can play multiple instruments in the band.",
    "questionId": "08d0174b4d891015b3da9cd930325b2f",
    "questionType": "true-false"
  },
  {
    "answer": "The War Chiefs",
    "category": "video-games",
    "choices": [
      "The War Chiefs",
      "The Tribal Warriors",
      "The Lakota Warriors",
      "Asian Dynasty"
    ],
    "newCategory": "Video Games",
    "question": "Which Age of Empires game expansion pack allows you to play as Native Americans?",
    "questionId": "80d2e7b88c0fd97c07e97701fe50e5b3",
    "questionType": "multiple-choice"
  },
  {
    "answer": "Diddy Kong",
    "category": "video-games",
    "choices": [
      "Tiny Kong",
      "Donkey Kong Jr.",
      "Diddy Kong",
      "Mini Donkey Kong"
    ],
    "newCategory": "Video Games",
    "question": "What is the name of Donkey Kongs tiny sidekick?",
    "questionId": "9ec2b6a5ae5086bffc4570625b615978",
    "questionType": "multiple-choice"
  },
  {
    "answer": "Vice City",
    "category": "video-games",
    "choices": [
      "Grand Theft Auto III",
      "San Andreas",
      "GTA 9,000",
      "Vice City"
    ],
    "newCategory": "Video Games",
    "question": "Which GTA game features Tommy Vercetti?",
    "questionId": "02a1780dfb247a56fc8d52a3855fe104",
    "questionType": "multiple-choice"
  },
  {
    "answer": "Resident Evil 4",
    "category": "video-games",
    "choices": [
      "Burnout Revenge",
      "Dead Rising",
      "Resident Evil 4",
      "Midnight Mayhem"
    ],
    "newCategory": "Video Games",
    "question": "Which game is Luis Sera featured in?",
    "questionId": "dd123162f7f83620f8d61dc8cab60284",
    "questionType": "multiple-choice"
  },
  {
    "answer": "Kingdom Hearts",
    "category": "video-games",
    "choices": [
      "The Darkness",
      "Ghost Rider",
      "Kingdom Hearts",
      "X-Men The Game"
    ],
    "newCategory": "Video Games",
    "question": "Which of these games is not based on a comic book?",
    "questionId": "cd8f97c35469ec859167de4741400d4a",
    "questionType": "multiple-choice"
  },
  {
    "answer": "We Will Rock You",
    "category": "video-games",
    "choices": [
      "Carry on My Wayward Son",
      "Strutter",
      "War Pigs",
      "We Will Rock You"
    ],
    "newCategory": "Video Games",
    "question": "Which of these songs is not in Guitar Hero 2?",
    "questionId": "9888c540508791303e4d68e3e77cc263",
    "questionType": "multiple-choice"
  },
  {
    "answer": "Super Smash Bros Melee",
    "category": "video-games",
    "choices": [
      "Pikmin",
      "Super Smash Bros Melee",
      "Resident Evil 4",
      "Nicktoons Unite"
    ],
    "newCategory": "Video Games",
    "question": "In 2007, this game was named by IGN the 3rd best GameCube game of all time.",
    "questionId": "01f034d7af2533fd9a6462d8499b99c7",
    "questionType": "multiple-choice"
  },
  {
    "answer": "Wooden sword",
    "category": "video-games",
    "choices": [
      "Ordon sword",
      "Four sword",
      "Wooden sword",
      "Master sword"
    ],
    "newCategory": "Video Games",
    "question": "In the Legend of Zelda: Twilight Princess, what is the name of the first sword you get?",
    "questionId": "fc23afdb90f96b7ad1c171c05921b88c",
    "questionType": "multiple-choice"
  },
  {
    "answer": "three",
    "category": "video-games",
    "choices": [
      "one",
      "nine",
      "three",
      "six"
    ],
    "newCategory": "Video Games",
    "question": "In The Legend of Zelda: Majoras Mask, how many days do you have until the moon crashes down on Temina?",
    "questionId": "4047776775650f090b7125e17bcbcde4",
    "questionType": "multiple-choice"
  },
  {
    "answer": "False",
    "category": "video-games",
    "newCategory": "Video Games",
    "question": "There is at least one game of the Zelda series of games, released from 1986 to 2006, in which Zelda and Link get married.",
    "questionId": "7f0d50a063d5031d7995113a1801ef5a",
    "questionType": "true-false"
  },
  {
    "answer": "Talon",
    "category": "video-games",
    "choices": [
      "Zelda",
      "Ingo",
      "Minda",
      "Talon"
    ],
    "newCategory": "Video Games",
    "question": "What is the name of the owner of lon-lon ranch in the Zelda series of games?",
    "questionId": "83ed60dc380d190e370343c2fea11f44",
    "questionType": "multiple-choice"
  },
  {
    "answer": "None of these",
    "category": "video-games",
    "choices": [
      "None of these",
      "Gannondorf",
      "Navi",
      "Vati"
    ],
    "newCategory": "Video Games",
    "question": "In The Legend of Zelda: Twilight Princess, what was the name of the villain that had been fired from a joker at Hyrule Castle?",
    "questionId": "c1a2f4e13e8e28cc321204e55db1dd02",
    "questionType": "multiple-choice"
  },
  {
    "answer": "Gerudo",
    "category": "video-games",
    "choices": [
      "Zora",
      "Gerudo",
      "Goron",
      "Hylian"
    ],
    "newCategory": "Video Games",
    "question": "In the Zelda series of games, what is the name of the tribe Gannondorf comes from?",
    "questionId": "b4a98cdcadee048347b0b8def5c1cee6",
    "questionType": "multiple-choice"
  },
  {
    "answer": "Hylians",
    "category": "video-games",
    "choices": [
      "Hylians",
      "Kokiri",
      "Zora",
      "Goron"
    ],
    "newCategory": "Video Games",
    "question": "Link, one of the main characters in the Zelda series of games, is a member of what race?",
    "questionId": "786ef6e8d7ce508b41a76200b266ec77",
    "questionType": "multiple-choice"
  },
  {
    "answer": "It has never been revealed.",
    "category": "video-games",
    "choices": [
      "It has never been revealed.",
      "Gerald",
      "Sam",
      "Lance"
    ],
    "newCategory": "Video Games",
    "question": "What is Links fathers name according to the Zelda series of games?",
    "questionId": "d95e447c544c8c03b2d596d1fd48b1b7",
    "questionType": "multiple-choice"
  },
  {
    "answer": "Link to the Past",
    "category": "video-games",
    "choices": [
      "Twilight Princess",
      "Link to the Past",
      "Ocarina of Time",
      "Links Awakening"
    ],
    "newCategory": "Video Games",
    "question": "In which Zelda game does Link turn into a bunny when he goes into the dark world without a pearl?",
    "questionId": "d69f05deff07df0282b33b4ca0c8e2e1",
    "questionType": "multiple-choice"
  },
  {
    "answer": "Double Dragon",
    "category": "video-games",
    "choices": [
      "Double Dragon",
      "Final Fight",
      "Punisher",
      "Street Fighter"
    ],
    "newCategory": "Video Games",
    "question": "Which computer game is this soundtrack from?",
    "questionId": "80f63eb1beb40befb421201237c2f314",
    "questionType": "multiple-choice"
  },
  {
    "answer": "Tutorial Island",
    "category": "video-games",
    "choices": [
      "Beginners Island",
      "Noobonia Island",
      "Startagonia Island",
      "Tutorial Island"
    ],
    "newCategory": "Video Games",
    "question": "What island do you start on in the online role-playing game RuneScape?",
    "questionId": "9ac3a135cca33d1dd7857a3a618606d2",
    "questionType": "multiple-choice"
  },
  {
    "answer": "A warrior",
    "category": "video-games",
    "choices": [
      "A skeleton",
      "An imp",
      "A warrior",
      "A barbarian"
    ],
    "newCategory": "Video Games",
    "question": "What icon is used to start a low detail RuneScape game?",
    "questionId": "7c2bd0c6021751354eea818896080953",
    "questionType": "multiple-choice"
  },
  {
    "answer": "Silverlight",
    "category": "video-games",
    "choices": [
      "Brightheart",
      "Demonbane",
      "The Shining Light",
      "Silverlight"
    ],
    "newCategory": "Video Games",
    "question": "What is the name of the sword used to defeat the demon in the demon slayer quest of the online role-playing game RuneScape?",
    "questionId": "01d8297242012feae5e61e82c8c9edae",
    "questionType": "multiple-choice"
  },
  {
    "answer": "Bananas",
    "category": "video-games",
    "choices": [
      "Apples",
      "Bananas",
      "Oranges",
      "Pineapples"
    ],
    "newCategory": "Video Games",
    "question": "In the online role-playing game RuneScape, what kind of fruit is grown in Karajama?",
    "questionId": "39136f25d436592bed6666757f451b0c",
    "questionType": "multiple-choice"
  },
  {
    "answer": "False",
    "category": "video-games",
    "newCategory": "Video Games",
    "question": "Priest robes raise your mage level in the mass online game RuneScape.",
    "questionId": "a0f2e4bc35d78f96733382b6d784592c",
    "questionType": "true-false"
  },
  {
    "answer": "Rune",
    "category": "video-games",
    "choices": [
      "Dragon",
      "Granite",
      "Rune",
      "Adamantite"
    ],
    "newCategory": "Video Games",
    "question": "What is the highest weapon type available to nonmembers in the online role-playing game RuneScape?",
    "questionId": "6f15c6a969bb4db2ceba188079f07779",
    "questionType": "multiple-choice"
  },
  {
    "answer": "Gielinor",
    "category": "video-games",
    "choices": [
      "None of these",
      "Modor",
      "Gomor",
      "Gielinor"
    ],
    "newCategory": "Video Games",
    "question": "What is the name of the fantasy realm in which the RuneScape game is set?",
    "questionId": "ddf7e8ffe43e2e2d04391180ccce3bb8",
    "questionType": "multiple-choice"
  },
  {
    "answer": "Thingummywut",
    "category": "video-games",
    "choices": [
      "Bungdungydingdong",
      "Hugmugabugger",
      "Thingummywut",
      "Trindindlekindy"
    ],
    "newCategory": "Video Games",
    "question": "What does Traiborn call you in the online role-playing game RuneScape?",
    "questionId": "26f1769919dd6a2d91b07122add509cc",
    "questionType": "multiple-choice"
  },
  {
    "answer": "Spain",
    "category": "video-games",
    "choices": [
      "Germany",
      "Spain",
      "France",
      "USA"
    ],
    "newCategory": "Video Games",
    "question": "The action in the survival horror game Resident Evil 4 takes place in what country?",
    "questionId": "11f7e0466ecba791c1386f8c2aa75a68",
    "questionType": "multiple-choice"
  },
  {
    "answer": "Killer7",
    "category": "video-games",
    "choices": [
      "Chicago typewriter",
      "Killer7",
      "Handcannon",
      "Infinite Launcher"
    ],
    "newCategory": "Video Games",
    "question": "Which of the guns listed is available before you beat the Resident Evil 4 game?",
    "questionId": "3c3f9f4e1f69413315536df142e6f7ef",
    "questionType": "multiple-choice"
  },
  {
    "answer": "It is not mentioned",
    "category": "video-games",
    "choices": [
      "Jeremy",
      "Krauser",
      "It is not mentioned",
      "Robert"
    ],
    "newCategory": "Video Games",
    "question": "What is the merchants real name in the video game Resident Evil 4?",
    "questionId": "ff07e6a9412c595fa5a6f26796edac9b",
    "questionType": "multiple-choice"
  },
  {
    "answer": "U3",
    "category": "video-games",
    "choices": [
      "None of the above",
      "Verdugo",
      "Garrador",
      "U3"
    ],
    "newCategory": "Video Games",
    "question": "This creature from the game Resident Evil 4 was created by splicing genes from reptiles, insects and a human into one organism.",
    "questionId": "d9de07c2dcaa01df3645d27f7d4f7763",
    "questionType": "multiple-choice"
  },
  {
    "answer": "True",
    "category": "video-games",
    "newCategory": "Video Games",
    "question": "In the survival video game Resident Evil 4, the handcannon with its exclusive upgrade does 99.9 damage and has infinite ammo.",
    "questionId": "59ad732ff2c8f902450c4513ae391512",
    "questionType": "true-false"
  },
  {
    "answer": "Broken butterfly",
    "category": "video-games",
    "choices": [
      "Semi-auto rifle",
      "Chicago typewriter",
      "Killer7",
      "Broken butterfly"
    ],
    "newCategory": "Video Games",
    "question": "Not including the rocket launcher, what is the second most powerful weapon in Resident Evil 4, according to its damage per shot?",
    "questionId": "c1476e6e784c21e35242b58cd0e5acdd",
    "questionType": "multiple-choice"
  },
  {
    "answer": "Arcturus Mengsk",
    "category": "video-games",
    "choices": [
      "Alexei Stukov",
      "Edmund Duke",
      "Jim Raynor",
      "Arcturus Mengsk"
    ],
    "newCategory": "Video Games",
    "question": "Whose final speech ends in We shall win through no matter the cost!",
    "questionId": "50aac1dc15015574f67da1cc655b2cfe",
    "questionType": "multiple-choice"
  },
  {
    "answer": "Zeratul",
    "category": "video-games",
    "choices": [
      "Zeratul",
      "Sarah Kerrigan",
      "Aldaris",
      "Samir Duran"
    ],
    "newCategory": "Video Games",
    "question": "Who kills the Matriarch?",
    "questionId": "523d5d3bb0c414dfe0ba5d7302afa52a",
    "questionType": "multiple-choice"
  },
  {
    "answer": "Zealot",
    "category": "video-games",
    "choices": [
      "Zealot",
      "Dark Templar",
      "Archon",
      "Dark Archon"
    ],
    "newCategory": "Video Games",
    "question": "The words Doom to all who threaten the homeworld belong to which unit?",
    "questionId": "174ea123a62aec6329e8b7c9821662f8",
    "questionType": "multiple-choice"
  },
  {
    "answer": "You pig!",
    "category": "video-games",
    "choices": [
      "You pig!",
      "Hello, Jimmy",
      "Hello, sheriff",
      "Hello, marshal"
    ],
    "newCategory": "Video Games",
    "question": "What were the words of Sarah Kerrigan to Jim Raynor when they first met?",
    "questionId": "27c58e282ffbf08e41cc00b3b6761407",
    "questionType": "multiple-choice"
  },
  {
    "answer": "150",
    "category": "video-games",
    "choices": [
      "140",
      "160",
      "150",
      "120"
    ],
    "newCategory": "Video Games",
    "question": "How many hit points does the Arclite Siege Tank have?",
    "questionId": "3319eeb3f54560ba3be99820d2228766",
    "questionType": "multiple-choice"
  },
  {
    "answer": "Alexei",
    "category": "video-games",
    "choices": [
      "Raynor",
      "Alexei",
      "Gerard",
      "Kerrigan"
    ],
    "newCategory": "Video Games",
    "question": "Listen to the dialogue and determine what name is missing at the end",
    "questionId": "8cf629c78b4a10e9edebc46f7ab9780d",
    "questionType": "multiple-choice"
  },
  {
    "answer": "Fenix",
    "category": "video-games",
    "choices": [
      "Artanis",
      "Zeratul",
      "Fenix",
      "Tessadar"
    ],
    "newCategory": "Video Games",
    "question": "What hero do these words belong to: I fear no death, I fear no enemy, our strength is eternal",
    "questionId": "a8c0a2b299125a4137c46b00efc0e5e1",
    "questionType": "multiple-choice"
  },
  {
    "answer": "He dies during the final assault on planet Char",
    "category": "video-games",
    "choices": [
      "He commits suicide after his fleet is destroyed",
      "He is killed by Samir Duran, because he was a traitor",
      "His spaceship is blown up by Prottos forces",
      "He dies during the final assault on planet Char"
    ],
    "newCategory": "Video Games",
    "question": "What is the official version for the death of Alexei Stukov?",
    "questionId": "e806abe1d993a66f01cd89af76ce5b25",
    "questionType": "multiple-choice"
  },
  {
    "answer": "Ghost",
    "category": "video-games",
    "choices": [
      "Ghost",
      "Medic",
      "Marine",
      "Firebat"
    ],
    "newCategory": "Video Games",
    "question": "Which unit says You called down the Thunder, now reap the Whirlwind.",
    "questionId": "b45379183a08d7de5f6d30f3eb026beb",
    "questionType": "multiple-choice"
  },
  {
    "answer": "Super Mario Bros",
    "category": "video-games",
    "choices": [
      "Star Fox",
      "Donkey Kong",
      "Super Mario Bros",
      "The Legend of Zelda"
    ],
    "newCategory": "Video Games",
    "question": "This sound clip is from what classic Nintendo game?",
    "questionId": "00a172bfb684ca5541151b2247a997e3",
    "questionType": "multiple-choice"
  },
  {
    "answer": "Kirbys Adventure",
    "category": "video-games",
    "choices": [
      "Metroid",
      "Legend of Zelda",
      "Super Mario Bros.",
      "Kirbys Adventure"
    ],
    "newCategory": "Video Games",
    "question": "This sound clip is from what NES game featuring a creature that could eat anything?",
    "questionId": "362886f8929b1b9526e7f3382978ca4c",
    "questionType": "multiple-choice"
  },
  {
    "answer": "Halo",
    "category": "video-games",
    "choices": [
      "Final Fantasy",
      "Eldar Scrolls IV: Oblivion",
      "Rainbow 6",
      "Halo"
    ],
    "newCategory": "Video Games",
    "question": "This is the theme to what Xbox video game?",
    "questionId": "9a98b467a21f060bc32534142ccab215",
    "questionType": "multiple-choice"
  },
  {
    "answer": "Legend of Zelda",
    "category": "video-games",
    "choices": [
      "Metroid",
      "Donkey Kong",
      "Legend of Zelda",
      "Super Mario Bros."
    ],
    "newCategory": "Video Games",
    "question": "This is the overworld theme to this NES game that introduced the save function because the game took so long to complete.",
    "questionId": "92acb3caa683ea5b3ff81b92d128c77c",
    "questionType": "multiple-choice"
  },
  {
    "answer": "Final Fantasy",
    "category": "video-games",
    "choices": [
      "Mortal Combat",
      "Legend of Zelda",
      "Final Fantasy",
      "Super Mario"
    ],
    "newCategory": "Video Games",
    "question": "This is the victory theme to what popular video game series?",
    "questionId": "c97813ffa6d98114d52570536ff75d20",
    "questionType": "multiple-choice"
  },
  {
    "answer": "Super Smash Bros. Melee",
    "category": "video-games",
    "choices": [
      "Street Fighter II",
      "Super Smash Bros. Melee",
      "Teken 4",
      "Soul Caliber II"
    ],
    "newCategory": "Video Games",
    "question": "From which fighting game is this sound clip?",
    "questionId": "41faf6cbafb3c993079daefaf1612636",
    "questionType": "multiple-choice"
  },
  {
    "answer": "Pokemon",
    "category": "video-games",
    "choices": [
      "Final Fantasy",
      "Pokemon",
      "Magic the Gathering",
      "Yu-Gi-Oh"
    ],
    "newCategory": "Video Games",
    "question": "This sound clip is from what Game Boy game that spawned an anime TV show and a collectible card game?",
    "questionId": "0ec3f5524449d8623b7abcd4454b0273",
    "questionType": "multiple-choice"
  },
  {
    "answer": "Age of Empires II",
    "category": "video-games",
    "choices": [
      "Age of Empires II",
      "StarCraft",
      "Command and Conquer",
      "Warcraft III"
    ],
    "newCategory": "Video Games",
    "question": "This sound clip is from what PC RTS game?",
    "questionId": "6603be4c3c3fa8a7bff9806923317fd9",
    "questionType": "multiple-choice"
  },
  {
    "answer": "The Legend of Zelda: Ocarina of Time",
    "category": "video-games",
    "choices": [
      "The Legend of Zelda: A Link to the Past",
      "The Legend of Zelda",
      "The Legend of Zelda: The Wind Waker",
      "The Legend of Zelda: Ocarina of Time"
    ],
    "newCategory": "Video Games",
    "question": "This sound clip is a theme in which of the following Legend of Zelda games?",
    "questionId": "88138d1e193c35bce5983e2e7c7c87b8",
    "questionType": "multiple-choice"
  },
  {
    "answer": "Star Fox",
    "category": "video-games",
    "choices": [
      "Star Wars: Rouge Squadron",
      "Final Fantasy",
      "Star Fox",
      "Halo"
    ],
    "newCategory": "Video Games",
    "question": "This sound clip is from what video game series?",
    "questionId": "aeb4ec308952e1e1818c3c09ab8df895",
    "questionType": "multiple-choice"
  },
  {
    "answer": "Kamino",
    "category": "video-games",
    "choices": [
      "Death Star",
      "Kamino",
      "Bespin",
      "Mustafar"
    ],
    "newCategory": "Video Games",
    "question": "Which of these levels is on both Star Wars: Battlefront 1 and 2?",
    "questionId": "adb144dd36c14dd07afc5f2c3469aa39",
    "questionType": "multiple-choice"
  },
  {
    "answer": "False",
    "category": "video-games",
    "newCategory": "Video Games",
    "question": "You can control Jedi on both Star Wars: Battlefront 1 and 2.",
    "questionId": "6e2ef9876f0738e187d0c31fa51fa8d0",
    "questionType": "true-false"
  },
  {
    "answer": "180",
    "category": "video-games",
    "choices": [
      "500",
      "200",
      "10",
      "180"
    ],
    "newCategory": "Video Games",
    "question": "What is the default number of points to destroy a ship in a space battle on Star Wars: Battlefront 2?",
    "questionId": "6bc709a7279fe422abdbdf9df26bcf74",
    "questionType": "multiple-choice"
  },
  {
    "answer": "Endurance, Guardian, War Hero",
    "category": "video-games",
    "choices": [
      "Endurance, Guardian, War Hero",
      "Guardian, Endurance, War Hero",
      "War Hero, Guardian, Endurance",
      "Marksman, Demolition, Technician"
    ],
    "newCategory": "Video Games",
    "question": "Choose the correct order for player points bonuses in Star Wars: Battlefront from least to greatest.",
    "questionId": "c4ed87f695855a338509b31b941c13ce",
    "questionType": "multiple-choice"
  },
  {
    "answer": "True",
    "category": "video-games",
    "newCategory": "Video Games",
    "question": "The two levels on Kashyyyk on Star Wars: Battlefront 1 are Islands and Docks.",
    "questionId": "5998711fada9e1f306ad595b819b5928",
    "questionType": "true-false"
  },
  {
    "answer": "Jawas",
    "category": "video-games",
    "choices": [
      "Mace Windu",
      "Heavy weapons soldier",
      "Luke Skywalker",
      "Jawas"
    ],
    "newCategory": "Video Games",
    "question": "On the Star Wars: Battlefront game, which of these is among the non-player characters of the game?",
    "questionId": "34bc0f529c641fa9d3cd39b2738cb47b",
    "questionType": "multiple-choice"
  },
  {
    "answer": "Empire",
    "category": "video-games",
    "choices": [
      "Empire",
      "Rebels",
      "Republic",
      "CIS"
    ],
    "newCategory": "Video Games",
    "question": "Who controls the AT-ATs on Hoth in Star Wars: Battlefront?",
    "questionId": "31d43ad939415bf1ba37c91d24f1d4d7",
    "questionType": "multiple-choice"
  },
  {
    "answer": "Doomhammer",
    "category": "video-games",
    "choices": [
      "Warsong",
      "Death Spear",
      "Black Rock",
      "Doomhammer"
    ],
    "newCategory": "Video Games",
    "question": "Warchief Thrall is the leader of which clan?",
    "questionId": "e3b5cde31b14071625833e502219f311",
    "questionType": "multiple-choice"
  },
  {
    "answer": "Black Dragon",
    "category": "video-games",
    "choices": [
      "Black Dragon",
      "Red Dragon",
      "Bone Dragon",
      "Green Dragon"
    ],
    "newCategory": "Video Games",
    "question": "What type of creature is the DeathWing?",
    "questionId": "c8c255bd12cc4b101c93da230638a9ac",
    "questionType": "multiple-choice"
  },
  {
    "answer": "Prince Arthas as Dead Knight",
    "category": "video-games",
    "choices": [
      "Ghoul",
      "Druid of the Claw",
      "Prince Arthas as Dead Knight",
      "Prince Arthas"
    ],
    "newCategory": "Video Games",
    "question": "What unit or hero does the phrase Speak up fool belong to?",
    "questionId": "0a00444d5fee4fedddb7c13248410297",
    "questionType": "multiple-choice"
  },
  {
    "answer": "Grom Hellscream",
    "category": "video-games",
    "choices": [
      "Thrall",
      "Prince Arthas",
      "Grom Hellscream",
      "Illidan Stormrage"
    ],
    "newCategory": "Video Games",
    "question": "Who kills Mannoroth?",
    "questionId": "606a0722120e8d9acf4df6bf9dee6552",
    "questionType": "multiple-choice"
  },
  {
    "answer": "Dwarf Rifleman",
    "category": "video-games",
    "choices": [
      "muradin bronzebeard",
      "Human Footman",
      "Dwarf Rifleman",
      "Throll Hunter"
    ],
    "newCategory": "Video Games",
    "question": "What unit or hero does this phrase belong to?",
    "questionId": "c6576a016df121616adf7b1c40132eb2",
    "questionType": "multiple-choice"
  },
  {
    "answer": "Ancient of Lore",
    "category": "video-games",
    "choices": [
      "Ancient of Lore",
      "Ancient of Wind",
      "Ancient of Wisdom",
      "Ancient of War"
    ],
    "newCategory": "Video Games",
    "question": "Which building makes the Druid of the Claw unit?",
    "questionId": "cf0bb644f8898b8f275cd5a605e64d71",
    "questionType": "multiple-choice"
  },
  {
    "answer": "Huntresses",
    "category": "video-games",
    "choices": [
      "Wind Druids",
      "Head Hunters",
      "Huntresses",
      "Archers"
    ],
    "newCategory": "Video Games",
    "question": "Who rides \u0093Nightsabre Panthers\u0094?",
    "questionId": "f0188e33c2571b22ad53edfee1b5e268",
    "questionType": "multiple-choice"
  },
  {
    "answer": "Grom Hellscream",
    "category": "video-games",
    "choices": [
      "Thrall",
      "Shadow Hunter",
      "Grom Hellscream",
      "Thief"
    ],
    "newCategory": "Video Games",
    "question": "What unit or hero does the phrase \u0093I can see clearly, now the rain has gone\u0094 belong to?",
    "questionId": "ca3517699abc88ece86a7d6391240839",
    "questionType": "multiple-choice"
  },
  {
    "answer": "False",
    "category": "video-games",
    "newCategory": "Video Games",
    "question": "In the Pokemon TV series, Ash saw a Gyarados in the first episode.",
    "questionId": "8e82895f537cee2ee862dcc79f8e3bf0",
    "questionType": "true-false"
  },
  {
    "answer": "Red",
    "category": "video-games",
    "choices": [
      "Blue",
      "Yellow",
      "Green",
      "Red"
    ],
    "newCategory": "Video Games",
    "question": "On what other character is Ash Ketchum loosely based in the Pokemon video games?",
    "questionId": "633b72dd9aa644a4fd8fa99dff42234b",
    "questionType": "multiple-choice"
  },
  {
    "answer": "false",
    "category": "video-games",
    "newCategory": "Video Games",
    "question": "Is the Pokemon character Raikou included in any of the first ten Pokemon movies?:removeme",
    "questionId": "bfe4b199e0f4bb6270de3ee62a287239",
    "questionType": "true-false"
  },
  {
    "answer": "Johto Journeys",
    "category": "video-games",
    "choices": [
      "Johto",
      "Johto Quest",
      "Johto Journeys",
      "Master Quest"
    ],
    "newCategory": "Video Games",
    "question": "What is the first season of Johto called in Pokemon series?",
    "questionId": "cb2ce4cd3cfa0d7566684962249c2f3b",
    "questionType": "multiple-choice"
  },
  {
    "answer": "false",
    "category": "video-games",
    "newCategory": "Video Games",
    "question": "Was the tenth Pokemon movie released simultaneously in Japan and the USA?:removeme",
    "questionId": "540ec8e11375a094545c6ddabe193452",
    "questionType": "true-false"
  },
  {
    "answer": "Seaform Islands",
    "category": "video-games",
    "choices": [
      "Celadon City",
      "Seaform Islands",
      "Cinnabar Island",
      "Fusia city"
    ],
    "newCategory": "Video Games",
    "question": "Where can you find the gym leader Blaine in the video games Pokemon Gold and Silver and Pokemon Crystal?",
    "questionId": "6cc1efb7b18e8d9dc0fc55ed8dc94f5f",
    "questionType": "multiple-choice"
  },
  {
    "answer": "BMW M3 GTR",
    "category": "video-games",
    "choices": [
      "Golf GTI",
      "BMW M3 GTR",
      "Corvette C6",
      "Lamborghini Gallardo"
    ],
    "newCategory": "Video Games",
    "question": "What is the very first car you drive in the Need for Speed: Most Wanted game?",
    "questionId": "6efc8c5fadf80317ce8967f20a476d2d",
    "questionType": "multiple-choice"
  },
  {
    "answer": "False",
    "category": "video-games",
    "newCategory": "Video Games",
    "question": "There are a total of 20 blacklist drivers in the game Need for Speed: Most Wanted.",
    "questionId": "e116db06de26e1ee22faae457c574b4b",
    "questionType": "true-false"
  },
  {
    "answer": "Razor, JV, Kaze, Sonny",
    "category": "video-games",
    "choices": [
      "Razor, JV, Kaze, Sonny",
      "Taz, Big Lou, Baron, Ronnie",
      "Kaze, Big Lou, Bull, Razor",
      "Webster, Vic, Izzy, Bull"
    ],
    "newCategory": "Video Games",
    "question": "In the racing game Need for Speed: Most Wanted, what are the street names of Blacklist numbers 1, 4, 7, and 15?",
    "questionId": "ad18b883fd6e0459ca18f3861696a6d4",
    "questionType": "multiple-choice"
  },
  {
    "answer": "8",
    "category": "video-games",
    "choices": [
      "10",
      "9",
      "8",
      "7"
    ],
    "newCategory": "Video Games",
    "question": "How many maximum infractions can you get in a single pursuit in the game Need for Speed: Most Wanted?",
    "questionId": "4d5f61b0926d0b1a755552781ad9f81a",
    "questionType": "multiple-choice"
  },
  {
    "answer": "true",
    "category": "video-games",
    "newCategory": "Video Games",
    "question": "Do you have a rap sheet in the game Need for Speed: Most Wanted?:removeme",
    "questionId": "f447399cc1273ced3a40c27e912f6c65",
    "questionType": "true-false"
  },
  {
    "answer": "pink slip",
    "category": "video-games",
    "choices": [
      "pink slip",
      "gold bars",
      "orange tye",
      "thong wrap"
    ],
    "newCategory": "Video Games",
    "question": "Which of the following refers to the ability to win a Blacklist opponents car in the game Need for Speed: Most Wanted?",
    "questionId": "2746e6303e2e00ac775f02bbdd3a1bbc",
    "questionType": "multiple-choice"
  },
  {
    "answer": "Rockport",
    "category": "video-games",
    "choices": [
      "Johan City",
      "Rockport",
      "Goodwales",
      "Amberhill"
    ],
    "newCategory": "Video Games",
    "question": "In the racing game Need for Speed: Most Wanted, where is is Blacklist number one located?",
    "questionId": "3002e5a28eb8011c5b83b2dac28d3913",
    "questionType": "multiple-choice"
  },
  {
    "answer": "Koji Kondo",
    "category": "video-games",
    "choices": [
      "Nobuo Uematsu",
      "Koji Kondo",
      "Yasunori Mitsuda",
      "Shigeru Miyamoto"
    ],
    "newCategory": "Video Games",
    "question": "Who created the theme song of the Super Mario Brothers game?",
    "questionId": "c0f4e6f6c5bd2b6fa00d0b9c9cae0025",
    "questionType": "multiple-choice"
  },
  {
    "answer": "True",
    "category": "video-games",
    "newCategory": "Video Games",
    "question": "Shigeru Miyamoto constructed the arcade game Donkey Kongs music himself, using an Electronic Keyboard.",
    "questionId": "9ee88b517b2a0dc398c9a0537a3e0ea2",
    "questionType": "true-false"
  },
  {
    "answer": "Atari 2600",
    "category": "video-games",
    "choices": [
      "Sega Master System",
      "Intellivision",
      "Atari 2600",
      "Nintendo Entertainment System (NES)"
    ],
    "newCategory": "Video Games",
    "question": "The core of this gaming console, released in 1977, was combined with a display and sound chip known as the TIA, for Television Interface Adaptor. The console was capable of producing 2 channel mono sound.",
    "questionId": "3a9438438401b48bbf0948a3638842c4",
    "questionType": "multiple-choice"
  },
  {
    "answer": "Sound Interface Device",
    "category": "video-games",
    "choices": [
      "Sound Interface Disk",
      "Sound Interface Component",
      "Sound Interface Device",
      "Sound Interface Chip"
    ],
    "newCategory": "Video Games",
    "question": "The sound chip of the Commodore 64 home computer, released in 1982, was very advanced for its time. It had three channels with several different waveforms, which could reach 8 different octaves each (approximately 16 - 4000 Hz). Name the chip.",
    "questionId": "64b7c7590a6a16b11dcb936753061a76",
    "questionType": "multiple-choice"
  },
  {
    "answer": "20",
    "category": "video-games",
    "choices": [
      "25",
      "30",
      "20",
      "15"
    ],
    "newCategory": "Video Games",
    "question": "My rogue in the game Dungeons and Dragons wants to use a wand of Greater Invisibility. In order to do this he must make a Use Magic Device check at what Difficulty Class?",
    "questionId": "3dea2290b93db93889ce00dabad01be8",
    "questionType": "multiple-choice"
  },
  {
    "answer": "Dodge",
    "category": "video-games",
    "choices": [
      "Dodge",
      "Enchantment",
      "Armor",
      "Divine"
    ],
    "newCategory": "Video Games",
    "question": "Which of the listed bonuses in the game Dungeons and Dragons stacks?",
    "questionId": "c7c09770855e414eeb2e625888ccde81",
    "questionType": "multiple-choice"
  },
  {
    "answer": "Flyby Attack",
    "category": "video-games",
    "choices": [
      "Spring Attack",
      "Flyby Attack",
      "Improved Unarmed Strike",
      "Improved Trip"
    ],
    "newCategory": "Video Games",
    "question": "Which of these feats does not prevent attacks of opportunity in one form or another in the role-playing game Dungeons and Dragons?",
    "questionId": "ca4b0b14a948935d1ddae352ee77408a",
    "questionType": "multiple-choice"
  },
  {
    "answer": "Nature",
    "category": "video-games",
    "choices": [
      "Dungeoneering",
      "Religion",
      "Arcane",
      "Nature"
    ],
    "newCategory": "Video Games",
    "question": "Which Knowledge Skill would allow you to determine the type of Giant you are facing in Dungeons and Dragons?",
    "questionId": "b9b9076fc975f76e1949fdffdfa07e05",
    "questionType": "multiple-choice"
  },
  {
    "answer": "Gather Information",
    "category": "video-games",
    "choices": [
      "Diplomacy",
      "Intimidate",
      "Sleight of Hand",
      "Gather Information"
    ],
    "newCategory": "Video Games",
    "question": "In the game Dungeons and Dragons, a character with 5 ranks in Bluff gains a +2 synergy bonus to all these skills but one. Which is the odd one?",
    "questionId": "d1322bcb177fc263154f732d084d2474",
    "questionType": "multiple-choice"
  },
  {
    "answer": "Disguise 8 ranks",
    "category": "video-games",
    "choices": [
      "Disguise 8 ranks",
      "Move Silently 8 ranks",
      "Hide 8 ranks",
      "Alignment: Any evil"
    ],
    "newCategory": "Video Games",
    "question": "Which of these is not a correct entrance requirement to join the Assassin Prestige Class in Dungeons and Dragons?",
    "questionId": "e8ae634eecc0b71deac6451d7956267d",
    "questionType": "multiple-choice"
  },
  {
    "answer": "Magic, Lawful, Adamantine",
    "category": "video-games",
    "choices": [
      "Magic, Adamantine, Lawful",
      "Lawful, Magic, Adamantine",
      "Magic, Lawful, Adamantine",
      "Adamantine, Magic, Lawful"
    ],
    "newCategory": "Video Games",
    "question": "In the game Dungeons and Dragons, Aamonks Ki Strike ability evolves in what order?",
    "questionId": "734c32bdfa5c65298c90233834a2cbd8",
    "questionType": "multiple-choice"
  },
  {
    "answer": "35",
    "category": "video-games",
    "choices": [
      "30",
      "35",
      "40",
      "25"
    ],
    "newCategory": "Video Games",
    "question": "In Dungeons and Dragons, the Tumble Difficulty Class needed to kip up, according the Complete Adventurer book, is what?",
    "questionId": "4ace94cd3e3752ae11de1e7502fcd83a",
    "questionType": "multiple-choice"
  },
  {
    "answer": "Barbarian",
    "category": "video-games",
    "choices": [
      "Monk",
      "Rogue",
      "Ranger",
      "Barbarian"
    ],
    "newCategory": "Video Games",
    "question": "Which class in Dungeons and Dragons does not get evasion?",
    "questionId": "b8d3f83b7fdf343ed46d085eff17330c",
    "questionType": "multiple-choice"
  },
  {
    "answer": "5",
    "category": "video-games",
    "choices": [
      "6",
      "4",
      "3",
      "5"
    ],
    "newCategory": "Video Games",
    "question": "Of the choices for a Rangers favored enemy in Dungeons and Dragons, which number is immune to sneak attacks?",
    "questionId": "39e49675de44b461e9ca50ce92057e36",
    "questionType": "multiple-choice"
  },
  {
    "answer": "35",
    "category": "video-games",
    "choices": [
      "35",
      "10",
      "20",
      "30"
    ],
    "newCategory": "Video Games",
    "question": "How many golden skulltulas could you get as child Link out of the whole game The Legend of Zelda: Ocarina of Time?",
    "questionId": "f8ae1ee7b248f46520791d146ec0661a",
    "questionType": "multiple-choice"
  },
  {
    "answer": "24",
    "category": "video-games",
    "choices": [
      "5",
      "24",
      "20",
      "10"
    ],
    "newCategory": "Video Games",
    "question": "How many heart pieces can you get as adult Link in the game The Legend of Zelda: Ocarina of Time?",
    "questionId": "7b3aa46ba633ec99e768990363149c8f",
    "questionType": "multiple-choice"
  },
  {
    "answer": "Kakariko Graveyard and Hyrule town market.",
    "category": "video-games",
    "choices": [
      "lake Hylia and Hyrule castle.",
      "Haunted Wasteland and Zoras domain.",
      "Goron city and Kokiri forest.",
      "Kakariko Graveyard and Hyrule town market."
    ],
    "newCategory": "Video Games",
    "question": "In the video game The Legend of Zelda: Ocarina of Time, what are the two places where you can get the hylian shield?",
    "questionId": "3a20b001039e98225f57b234d48fbeb7",
    "questionType": "multiple-choice"
  },
  {
    "answer": "four",
    "category": "video-games",
    "choices": [
      "one",
      "six",
      "three",
      "four"
    ],
    "newCategory": "Video Games",
    "question": "In The Legend of Zelda: Ocarina of Time, how many items do you get that are improved later in the game?",
    "questionId": "398085e287272517024cb87ce46da1bd",
    "questionType": "multiple-choice"
  },
  {
    "answer": "9",
    "category": "video-games",
    "choices": [
      "11",
      "7",
      "10",
      "9"
    ],
    "newCategory": "Video Games",
    "question": "In The Legend of Zelda: Ocarina of Time, how many items do you trade to get the Biggorons sword?",
    "questionId": "d8ae37c7b1e5263e597dcb2f0265d526",
    "questionType": "multiple-choice"
  },
  {
    "answer": "False",
    "category": "video-games",
    "newCategory": "Video Games",
    "question": "In the video game The Legend of Zelda: Ocarina of Time, Link wore tunics in three colors. They were green, red and yellow.",
    "questionId": "362726d423d57a364a970b40b70a76b4",
    "questionType": "true-false"
  },
  {
    "answer": "6",
    "category": "video-games",
    "choices": [
      "3",
      "5",
      "6",
      "2"
    ],
    "newCategory": "Video Games",
    "question": "How many hidden fairy fountains are there in the game The Legend of Zelda: Ocarina of Time, not counting the great fairies?",
    "questionId": "a88cc1c60a7fca94a0d183c7eaee7a72",
    "questionType": "multiple-choice"
  },
  {
    "answer": "Blood-Elf",
    "category": "video-games",
    "choices": [
      "Warlock",
      "Paladin",
      "Blood-Elf",
      "Druid"
    ],
    "newCategory": "Video Games",
    "question": "Which of the following is NOT a character class in World of Warcraft?",
    "questionId": "8fb3421c670e06645c4a03c4c8daa958",
    "questionType": "multiple-choice"
  },
  {
    "answer": "Gnome",
    "category": "video-games",
    "choices": [
      "Draenei",
      "Gnome",
      "Dwarf",
      "Tauren"
    ],
    "newCategory": "Video Games",
    "question": "Which of the following races cannot play a Hunter in World of Warcraft?",
    "questionId": "19e76a8ba1a7c771767d7e5fc11efba4",
    "questionType": "multiple-choice"
  },
  {
    "answer": "True",
    "category": "video-games",
    "newCategory": "Video Games",
    "question": "The Horde and the Alliance are the two playable factions in World of Warcraft.",
    "questionId": "c7b21b81eed929b5149fbea6c54751d4",
    "questionType": "true-false"
  },
  {
    "answer": "False",
    "category": "video-games",
    "newCategory": "Video Games",
    "question": "In World of Warcraft, it is possible to fly from Theramore to Stormwind.",
    "questionId": "b7eb347cdb4108553b27d88309029ea2",
    "questionType": "true-false"
  },
  {
    "answer": "False",
    "category": "video-games",
    "newCategory": "Video Games",
    "question": "In World of Warcraft, it is sometimes necessary to fight other groups of players inside an instance.",
    "questionId": "4c5561ca1bd0668209c70f8007b9368b",
    "questionType": "true-false"
  },
  {
    "answer": "RP",
    "category": "video-games",
    "choices": [
      "PvP",
      "RP",
      "RP-PvP",
      "Normal"
    ],
    "newCategory": "Video Games",
    "question": "Which of the following is not a realm type in World of Warcraft?",
    "questionId": "7ce88cf9db712014d0ea29007444b4e0",
    "questionType": "multiple-choice"
  },
  {
    "answer": "The Number of the Beast",
    "category": "video-games",
    "choices": [
      "The Metal",
      "Enter Sandman",
      "One",
      "The Number of the Beast"
    ],
    "newCategory": "Video Games",
    "question": "What is the Iron Maiden song performed in Guitar Hero 3?",
    "questionId": "369249cb53bdbb585215232cddb1e853",
    "questionType": "multiple-choice"
  },
  {
    "answer": "Foghat",
    "category": "video-games",
    "choices": [
      "Foghat",
      "Metallica",
      "ZZ Top",
      "Sonic Youth"
    ],
    "newCategory": "Video Games",
    "question": "Who sings Slow Ride, one of the songs included in Guitar Hero 3?",
    "questionId": "e43edd48dfbb8bd9d93454cbacac0c37",
    "questionType": "multiple-choice"
  },
  {
    "answer": "The Metal",
    "category": "video-games",
    "choices": [
      "Lou",
      "Bulls On Parade",
      "Anarchy in the U.K.",
      "The Metal"
    ],
    "newCategory": "Video Games",
    "question": "What song by Tenacious D appeared in the video game Guitar Hero 3?",
    "questionId": "e6dcab720fd47f4de010c933de916fb5",
    "questionType": "multiple-choice"
  },
  {
    "answer": "False",
    "category": "video-games",
    "newCategory": "Video Games",
    "question": "Tom Morello is a member of the band Sonic Youth.",
    "questionId": "a9451e53b04b06393ff8d06ff64464fa",
    "questionType": "true-false"
  },
  {
    "answer": "Backyard Bash",
    "category": "video-games",
    "choices": [
      "Fenway Park",
      "Backyard Bash",
      "Yankee Stadium",
      "Mitchs Moose Lounge"
    ],
    "newCategory": "Video Games",
    "question": "What is the first place you get a gig at on Guitar Hero 3?",
    "questionId": "f74ed618867581b6f2d468e2367dac4e",
    "questionType": "multiple-choice"
  },
  {
    "answer": "Level it up after learning ancient power.",
    "category": "video-games",
    "choices": [
      "Level it up after learning ancient power.",
      "Trade it while holding a growth incense.",
      "Use a leaf stone on it.",
      "Level it up."
    ],
    "newCategory": "Video Games",
    "question": "What is the way to evolve the pokemon Tangela to tangrowth in the Diamond and Pearl Pokemon series?",
    "questionId": "523129ad0ad3294e4692ad8ad723ae98",
    "questionType": "multiple-choice"
  },
  {
    "answer": "Trade Rhydon up while holding a protector.",
    "category": "video-games",
    "choices": [
      "Level Rhydon up.",
      "Trade Rhydon up while holding a hard stone.",
      "Trade Rhydon up while holding a protector.",
      "Trade Rhydon."
    ],
    "newCategory": "Video Games",
    "question": "How do you evolve Rhydon into Rhyperior in the Diamond and Pearl Pokemon series?",
    "questionId": "95f26bd9fb29957d89584b185cf008c0",
    "questionType": "multiple-choice"
  },
  {
    "answer": "None of these",
    "category": "video-games",
    "choices": [
      "Trade it.",
      "Trade it holding a razor fang.",
      "None of these",
      "Level up."
    ],
    "newCategory": "Video Games",
    "question": "In what way can you evolve the pokemon Gilgar into Gliscor in the Diamond and Pearl Pokemon series for Nintendo DS?",
    "questionId": "4944447fa20c28a7804171b49b85ef49",
    "questionType": "multiple-choice"
  },
  {
    "answer": "Trade it while holding a electrizer.",
    "category": "video-games",
    "choices": [
      "None of these",
      "Trade it while holding a electrizer.",
      "Give it a electrizer.",
      "Train it while holding a electrizer."
    ],
    "newCategory": "Video Games",
    "question": "How do you evolve an Electabuzz into an Electrivire in the Diamond and Pearl Pokemon series?",
    "questionId": "8c463e174bb1a34c31e9b8b9eec93d11",
    "questionType": "multiple-choice"
  },
  {
    "answer": "Give it a dubious disc and trade it.",
    "category": "video-games",
    "choices": [
      "Give it an upgrade and trade it.",
      "Give it a tech disc and trade it.",
      "Level it up.",
      "Give it a dubious disc and trade it."
    ],
    "newCategory": "Video Games",
    "question": "In Pokemon Diamond and Pearl, in what way do you evolve a Porygon2 into a Porygon-Z?",
    "questionId": "6eb6d14f5d6f77eaa08a9d0710c6ed5c",
    "questionType": "multiple-choice"
  },
  {
    "answer": "At level 33 let Yanma learn anchient power.",
    "category": "video-games",
    "choices": [
      "At level 33 let Yanma learn rollout.",
      "At level 33 let Yanma learn silver wind.",
      "None of these",
      "At level 33 let Yanma learn anchient power."
    ],
    "newCategory": "Video Games",
    "question": "What is the way to evolve a Yanma into a Yanmega in the Diamond and Pearl Pokemon series for Nintendo DS?",
    "questionId": "a30305f8ac06e4140811e623ab508544",
    "questionType": "multiple-choice"
  },
  {
    "answer": "None of these",
    "category": "video-games",
    "choices": [
      "Use a dawn stone on Kirlia.",
      "Trade Kirlia.",
      "Use a dawn stone on a female Kirlia.",
      "None of these"
    ],
    "newCategory": "Video Games",
    "question": "Which of these is the correct way to evolve a Kirlia into a Gallade in Pokemon Diamond and Pearl?",
    "questionId": "2ebb84b5253b03852c247fd6a1dda812",
    "questionType": "multiple-choice"
  },
  {
    "answer": "Use a dawn stone on a female Snorunt.",
    "category": "video-games",
    "choices": [
      "Use a dawn stone on a male Snorunt.",
      "Use a shiny stone on a male Snorunt.",
      "Use a dawn stone on a female Snorunt.",
      "Use a shiny stone on a females Snorunt."
    ],
    "newCategory": "Video Games",
    "question": "In what way can you evolve the pokemon Snorunt into a Frosslass in the Diamond and Pearl Pokemon series for Nintendo DS?",
    "questionId": "54072f0b086bb2681e116499e254e34b",
    "questionType": "multiple-choice"
  },
  {
    "answer": "Trade a Dusclops that is holding a reapers cloth.",
    "category": "video-games",
    "choices": [
      "Trade a Dusclops.",
      "Train Dusclops at night.",
      "Trade a Dusclops that is holding a reapers cloth.",
      "None of these"
    ],
    "newCategory": "Video Games",
    "question": "How do you evolve a Dusclops into a Duskinoir in Pokemon Diamond and Pearl?",
    "questionId": "6d21a4bf5c8ef6aad92774635dd1ddaf",
    "questionType": "multiple-choice"
  },
  {
    "answer": "Zanarkand",
    "category": "video-games",
    "choices": [
      "Zanarkand",
      "Mt. Gagazet",
      "Besaid",
      "Kilika"
    ],
    "newCategory": "Video Games",
    "question": "At what location does the PS2 role-playing game Final Fantasy X start?",
    "questionId": "a6ce4e12ba41425699cd3fa38f49490f",
    "questionType": "multiple-choice"
  },
  {
    "answer": "Auron",
    "category": "video-games",
    "choices": [
      "Rikku",
      "Kimhari",
      "Auron",
      "Yuna"
    ],
    "newCategory": "Video Games",
    "question": "Which other team member do you meet first in the PS2 game Final Fantasy X?",
    "questionId": "ec903d62455c0963b33d8b5c0730b13c",
    "questionType": "multiple-choice"
  },
  {
    "answer": "Kilika",
    "category": "video-games",
    "choices": [
      "Kilika",
      "Besaid",
      "Djos\u00e9",
      "Home"
    ],
    "newCategory": "Video Games",
    "question": "In Final Fantasy X, where does Yuna perform her first Sending?",
    "questionId": "fcef24fe810ef2fafa39e67a96c6acf5",
    "questionType": "multiple-choice"
  },
  {
    "answer": "False",
    "category": "video-games",
    "newCategory": "Video Games",
    "question": "In Final Fantasy X, when you enter the Farplane in Guadosalam to talk to Yunas father, Auron stays behind because he is scared of confronting Jecht.",
    "questionId": "13a64a118497516a3500c44ec3addd6c",
    "questionType": "true-false"
  },
  {
    "answer": "Ronso Rovers",
    "category": "video-games",
    "choices": [
      "Guado Glories",
      "Besiad Aurochs",
      "Ronso Rovers",
      "Luca Goers"
    ],
    "newCategory": "Video Games",
    "question": "Which of these is not a blitzball team from the PS2 game Final Fantasy X?",
    "questionId": "022b2f3c100c6319c648ca4a552bae0d",
    "questionType": "multiple-choice"
  },
  {
    "answer": "Kilika, Macalania, Calm Lands, Besaid, Requiem, Djose",
    "category": "video-games",
    "choices": [
      "Djose, Requiem, Besaid, Macalania, Calm Lands, Kilika",
      "Kilika, Macalania, Calm Lands, Besaid, Requiem, Djose",
      "Macalania, Kilika, Calm Lands, Gagazet, Requiem, Djose.",
      "Kilika, Djose, Calm Lands, Requiem, Besiad, Macalania"
    ],
    "newCategory": "Video Games",
    "question": "In Final Fantasy X, where do you get each of the following aeons respectively: Ifrit, Shiva, Yojimbo, Valefor, Magus Sisters, Ixion?",
    "questionId": "caefa041e162f23919a70b0dfe735d94",
    "questionType": "multiple-choice"
  },
  {
    "answer": "In the Sea of Sorrows inside Sin",
    "category": "video-games",
    "choices": [
      "On top of Mt. Gagazet",
      "On the Highroad in Bevelle",
      "Outside Besaid",
      "In the Sea of Sorrows inside Sin"
    ],
    "newCategory": "Video Games",
    "question": "Where is Maester Seymour the final time you have to fight him in the PS2 role-playing game Final Fantasy X?",
    "questionId": "4cdae5e2666d4ab7c675e126d1710a29",
    "questionType": "multiple-choice"
  },
  {
    "answer": "Why are you taking a quiz?",
    "category": "video-games",
    "choices": [
      "How can you ignore a call?",
      "Did you see Tidus swim?",
      "Why not see snakes a rule!",
      "Why are you taking a quiz?"
    ],
    "newCategory": "Video Games",
    "question": "According to Final Fantasy X, what does this sentence in the Al Bhed language translate to: Xna ehi ayo degurk e wouj?",
    "questionId": "ff1ee220f173a872e9efe13821457833",
    "questionType": "multiple-choice"
  },
  {
    "answer": "The dreams that have faded",
    "category": "video-games",
    "choices": [
      "The friends who have gone",
      "Stand by your friends",
      "The dreams that have faded",
      "Life is a game of blitzball"
    ],
    "newCategory": "Video Games",
    "question": "In Yunas speech at the end of Final Fantasy X, what phrase is an almost direct reference to Tidus?",
    "questionId": "eb3503d3cf0f43426f6e0f6a5aa155a7",
    "questionType": "multiple-choice"
  },
  {
    "answer": "Enables you to talk to Saria",
    "category": "video-games",
    "choices": [
      "Enables you to fly",
      "Teleports you to the Hyrule Castle",
      "Teleports you anywhere",
      "Enables you to talk to Saria"
    ],
    "newCategory": "Video Games",
    "question": "What does Sarias Song do in Legend of Zelda Ocarina of Time?",
    "questionId": "54007f7ffcc4abf7f5f79efd3425a31a",
    "questionType": "multiple-choice"
  },
  {
    "answer": "False",
    "category": "video-games",
    "newCategory": "Video Games",
    "question": "In Legend of Zelda Majoras Mask you are transformed into a Zora by Ganondorf.",
    "questionId": "bc865cb8a4ad3e604cf720374f1d1ce9",
    "questionType": "true-false"
  },
  {
    "answer": "true",
    "category": "video-games",
    "newCategory": "Video Games",
    "question": "Is it true that in Legend of Zelda Twilight Princess, after you get the Master Sword you can transform into a wolf any time you like?:removeme",
    "questionId": "1318b719cc7e3d91785eddeb5062d825",
    "questionType": "true-false"
  },
  {
    "answer": "true",
    "category": "video-games",
    "newCategory": "Video Games",
    "question": "Is it true that in Legend of Zelda and the Wind Waker, after you beat the game you can make a new file and not get Links green clothing?:removeme",
    "questionId": "f78f434d607a50bfb09e1f13f099e953",
    "questionType": "true-false"
  },
  {
    "answer": "True",
    "category": "video-games",
    "newCategory": "Video Games",
    "question": "In Legend of Zelda Ocarina of Time, once you pull out the Master Sword you will become older.",
    "questionId": "d28eef724d1fcfdcef204b6a9170935b",
    "questionType": "true-false"
  },
  {
    "answer": "true",
    "category": "video-games",
    "newCategory": "Video Games",
    "question": "Is it true that in the whole Legend of Zelda series, the currency is rupees?:removeme",
    "questionId": "4800884c48fab3f977b92a8e7d8a3e9a",
    "questionType": "true-false"
  },
  {
    "answer": "Zoras Domain",
    "category": "video-games",
    "choices": [
      "Deku Tree",
      "Zoras Domain",
      "Death Moutain",
      "Sky World"
    ],
    "newCategory": "Video Games",
    "question": "Where can you find the Spiritual Gem of Water in Legend of Zelda and the Ocarina of Time?",
    "questionId": "8aaab197773e73f1c67a97bb80b77c87",
    "questionType": "multiple-choice"
  },
  {
    "answer": "Xbox/PSP/PS2",
    "category": "video-games",
    "choices": [
      "DS/Gamecube/PS3",
      "Xbox/PSP/PS2",
      "PSP/PS3/PS2",
      "PS3/PS2/DS"
    ],
    "newCategory": "Video Games",
    "question": "What game console is the strategy video game Thrillville available on?",
    "questionId": "8b5124827173493adb474db16638dc5c",
    "questionType": "multiple-choice"
  },
  {
    "answer": "False",
    "category": "video-games",
    "newCategory": "Video Games",
    "question": "In the strategy video game Thrillville, there are 4 categories in the park menu.",
    "questionId": "e03ee26450e2c211fdf1f0277aa7699c",
    "questionType": "true-false"
  },
  {
    "answer": "true",
    "category": "video-games",
    "newCategory": "Video Games",
    "question": "Can you take control of your staff members in the Thrillville video game strategy?:removeme",
    "questionId": "ead5d57f0283c4ebb02cbe23247dd3f1",
    "questionType": "true-false"
  },
  {
    "answer": "Play the flirt mini-game",
    "category": "video-games",
    "choices": [
      "Play the flirt mini-game",
      "Talk with the person",
      "A challenge the person to a mini-game off",
      "Ride rides together"
    ],
    "newCategory": "Video Games",
    "question": "In the simulation and strategy Thrillville, what is the best way to increase your attraction meter?",
    "questionId": "96e7ffb6185eb62358b493c3ed6bfef1",
    "questionType": "multiple-choice"
  },
  {
    "answer": "False",
    "category": "video-games",
    "newCategory": "Video Games",
    "question": "The video game Thrillville is rated T by the Entertainment Software Rating Board (ESRB).",
    "questionId": "2c749a9466a7ccddd6cfdf49a2d8388b",
    "questionType": "true-false"
  },
  {
    "answer": "False",
    "category": "video-games",
    "newCategory": "Video Games",
    "question": "In the Thrillville strategy video game you cant make money off of mini-games.",
    "questionId": "5d5f2aa61f925dde86039a631ccfd14b",
    "questionType": "true-false"
  },
  {
    "answer": "true",
    "category": "video-games",
    "newCategory": "Video Games",
    "question": "In the Thrillville video game, can you make money off of playing mini-golf?:removeme",
    "questionId": "4a3fe7287e0dac69b1ff3e9f64c04b5f",
    "questionType": "true-false"
  },
  {
    "answer": "True",
    "category": "video-games",
    "newCategory": "Video Games",
    "question": "You suck up trash by using a vacuum gun in the Thrillville video game.",
    "questionId": "3622be997b637d95c0c2edded94cb263",
    "questionType": "true-false"
  },
  {
    "answer": "Ness, King Dedede, Luigi, Kirby",
    "category": "video-games",
    "choices": [
      "Ness, King Dedede, Luigi, Kirby",
      "Mario, Luigi, Pit, Bowser",
      "Nobody saves them.",
      "R.O.B., Lucario, Snake"
    ],
    "newCategory": "Video Games",
    "question": "Who are the people that save the gang from Tabuu in Super Smash Bros. Brawl?",
    "questionId": "6846f1d068771d63ba20295a30b0bc44",
    "questionType": "multiple-choice"
  },
  {
    "answer": "40",
    "category": "video-games",
    "choices": [
      "There is no great maze.",
      "126",
      "999999",
      "40"
    ],
    "newCategory": "Video Games",
    "question": "How many rooms are there in the Great Maze in Super Smash Bros. Brawl?",
    "questionId": "46025cf61be1e6ce5ffdd466054c6434",
    "questionType": "multiple-choice"
  },
  {
    "answer": "Ike",
    "category": "video-games",
    "choices": [
      "Pikachu",
      "Falco",
      "Link",
      "Ike"
    ],
    "newCategory": "Video Games",
    "question": "What character from Super Smash Bros. Brawl was not in Super Smash Bros. Melee?",
    "questionId": "762948df5af732d49978c86d73b57065",
    "questionType": "multiple-choice"
  },
  {
    "answer": "3",
    "category": "video-games",
    "choices": [
      "2",
      "6",
      "1",
      "3"
    ],
    "newCategory": "Video Games",
    "question": "Including the Melee Pokemon Stadium, how many stadiums in Super Smash Bros. Brawl are related to Pokemon?",
    "questionId": "42527b8995cb59cbddfcf9a5c65f38b2",
    "questionType": "multiple-choice"
  },
  {
    "answer": "Serves as a key to open dimension ports to other worlds",
    "category": "video-games",
    "choices": [
      "Serves as a key to open dimension ports to other worlds",
      "To see the future",
      "Makes you invisible",
      "Upgrades your weapons"
    ],
    "newCategory": "Video Games",
    "question": "What is the function of the the Astral Amulet in the computer game Chrono Cross?",
    "questionId": "baca512b2dfd6f632466a42215264e6a",
    "questionType": "multiple-choice"
  },
  {
    "answer": "Ice Breath",
    "category": "video-games",
    "choices": [
      "Ice Breath",
      "Fire attack",
      "Blizzard storm",
      "Water attack"
    ],
    "newCategory": "Video Games",
    "question": "In the computer game Chrono Cross, the water dragon gives you what ability?",
    "questionId": "3b119c417844ba4cb866a4fae9df2398",
    "questionType": "multiple-choice"
  },
  {
    "answer": "Fate",
    "category": "video-games",
    "choices": [
      "Fate",
      "Kid",
      "Lynx",
      "Sarge"
    ],
    "newCategory": "Video Games",
    "question": "Who made the following statement in the game Chrono Cross: I love you so much... That is why I sometimes desire to smash you to bits!!!?",
    "questionId": "22ae04b019661133642ca223e3c8b665",
    "questionType": "multiple-choice"
  },
  {
    "answer": "Radical Dreamers",
    "category": "video-games",
    "choices": [
      "Garden of the Gods",
      "Radical Dreamers",
      "Frozen Flame",
      "Dream of the Shore Near Another World"
    ],
    "newCategory": "Video Games",
    "question": "Which of these songs from the Chrono Cross soundtrack is on the sound clip?",
    "questionId": "d6448b04af4cb2f306474dd68426c89b",
    "questionType": "multiple-choice"
  },
  {
    "answer": "Fortune Teller",
    "category": "video-games",
    "choices": [
      "Harle",
      "Kid",
      "Fortune Teller",
      "Serge"
    ],
    "newCategory": "Video Games",
    "question": "Which Chrono Cross character delivered the following words: In your eyes, I perceive both the look of a beauty and the look of a beast.?",
    "questionId": "bdf2066ab4dabcaf5bb764bb5efbd48a",
    "questionType": "multiple-choice"
  },
  {
    "answer": "Dreamwatch of time",
    "category": "video-games",
    "choices": [
      "Dreamwatch of time",
      "Radical Dreamers",
      "Time Scar",
      "Dragon Knight"
    ],
    "newCategory": "Video Games",
    "question": "Listen to the sound clip and name the song from the Chrono Cross soundtrack.",
    "questionId": "7e1c354f5ac65eff636b1bcc1cb3e786",
    "questionType": "multiple-choice"
  },
  {
    "answer": "true",
    "category": "video-games",
    "newCategory": "Video Games",
    "question": "Is Gyarados a water and flying type of Pokemon?:removeme",
    "questionId": "dbcea0806dc18e4f9ab9f05e817cbdd3",
    "questionType": "true-false"
  },
  {
    "answer": "Ghost dark",
    "category": "video-games",
    "choices": [
      "Ghost",
      "Ghost dark",
      "Ghost psychic",
      "Ghost poison"
    ],
    "newCategory": "Video Games",
    "question": "What type of Pokemon is Sableye?",
    "questionId": "845cbd0b210d13e2298f3ff399f72f7c",
    "questionType": "multiple-choice"
  },
  {
    "answer": "Rock dark",
    "category": "video-games",
    "choices": [
      "Rock dark",
      "Ground dark",
      "Ground",
      "Ground rock"
    ],
    "newCategory": "Video Games",
    "question": "What type of Pokemon is Tyranitar?",
    "questionId": "cef2b50b19bcb1c7d5257d02da38264b",
    "questionType": "multiple-choice"
  },
  {
    "answer": "False",
    "category": "video-games",
    "newCategory": "Video Games",
    "question": "Gengar is a ghost dark type of Pokemon.",
    "questionId": "90cf0cb0d6e0c10226d8c027cce511b6",
    "questionType": "true-false"
  },
  {
    "answer": "true",
    "category": "video-games",
    "newCategory": "Video Games",
    "question": "Is the Pokemon Togekiss flying and normal type of Pokemon?:removeme",
    "questionId": "ffa7b693caa751724f28cd336a8155b0",
    "questionType": "true-false"
  },
  {
    "answer": "false",
    "category": "video-games",
    "newCategory": "Video Games",
    "question": "Does the Pokemon Empolean belong only to the water type of Pokemon?:removeme",
    "questionId": "4eb590fb5166ae8989727f03ef51d05b",
    "questionType": "true-false"
  },
  {
    "answer": "true",
    "category": "video-games",
    "newCategory": "Video Games",
    "question": "Is Typlosion only a fire type of Pokemon?:removeme",
    "questionId": "70d0f1d3128183d600471b417d5bc823",
    "questionType": "true-false"
  },
  {
    "answer": "False",
    "category": "video-games",
    "newCategory": "Video Games",
    "question": "In the online game RuneScape, you can wear rune platebody without doing the quest Dragonslayer.",
    "questionId": "7e30c8f189bcb06bcb324ef9c823e544",
    "questionType": "true-false"
  },
  {
    "answer": "False",
    "category": "video-games",
    "newCategory": "Video Games",
    "question": "In the game RuneScape, big bones get your prayer level up higher than dragon bones.",
    "questionId": "bff4ef34ca56552991fa414a92a72c1d",
    "questionType": "true-false"
  },
  {
    "answer": "Horacio",
    "category": "video-games",
    "choices": [
      "Horacio",
      "Haracio",
      "Roald",
      "Royald"
    ],
    "newCategory": "Video Games",
    "question": "Name the RuneScape character who is the duke of Lumberidge.",
    "questionId": "bc7d0f12b0d6f0a534e049f760bf47f7",
    "questionType": "multiple-choice"
  },
  {
    "answer": "True",
    "category": "video-games",
    "newCategory": "Video Games",
    "question": "In the RuneScape game, you have to be level 85 to mine rune.",
    "questionId": "b0a090548232bff4dcc41681cb474be0",
    "questionType": "true-false"
  },
  {
    "answer": "False",
    "category": "video-games",
    "newCategory": "Video Games",
    "question": "In RuneScape, green dragonhide is better than black dragonhide.",
    "questionId": "0a11d82a0c99746717ece1fbf387f945",
    "questionType": "true-false"
  },
  {
    "answer": "40",
    "category": "video-games",
    "choices": [
      "50",
      "40",
      "35",
      "99"
    ],
    "newCategory": "Video Games",
    "question": "In the game RuneScape, wearing Zamorack armour requires this level.",
    "questionId": "92f18efed23a20c3ea1a0028a1b687a4",
    "questionType": "multiple-choice"
  },
  {
    "answer": "Squall, Seifer, Rinoa, Edea",
    "category": "video-games",
    "choices": [
      "Squall, Seifer, Rinoa, Edea",
      "Squall, Rinoa",
      "Squall, Seifer, Quistis",
      "Zell, Selphie, Squall"
    ],
    "newCategory": "Video Games",
    "question": "At the start of the RPG game Final Fantasy VIII, which characters are shown in the opening movie?",
    "questionId": "e5aa15689d758daeb466c118200152f0",
    "questionType": "multiple-choice"
  },
  {
    "answer": "Diablos",
    "category": "video-games",
    "choices": [
      "Ethers",
      "Ifrit",
      "Potions",
      "Diablos"
    ],
    "newCategory": "Video Games",
    "question": "What is inside the lamp given to you by Headmaster Cid before your first official SEED mission in the role-playing game Final Fantasy VIII?",
    "questionId": "461c9579f58bc115914c6ed859566a2d",
    "questionType": "multiple-choice"
  },
  {
    "answer": "To be Edeas knight",
    "category": "video-games",
    "choices": [
      "To be Edeas knight",
      "To marry Selphie",
      "To date Rinoa",
      "To go on holiday with Ade"
    ],
    "newCategory": "Video Games",
    "question": "In Final Fantasy VIII, what is Seifers romantic dream?",
    "questionId": "7a8866232be6152ecbe0efd8212f48ad",
    "questionType": "multiple-choice"
  },
  {
    "answer": "true",
    "category": "video-games",
    "newCategory": "Video Games",
    "question": "Did Quistis Trepe from Final Fantasy VIII have a group of admirers called the Trepies?:removeme",
    "questionId": "ad3fc5cca185f582fe46c2b88fe0977a",
    "questionType": "true-false"
  },
  {
    "answer": "They want to plant flowers and then invade the countries.",
    "category": "video-games",
    "choices": [
      "They want to kill as many Galbadians as possible.",
      "They want to nuke the planet and fly to a sanctuary.",
      "They want to plant flowers and then invade the countries.",
      "They want to master as many GFs as possible."
    ],
    "newCategory": "Video Games",
    "question": "What did Squall say to the torturer in D-District Prison about SEED in Final Fantasy VIII?",
    "questionId": "6aa2129b7d67f6a460b17d98ac16c20d",
    "questionType": "multiple-choice"
  },
  {
    "answer": "The Brothers",
    "category": "video-games",
    "choices": [
      "Seifer and Squall",
      "Adel and Edea",
      "The Brothers",
      "Squall and Zell"
    ],
    "newCategory": "Video Games",
    "question": "Which two characters played Rock, Paper, Scissors in the role-playing game Final Fantasy VIII?",
    "questionId": "bdfa6653b07aadfe0c1904b23dd2c374",
    "questionType": "multiple-choice"
  },
  {
    "answer": "Griever",
    "category": "video-games",
    "choices": [
      "None of these",
      "Rinoa",
      "Ultima Weapon",
      "Griever"
    ],
    "newCategory": "Video Games",
    "question": "In the last fight of the role-playing game Final Fantasy VIII, who does Ultimecia summon?",
    "questionId": "b5454a214f105a3f2a87b97bd1d6b6a5",
    "questionType": "multiple-choice"
  },
  {
    "answer": "False",
    "category": "video-games",
    "newCategory": "Video Games",
    "question": "In the game Animal Crossing, the players must work part-time for the character who gives them their first house.",
    "questionId": "9551fe969aea2829d55ceedb6403b8f1",
    "questionType": "true-false"
  },
  {
    "answer": "True",
    "category": "video-games",
    "newCategory": "Video Games",
    "question": "In the video game Animal Crossing the player can dig up fossils.",
    "questionId": "496c819d9092bde6c622011aae282dbc",
    "questionType": "true-false"
  },
  {
    "answer": "A barbers shop.",
    "category": "video-games",
    "choices": [
      "A tailors shop",
      "A dump",
      "A museum",
      "A barbers shop."
    ],
    "newCategory": "Video Games",
    "question": "Which of these is not included in the game Animal Crossing?",
    "questionId": "3c03fe1898efde116d1838ebd3185a15",
    "questionType": "multiple-choice"
  },
  {
    "answer": "True",
    "category": "video-games",
    "newCategory": "Video Games",
    "question": "In the game Animal Crossing your character may have horns.",
    "questionId": "7adc72bfbd335ed025c6a6739498776a",
    "questionType": "true-false"
  },
  {
    "answer": "true",
    "category": "video-games",
    "newCategory": "Video Games",
    "question": "Can you have pets in the game Animal Crossing?:removeme",
    "questionId": "36384276215fe08cd35dc774d4babcb1",
    "questionType": "true-false"
  },
  {
    "answer": "false",
    "category": "video-games",
    "newCategory": "Video Games",
    "question": "Can you have two houses in the Nintendo game Animal Crossing?:removeme",
    "questionId": "224bc968a3902db47fc9664fe2f877e4",
    "questionType": "true-false"
  },
  {
    "answer": "A basement",
    "category": "video-games",
    "choices": [
      "Rats",
      "A mailbox",
      "A roller-coaster",
      "A basement"
    ],
    "newCategory": "Video Games",
    "question": "What can you have in your house in the game Animal Crossing?",
    "questionId": "e9565f340d74a27ad7ed89a7b4b96e11",
    "questionType": "multiple-choice"
  },
  {
    "answer": "false",
    "category": "video-games",
    "newCategory": "Video Games",
    "question": "Can you own a shop in the game Animal Crossing?:removeme",
    "questionId": "9f759ae5ee4abc0550a635c9d1109d71",
    "questionType": "true-false"
  },
  {
    "answer": "True",
    "category": "video-games",
    "newCategory": "Video Games",
    "question": "The seasons in the game Animal Crossing change as the seasons actually change in real life.",
    "questionId": "bfabe299120351aca8e2798fa21fcc45",
    "questionType": "true-false"
  },
  {
    "answer": "a vampire",
    "category": "video-games",
    "choices": [
      "a vampire",
      "a witch",
      "a werewolf",
      "a zombie"
    ],
    "newCategory": "Video Games",
    "question": "In Runescape, what creature lives in the basement of Draynor Manor?",
    "questionId": "ad3ce5d9cb9338fd6324dddc7cffa5c1",
    "questionType": "multiple-choice"
  },
  {
    "answer": "126",
    "category": "video-games",
    "choices": [
      "99",
      "126",
      "113",
      "It never ends"
    ],
    "newCategory": "Video Games",
    "question": "What is the highest level your character can go up to in the Runescape game for non-members?",
    "questionId": "456b3715a5a395c8ff9498d4cfe1a394",
    "questionType": "multiple-choice"
  },
  {
    "answer": "False",
    "category": "video-games",
    "newCategory": "Video Games",
    "question": "In Runescape, you must have level 40 defence to wear adamant armor.",
    "questionId": "f498db8652e5f1359c56956a3c0a90a8",
    "questionType": "true-false"
  },
  {
    "answer": "bananas",
    "category": "video-games",
    "choices": [
      "peaches",
      "oranges",
      "apples",
      "bananas"
    ],
    "newCategory": "Video Games",
    "question": "What fruit grows on Karmaja in the Runescape video game?",
    "questionId": "abe73fd5f2ccefad22d9e96bd1c3edc9",
    "questionType": "multiple-choice"
  },
  {
    "answer": "a reindeer hat",
    "category": "video-games",
    "choices": [
      "a pair of Santas magical boots",
      "a reindeer hat",
      "a Santa hat",
      "a polar bear suit"
    ],
    "newCategory": "Video Games",
    "question": "What item do you obtain from the 2006 Runescape Christmas Special?",
    "questionId": "804fd0bc671a056efe837137412df967",
    "questionType": "multiple-choice"
  },
  {
    "answer": "true",
    "category": "video-games",
    "newCategory": "Video Games",
    "question": "Can you kill demons in a non-members world of Runescape?:removeme",
    "questionId": "3ccdad682f2fdd832cfbe70c156b6aef",
    "questionType": "true-false"
  },
  {
    "answer": "false",
    "category": "video-games",
    "newCategory": "Video Games",
    "question": "Can you wear goblin mail in Runescape?:removeme",
    "questionId": "712762dcf9939801e73232824e11d27b",
    "questionType": "true-false"
  },
  {
    "answer": "True",
    "category": "video-games",
    "newCategory": "Video Games",
    "question": "In Runescape, you must have a level of 99 on any skill to get a Skill Cape.",
    "questionId": "04ae82e7cc191323713a045c39072317",
    "questionType": "true-false"
  },
  {
    "answer": "True",
    "category": "video-games",
    "newCategory": "Video Games",
    "question": "Sasuke, one of the main characters in the anime series Naruto, is branded with a cursed seal.",
    "questionId": "0d553ba0a6da30774302cb8a5976965b",
    "questionType": "true-false"
  },
  {
    "answer": "Naruto",
    "category": "video-games",
    "choices": [
      "Kakashi",
      "Lee",
      "Tenten",
      "Naruto"
    ],
    "newCategory": "Video Games",
    "question": "Which of these anime characters can use the technique, known as Rasengan?",
    "questionId": "69868e0944e75370793597566ac531ae",
    "questionType": "multiple-choice"
  },
  {
    "answer": "Im an avenger.",
    "category": "video-games",
    "choices": [
      "Ill destroy your whole clan.",
      "Im an avenger.",
      "With this power Ill brake every bone in your body.",
      "You are dead."
    ],
    "newCategory": "Video Games",
    "question": "What did anime character Sasuke say when he received the cursed seal?",
    "questionId": "1fced2da78ecd7f312018fd138236581",
    "questionType": "multiple-choice"
  },
  {
    "answer": "False",
    "category": "video-games",
    "newCategory": "Video Games",
    "question": "Fictional character Naruto killed Gaara.",
    "questionId": "27d2f13caa0c132ec7549ed4c6261e1d",
    "questionType": "true-false"
  },
  {
    "answer": "ramen",
    "category": "video-games",
    "choices": [
      "tomatoes",
      "pizza",
      "brocoli",
      "ramen"
    ],
    "newCategory": "Video Games",
    "question": "What is Narutos favorite food?",
    "questionId": "dc2ec79e654c824308708f2fd14833bc",
    "questionType": "multiple-choice"
  },
  {
    "answer": "Kakashi",
    "category": "video-games",
    "choices": [
      "Naruto",
      "Itachi",
      "Kakashi",
      "Orochimaru"
    ],
    "newCategory": "Video Games",
    "question": "Who taught Sasuke the Chidori technique in the Naruto series?",
    "questionId": "0468ebffd47f4851f5f90294076a60b4",
    "questionType": "multiple-choice"
  },
  {
    "answer": "Chidori",
    "category": "video-games",
    "choices": [
      "Primary lotus",
      "Rasengan",
      "Leaf whirlwind",
      "Chidori"
    ],
    "newCategory": "Video Games",
    "question": "What technique in the Naruto series was created by Kakashi?",
    "questionId": "9cad006ad322582d08c57a4cfc68b561",
    "questionType": "multiple-choice"
  },
  {
    "answer": "hokage",
    "category": "video-games",
    "choices": [
      "hokage",
      "real estate salesman",
      "singer",
      "a pizza man"
    ],
    "newCategory": "Video Games",
    "question": "What does Naruto dream of being in the self-titled anime series?",
    "questionId": "18dafe9cfa0dbdf2afaefdf11fd8aacd",
    "questionType": "multiple-choice"
  },
  {
    "answer": "Sakura",
    "category": "video-games",
    "choices": [
      "Ino",
      "None of these",
      "Sakura",
      "Hinata"
    ],
    "newCategory": "Video Games",
    "question": "What Naruto character was initially infatuated with Sasuke?",
    "questionId": "1387aac4cac88a200b15b21eda168a38",
    "questionType": "multiple-choice"
  },
  {
    "answer": "40",
    "category": "video-games",
    "choices": [
      "37",
      "43",
      "34",
      "40"
    ],
    "newCategory": "Video Games",
    "question": "You get the P90 weapon at what level in Call of Duty 4?",
    "questionId": "69dcea4080e3184aa90b7b118e316d4e",
    "questionType": "multiple-choice"
  },
  {
    "answer": "29",
    "category": "video-games",
    "choices": [
      "30",
      "29",
      "17",
      "22"
    ],
    "newCategory": "Video Games",
    "question": "How many different weapons are there in Call of Duty 4?",
    "questionId": "e363ae16766f7278e6cbcb87f2ea9387",
    "questionType": "multiple-choice"
  },
  {
    "answer": "False",
    "category": "video-games",
    "newCategory": "Video Games",
    "question": "You can go into 15 Prestiges on XBox Livve.",
    "questionId": "2e945a07b5e6213d916c98add7a62c76",
    "questionType": "true-false"
  },
  {
    "answer": "False",
    "category": "video-games",
    "newCategory": "Video Games",
    "question": "In Call of Duty 4 you can run around with your knife and kill as many people as you want with it.",
    "questionId": "a9d0ec5ce9cb1c3abf4c265dfdb521a2",
    "questionType": "true-false"
  },
  {
    "answer": "True",
    "category": "video-games",
    "newCategory": "Video Games",
    "question": "The Barret .50 Caliber is the most powerful sniper rifle in the game Call of Duty 4.",
    "questionId": "19f68abee69162647ce739a78605c3cf",
    "questionType": "true-false"
  },
  {
    "answer": "6",
    "category": "video-games",
    "choices": [
      "5",
      "6",
      "3",
      "1"
    ],
    "newCategory": "Video Games",
    "question": "How many skins for the weapons are there in Call of Duty 4?",
    "questionId": "59b248e1df80dd85922bc0d4424692b1",
    "questionType": "multiple-choice"
  },
  {
    "answer": "True",
    "category": "video-games",
    "newCategory": "Video Games",
    "question": "If you shoot a person in the head in the game Call of Duty 4, they can survive.",
    "questionId": "74136001cbffea479a4bdb793c0ce222",
    "questionType": "true-false"
  },
  {
    "answer": "Cloud Cuckooland",
    "category": "video-games",
    "choices": [
      "Gobis Valley",
      "Mumbos Mountain",
      "Cloud Cuckooland",
      "Freezeezy Peak"
    ],
    "newCategory": "Video Games",
    "question": "Which of these is not a stage in the first game of Banjo and Kazooie for Nintendo 64?",
    "questionId": "cc225fabdbc5c7f69ed6cac03cbd77d0",
    "questionType": "multiple-choice"
  },
  {
    "answer": "6",
    "category": "video-games",
    "choices": [
      "7",
      "6",
      "5",
      "8"
    ],
    "newCategory": "Video Games",
    "question": "In the adventure video game Banjo-Kazooie, how many turtles are in Tiptups choir?",
    "questionId": "7abc6cd80eab33f882dc3680d87d753e",
    "questionType": "multiple-choice"
  },
  {
    "answer": "5",
    "category": "video-games",
    "choices": [
      "3",
      "5",
      "9",
      "7"
    ],
    "newCategory": "Video Games",
    "question": "In Gobis Valley from the Banjo-Kazooie adventure video game, how many notes are there in front of the door that you ride the magic carpet to?",
    "questionId": "aaff7a3a0de03c5fe9cb443593a6cf5e",
    "questionType": "multiple-choice"
  },
  {
    "answer": "None of these",
    "category": "video-games",
    "choices": [
      "13 oclock",
      "None of these",
      "The hands are moving",
      "Midnight"
    ],
    "newCategory": "Video Games",
    "question": "In Mad Monster Mansion from the Banjo-Kazooie video game, what is the time shown on the clock above the church?",
    "questionId": "de3f6d80f589366b38a1b41aa84eb23d",
    "questionType": "multiple-choice"
  },
  {
    "answer": "False",
    "category": "video-games",
    "newCategory": "Video Games",
    "question": "In the quiz stage of the adventure video game Banjo-Kazooie, failing a question on a Grunty Space will cause the characters to fall into the lava pit.",
    "questionId": "cccae55ea9dce98c2fce5bd60d23f4fa",
    "questionType": "true-false"
  },
  {
    "answer": "True",
    "category": "video-games",
    "newCategory": "Video Games",
    "question": "Gobi is the name of the camel in Gobis Valley in the Banjo and Kazooie video game.",
    "questionId": "68a3ef87083fbdd649b315294178a15b",
    "questionType": "true-false"
  },
  {
    "answer": "false",
    "category": "video-games",
    "newCategory": "Video Games",
    "question": "Do you need to talk to somebody in Kurast Docks in order to activate the first quest in Act III of the computer game Diablo II?:removeme",
    "questionId": "723a2edcb7e979142f2f7e7c26ddaaef",
    "questionType": "true-false"
  },
  {
    "answer": "Old",
    "category": "video-games",
    "choices": [
      "New",
      "Lost",
      "Old",
      "Found"
    ],
    "newCategory": "Video Games",
    "question": "Complete the title of the 2nd quest in Act III of the computer game Diablo II: Blade of the _____ Religion.",
    "questionId": "2cc2646322ebd93a5c57fa8dbca3fd90",
    "questionType": "multiple-choice"
  },
  {
    "answer": "4",
    "category": "video-games",
    "choices": [
      "4",
      "1",
      "5",
      "2"
    ],
    "newCategory": "Video Games",
    "question": "In the third quest of Act III in Diablo II, how many items must be retrieved?",
    "questionId": "f3985ed4d3bdf9e0791a9a9c27e96657",
    "questionType": "multiple-choice"
  },
  {
    "answer": "Alkor",
    "category": "video-games",
    "choices": [
      "Asheara",
      "Ormus",
      "Deckard Cain",
      "Alkor"
    ],
    "newCategory": "Video Games",
    "question": "Who must you talk to, in order to activate the Lam Esens Tome quest in the computer game Diablo II?",
    "questionId": "0da30e4a2f1d876df06f3d4082d0a995",
    "questionType": "multiple-choice"
  },
  {
    "answer": "Travincal",
    "category": "video-games",
    "choices": [
      "Kurast Bazaar",
      "Durance of Hate",
      "Upper Kurast",
      "Travincal"
    ],
    "newCategory": "Video Games",
    "question": "The 5th quest in Act III of Diablo II is activated by Ormus, only if you are able to find this place.",
    "questionId": "a7d48084d3d094d24327060b4f092448",
    "questionType": "multiple-choice"
  },
  {
    "answer": "Mephisto",
    "category": "video-games",
    "choices": [
      "Andariel",
      "Diablo",
      "Baal",
      "Mephisto"
    ],
    "newCategory": "Video Games",
    "question": "What boss must be fought in the last quest in Act III of the computer game Diablo II?",
    "questionId": "a3a57ca273ba70304f9c41b290358a4c",
    "questionType": "multiple-choice"
  },
  {
    "answer": "Two skill points",
    "category": "video-games",
    "choices": [
      "Free repair",
      "Two skill points",
      "Free potions",
      "Two points in your attributes"
    ],
    "newCategory": "Video Games",
    "question": "What reward will you receive upon completing the first quest in Act IV of the game Diablo II?",
    "questionId": "4b23deae85f8020e38fe20346decf76c",
    "questionType": "multiple-choice"
  },
  {
    "answer": "Deckard Cain",
    "category": "video-games",
    "choices": [
      "Tyrael",
      "Halbu",
      "Jamella",
      "Deckard Cain"
    ],
    "newCategory": "Video Games",
    "question": "You must talk to this person in order to activate your 2nd quest in Act IV of the computer game Diablo II.",
    "questionId": "41df7c85a784b96cdaa2c3478504465d",
    "questionType": "multiple-choice"
  },
  {
    "answer": "Terrors End",
    "category": "video-games",
    "choices": [
      "Diablo: Lord of Terror",
      "Revenge",
      "Terrors End",
      "Restoration of Goodness"
    ],
    "newCategory": "Video Games",
    "question": "What is the title of the last quest in Act IV of the computer game Diablo II?",
    "questionId": "bfe367af3229d5f3c63acb8607d75c7a",
    "questionType": "multiple-choice"
  },
  {
    "answer": "Stricken",
    "category": "video-games",
    "choices": [
      "Stricken",
      "Raining Blood",
      "One",
      "The Number of the Beast"
    ],
    "newCategory": "Video Games",
    "question": "Which one of these songs is NOT in the final section of Guitar Hero III, Lous Inferno?",
    "questionId": "b0eab9f071b11e8a0b75a2a7389b5c0d",
    "questionType": "multiple-choice"
  },
  {
    "answer": "False",
    "category": "video-games",
    "newCategory": "Video Games",
    "question": "You must beat Guitar Hero III on Expert to be able to play Through the Fire and Flames.",
    "questionId": "b5101fa214c7b56542ab8debf2f95a34",
    "questionType": "true-false"
  },
  {
    "answer": "Bulls on Parade",
    "category": "video-games",
    "choices": [
      "Bulls on Parade",
      "She Bangs the Drums",
      "Schools out",
      "Slow Ride"
    ],
    "newCategory": "Video Games",
    "question": "What song is unlocked after beating Tom Morello in a guitar battle in the video game Guitar Hero III?",
    "questionId": "9517b5e7afd5edd86e0d1be4e80e434d",
    "questionType": "multiple-choice"
  },
  {
    "answer": "playing Expert in Precision Mode",
    "category": "video-games",
    "choices": [
      "playing Expert in Precision Mode",
      "playing people online",
      "trying to get 5 stars on every song",
      "battling against a friend"
    ],
    "newCategory": "Video Games",
    "question": "After you beat Guitar Hero III on Expert, you are informed that you can really test your skill by doing this.",
    "questionId": "9a9a22148bf8c93f5eefac072f533bb0",
    "questionType": "multiple-choice"
  },
  {
    "answer": "April 25, 2007",
    "category": "video-games",
    "choices": [
      "April 25, 2007",
      "March 10, 2007",
      "June 30, 2007",
      "June 22, 2007"
    ],
    "newCategory": "Video Games",
    "question": "On what date was the release of Call of Duty 4: Modern Warfare announced?",
    "questionId": "1a3e6ed4b006a13fcec86b1167a8e123",
    "questionType": "multiple-choice"
  },
  {
    "answer": "10",
    "category": "video-games",
    "choices": [
      "11",
      "9",
      "10",
      "12"
    ],
    "newCategory": "Video Games",
    "question": "How many times can a player trade in their levels at prestige mode in the first-person shooter Call of Duty 4?",
    "questionId": "3e6b6600498aaf830f540fe9995d835e",
    "questionType": "multiple-choice"
  },
  {
    "answer": "False",
    "category": "video-games",
    "newCategory": "Video Games",
    "question": "In the Xbox 360 version of Call of Duty 4, the achievement war pig is given for killing Khaled Al-Asad.",
    "questionId": "1842503f4c337de1ab6198daabe7dbfd",
    "questionType": "true-false"
  },
  {
    "answer": "False",
    "category": "video-games",
    "newCategory": "Video Games",
    "question": "The AC-140 gunship has 3 different weapons and uses thermal vision in Call of Duty 4.",
    "questionId": "0ca7f7ee0f93bce2d8b36fd90b9942cb",
    "questionType": "true-false"
  },
  {
    "answer": "True",
    "category": "video-games",
    "newCategory": "Video Games",
    "question": "Billy Murray lends his voice to Captain Price from Call of Duty 4: Modern Warfare.",
    "questionId": "4e0d52542df3c9fcb2b2864425c6038d",
    "questionType": "true-false"
  },
  {
    "answer": "Akara",
    "category": "video-games",
    "choices": [
      "Kashya",
      "Akara",
      "Warriv",
      "Charsi"
    ],
    "newCategory": "Video Games",
    "question": "Who do you have to talk in order to receive your first quest after creating a character in the game Diablo II?",
    "questionId": "b80d902a7d254e9653735fe3e24c9188",
    "questionType": "multiple-choice"
  },
  {
    "answer": "Sisters Burial Grounds",
    "category": "video-games",
    "choices": [
      "The Forgotten Tower",
      "Sisters Burial Grounds",
      "Den of Evil",
      "The Search for Cain"
    ],
    "newCategory": "Video Games",
    "question": "What is the 2nd quest in the first chapter of the computer game Diablo II?",
    "questionId": "552fd3f83c20a34c62c2a30e790b233c",
    "questionType": "multiple-choice"
  },
  {
    "answer": "Deckard Cain",
    "category": "video-games",
    "choices": [
      "Deckard Cain",
      "Raven",
      "Gheed",
      "Flavie"
    ],
    "newCategory": "Video Games",
    "question": "Who must be rescued in the third quest of the game Diablo II?",
    "questionId": "17a19ee6dcf70dba4c8a1266c74a0713",
    "questionType": "multiple-choice"
  },
  {
    "answer": "Horadric Malus",
    "category": "video-games",
    "choices": [
      "Horadric Headpiece",
      "Horadric Staff",
      "Horadric Cube",
      "Horadric Malus"
    ],
    "newCategory": "Video Games",
    "question": "What must be retrieved in the fifth quest of the first act of the computer game Diablo II?",
    "questionId": "7a711a701b02d015f43cfabfd0178c81",
    "questionType": "multiple-choice"
  },
  {
    "answer": "Sisters to the Slaughter",
    "category": "video-games",
    "choices": [
      "Sisters to the Slaughter",
      "Fathers to the Slaughter",
      "Brothers to the Slaughter",
      "Mothers to the Slaughter"
    ],
    "newCategory": "Video Games",
    "question": "What is the last quest in Chapter I of the computer game Diablo II?",
    "questionId": "f1d50cd7aa0cc476e41a71e12c91462e",
    "questionType": "multiple-choice"
  },
  {
    "answer": "Radament",
    "category": "video-games",
    "choices": [
      "Radament",
      "Duriel",
      "Tal Rasha",
      "Summoner"
    ],
    "newCategory": "Video Games",
    "question": "Who must be defeated in the first quest of the second chapter of the computer game Diablo II?",
    "questionId": "ad98217406457afae40f439f0419758e",
    "questionType": "multiple-choice"
  },
  {
    "answer": "Horadric Staff",
    "category": "video-games",
    "choices": [
      "Horadric Malus",
      "Horadric Shaft",
      "Horadric Headpiece",
      "Horadric Staff"
    ],
    "newCategory": "Video Games",
    "question": "Which item must be formed, to succeed in the second quest of Chapter II of the computer game Diablo II?",
    "questionId": "bfa5aad9a7b284702570a8a99bc8b914",
    "questionType": "multiple-choice"
  },
  {
    "answer": "to get the Journal",
    "category": "video-games",
    "choices": [
      "to kill the Summoner",
      "to kill all monsters in the Arcane Sanctuary",
      "to open the portal to the Kurast Docks",
      "to get the Journal"
    ],
    "newCategory": "Video Games",
    "question": "What is your objective of the 4th quest of Chapter II in the game Diablo II?",
    "questionId": "bed4c9a2ae711724c2c7ca389e3f7941",
    "questionType": "multiple-choice"
  },
  {
    "answer": "Summoner",
    "category": "video-games",
    "choices": [
      "Hell Clan",
      "Summoner",
      "Ghoul Lord",
      "Specter"
    ],
    "newCategory": "Video Games",
    "question": "Who must be killed in the 5th quest in Chapter II of Diablo II?",
    "questionId": "1e735bd5c524ea3b9b9cb3c06e248177",
    "questionType": "multiple-choice"
  },
  {
    "answer": "Tyrael",
    "category": "video-games",
    "choices": [
      "Tyrael",
      "Ormus",
      "Jamella",
      "Halbu"
    ],
    "newCategory": "Video Games",
    "question": "Who must be saved in the last quest in Chapter II (The Seven Tombs) of the computer game Diablo II?",
    "questionId": "ef79844c0d3679aa8b4806413db701cc",
    "questionType": "multiple-choice"
  },
  {
    "answer": "Green Horns",
    "category": "video-games",
    "choices": [
      "Alienators",
      "Alien Hunters",
      "Green Toads",
      "Green Horns"
    ],
    "newCategory": "Video Games",
    "question": "Name Master Chiefs partners in the video game Halo 1.",
    "questionId": "3a32eb63235a1449bbd50dd4e01248db",
    "questionType": "multiple-choice"
  },
  {
    "answer": "Jackals",
    "category": "video-games",
    "choices": [
      "Hunters",
      "Jackals",
      "Grunts",
      "Elites"
    ],
    "newCategory": "Video Games",
    "question": "Name the aliens with the shields in the game Halo 1.",
    "questionId": "24b3e81ce5bc06f58d3568b42793f465",
    "questionType": "multiple-choice"
  },
  {
    "answer": "False",
    "category": "video-games",
    "newCategory": "Video Games",
    "question": "You start out with a weapon in the first level of Halo 1.",
    "questionId": "0f16a2db9cdba917f1625d3b5224cb9e",
    "questionType": "true-false"
  },
  {
    "answer": "Hunters",
    "category": "video-games",
    "choices": [
      "Hunters",
      "Grunts",
      "Elites",
      "Jackals"
    ],
    "newCategory": "Video Games",
    "question": "What is the name of the Halo 1 aliens with plasma cannons?",
    "questionId": "e7d0caee21cccf6a092d35a3033c7abe",
    "questionType": "multiple-choice"
  },
  {
    "answer": "Grunts",
    "category": "video-games",
    "choices": [
      "Jackals",
      "Hunters",
      "Elites",
      "Grunts"
    ],
    "newCategory": "Video Games",
    "question": "What are the smallest aliens you face in the video game Halo 1?",
    "questionId": "8fda9654c1fdaa1e1861aa92e42d6c91",
    "questionType": "multiple-choice"
  },
  {
    "answer": "Elites",
    "category": "video-games",
    "choices": [
      "Jackals",
      "Hunters",
      "Elites",
      "Grunts"
    ],
    "newCategory": "Video Games",
    "question": "These aliens are the protectors of halo in the video game Halo 1.",
    "questionId": "480e6323b32bc8a4129364c68ba38e1f",
    "questionType": "multiple-choice"
  },
  {
    "answer": "True",
    "category": "video-games",
    "newCategory": "Video Games",
    "question": "Master Chief is the protagonist of the Halo video game.",
    "questionId": "20896756d5f25466fc3746331953a216",
    "questionType": "true-false"
  },
  {
    "answer": "Space Pirates",
    "category": "video-games",
    "choices": [
      "Space Pirates",
      "The Federation",
      "The Chozo",
      "X Parasites"
    ],
    "newCategory": "Video Games",
    "question": "What is the name of Samus enemies common to nearly every Metroid video game",
    "questionId": "c05a94f676a122c2c6319904e8e09ca3",
    "questionType": "multiple-choice"
  },
  {
    "answer": "Varia Suit",
    "category": "video-games",
    "choices": [
      "Power Suit",
      "Gravity Suit",
      "Varia Suit",
      "Phazon Suit"
    ],
    "newCategory": "Video Games",
    "question": "What is the name of the suit Samus starts out with in almost every Metroid video game?",
    "questionId": "dd1fb3b1adb309f819f1b28b81f74138",
    "questionType": "multiple-choice"
  },
  {
    "answer": "Beam",
    "category": "video-games",
    "choices": [
      "Beam",
      "Rocket",
      "Gun",
      "Launcher"
    ],
    "newCategory": "Video Games",
    "question": "What word is always attached to the names of the shots that come from Samus arm-mounted gun in the Metroid video game?",
    "questionId": "4812ab11be4ca8f5538fc9d9fae39d2a",
    "questionType": "multiple-choice"
  },
  {
    "answer": "Human Female",
    "category": "video-games",
    "choices": [
      "Chozo Male",
      "Human Male",
      "Luminoth Female",
      "Human Female"
    ],
    "newCategory": "Video Games",
    "question": "What type of character is Samus from the Metroid video game?",
    "questionId": "85e345e057353f7b405d2b505d0e21e3",
    "questionType": "multiple-choice"
  },
  {
    "answer": "Bounty Hunter",
    "category": "video-games",
    "choices": [
      "Professional Collector",
      "Soldier",
      "Pirate",
      "Bounty Hunter"
    ],
    "newCategory": "Video Games",
    "question": "In the Metroid video game, what is Samus profession?",
    "questionId": "0f920ed963c6ca14340cff4b8671c8cc",
    "questionType": "multiple-choice"
  },
  {
    "answer": "They can suck out your life energy.",
    "category": "video-games",
    "choices": [
      "They can suck out your life energy.",
      "They can kill by physical contact.",
      "They can create lifelike illusions.",
      "They can kill by eye contact."
    ],
    "newCategory": "Video Games",
    "question": "What special abilities are unique to Metroids in the video game series Metroid?",
    "questionId": "99f9992beca6a1e55af422d89b9f9f8b",
    "questionType": "multiple-choice"
  },
  {
    "answer": "Grenade Launcher",
    "category": "video-games",
    "choices": [
      "Grenade Launcher",
      "Morph Ball",
      "Missile Launcher",
      "Grapple Beam"
    ],
    "newCategory": "Video Games",
    "question": "Which of these is not an upgrade Samus receives in the Metroid game series?",
    "questionId": "10bb37b77ff4503eaef9be900ad1198e",
    "questionType": "multiple-choice"
  },
  {
    "answer": "The Chozo",
    "category": "video-games",
    "choices": [
      "The Lords of Science",
      "The Chozo",
      "The Luminoth",
      "The X"
    ],
    "newCategory": "Video Games",
    "question": "In the Metroid video game series, what species created the suit and most of the upgrades available to Samus?",
    "questionId": "6be26961d95fa2a45d28b2b2eee94aed",
    "questionType": "multiple-choice"
  },
  {
    "answer": "Phazon Bomb",
    "category": "video-games",
    "choices": [
      "Phazon Bomb",
      "Bomb",
      "Power Bomb",
      "Boost Ball"
    ],
    "newCategory": "Video Games",
    "question": "Which of these is not an ability available to Samus while in Morph Ball Mode of the Metroid video game?",
    "questionId": "095bc448700c551604a8e46dceb75022",
    "questionType": "multiple-choice"
  },
  {
    "answer": "Weekly Shonen Jump",
    "category": "video-games",
    "choices": [
      "Weekly Shonen Run",
      "Weekly Shonen Jump",
      "Monthly Shonen Jump",
      "None of these"
    ],
    "newCategory": "Video Games",
    "question": "Naruto was first published in 1999, in this magazine.",
    "questionId": "78418f3a3808280b7b41bf078a4c425c",
    "questionType": "multiple-choice"
  },
  {
    "answer": "Konan",
    "category": "video-games",
    "choices": [
      "Jugo",
      "Madara",
      "Kanan",
      "Konan"
    ],
    "newCategory": "Video Games",
    "question": "Who is the only female Akatsuki member in the Naruto manga series?",
    "questionId": "0f1f93e6aea497552a638dcdecfb72cd",
    "questionType": "multiple-choice"
  },
  {
    "answer": "Suigetsu Hozuki",
    "category": "video-games",
    "choices": [
      "Suigetsu Hozuki",
      "Shunsuke Sakuya",
      "Sasuke Uchiha",
      "Akeno Watanabe"
    ],
    "newCategory": "Video Games",
    "question": "Who is the first ninja recruited for the fictional team Hawk?",
    "questionId": "95ada6ffcf0153cba80e51828a1b7e9e",
    "questionType": "multiple-choice"
  },
  {
    "answer": "1",
    "category": "video-games",
    "choices": [
      "1",
      "7",
      "6",
      "8"
    ],
    "newCategory": "Video Games",
    "question": "Namikaze Sateraito is the opening song for the first 22 episodes of which Naruto season?",
    "questionId": "5ace08ebc5a686c69989623e24789bde",
    "questionType": "multiple-choice"
  },
  {
    "answer": "7",
    "category": "video-games",
    "choices": [
      "5",
      "6",
      "7",
      "4"
    ],
    "newCategory": "Video Games",
    "question": "Orochimarus Curse is the title of which volume of the Naruto manga?",
    "questionId": "8b045923d9e5febc7b8687ab407a60ae",
    "questionType": "multiple-choice"
  },
  {
    "answer": "False",
    "category": "video-games",
    "newCategory": "Video Games",
    "question": "Masatoshi Kazikuga is the author of two novelizations of Naruto, published in Japan and America.",
    "questionId": "ee3869b99e5709c88d68d59f359819d8",
    "questionType": "true-false"
  },
  {
    "answer": "Dragon Scimitar",
    "category": "video-games",
    "choices": [
      "Dragon Scimitar",
      "Dragon Spear",
      "Dragon Halberd",
      "Dragon Longsword"
    ],
    "newCategory": "Video Games",
    "question": "What can you wield after the Monkey Madness Quest in RuneScape?",
    "questionId": "9b4e413316eb2bf7aad7af6808946917",
    "questionType": "multiple-choice"
  },
  {
    "answer": "False",
    "category": "video-games",
    "newCategory": "Video Games",
    "question": "The RuneScape game was created by Christopher Grower.",
    "questionId": "8667f3a8091ac8daff1609e3866d20b6",
    "questionType": "true-false"
  },
  {
    "answer": "Veracs (full)",
    "category": "video-games",
    "choices": [
      "Dragon (full)",
      "Guthans (full)",
      "Dharoks (full)",
      "Veracs (full)"
    ],
    "newCategory": "Video Games",
    "question": "Which of the following RuneScape defence armors is the best?",
    "questionId": "b2d0c880ca4715173d7746e04fe5ce72",
    "questionType": "multiple-choice"
  },
  {
    "answer": "January 4th 2001",
    "category": "video-games",
    "choices": [
      "July 4th, 2003",
      "Febuary 8th 1998",
      "January 4th 2001",
      "June 5th 2001"
    ],
    "newCategory": "Video Games",
    "question": "When was the first version of RuneScape released to the public?",
    "questionId": "53a96561c4fa3b0393be8446f162783b",
    "questionType": "multiple-choice"
  },
  {
    "answer": "True",
    "category": "video-games",
    "newCategory": "Video Games",
    "question": "RuneScape is set in the fantasy-themed realm of Gielinor.",
    "questionId": "9a6a438c0f3a789bb316f37cd0d586f8",
    "questionType": "true-false"
  },
  {
    "answer": "False",
    "category": "video-games",
    "newCategory": "Video Games",
    "question": "The creator of RuneScape was helped by his cousin, Joel, in developing the game.",
    "questionId": "73c56181f1d47477097fe76ed4bc5b51",
    "questionType": "true-false"
  },
  {
    "answer": "DeviousMUD",
    "category": "video-games",
    "choices": [
      "DeviousMUD",
      "Runeworld",
      "DeviousWOF",
      "RuneLand"
    ],
    "newCategory": "Video Games",
    "question": "What was RuneScape originally named?",
    "questionId": "50702d5af914a0187165bc72807ce6e0",
    "questionType": "multiple-choice"
  },
  {
    "answer": "Zamorak",
    "category": "video-games",
    "choices": [
      "Guthan",
      "Guthix",
      "Dharok",
      "Zamorak"
    ],
    "newCategory": "Video Games",
    "question": "What is the name of the evil god in RunesSape whose rival is Saradomin?",
    "questionId": "55abfe84b6a74157b52b351352dea228",
    "questionType": "multiple-choice"
  },
  {
    "answer": "true",
    "category": "video-games",
    "newCategory": "Video Games",
    "question": "Are there members-only servers for RuneScape Classic?:removeme",
    "questionId": "0613533f6cb6c2e24dd730dfcb62d941",
    "questionType": "true-false"
  },
  {
    "answer": "Dragon hally",
    "category": "video-games",
    "choices": [
      "Dragon hally",
      "Flaming sword of death",
      "Dragon longsword",
      "Dagon scimitar"
    ],
    "newCategory": "Video Games",
    "question": "What weapon do you wield after the Regicide Quest in RuneScape?",
    "questionId": "b75b0f120bf09f6a894f5a70306a8c1a",
    "questionType": "multiple-choice"
  },
  {
    "answer": "Red",
    "category": "video-games",
    "choices": [
      "Blue",
      "Green",
      "Red",
      "Yellow"
    ],
    "newCategory": "Video Games",
    "question": "Ash Ketchum, the main protagonist in the Pok\u00e9mon anime, is loosely based on what other character?",
    "questionId": "43273bef39d2fed2fa0da714639f2d85",
    "questionType": "multiple-choice"
  },
  {
    "answer": "none of these",
    "category": "video-games",
    "choices": [
      "none of these",
      "train it at night",
      "Trade it while holding a razor fang",
      "trade it"
    ],
    "newCategory": "Video Games",
    "question": "In what way can you evolve the Pokemon Gilgar into Gliscor in the Diamond and Pearl Pokemon series for Nintendo DS?",
    "questionId": "236b95cdfaa6ddf400551d8dc149f800",
    "questionType": "multiple-choice"
  },
  {
    "answer": "False",
    "category": "video-games",
    "newCategory": "Video Games",
    "question": "Celebi is a grass type Pokemon that you can find in the sinnow region.",
    "questionId": "8f161ad240f5afb7c01431cff098b3bc",
    "questionType": "true-false"
  },
  {
    "answer": "The Last Half of Darkness: New Ways to Die",
    "category": "video-games",
    "choices": [
      "The Last Half of Darkness 3",
      "The Last Half of Darkness: Shadows of the Servants",
      "The Last Half of Darkness VGA",
      "The Last Half of Darkness: New Ways to Die"
    ],
    "newCategory": "Video Games",
    "question": "Which of the following is not a game in The Last Half of Darkness series?",
    "questionId": "c5cb382e46e1687bf76c0b3fe3b29bd7",
    "questionType": "multiple-choice"
  },
  {
    "answer": "Last Warrior of Orion",
    "category": "video-games",
    "choices": [
      "Power Rangers Time Force",
      "Last Warrior of Orion",
      "Master of Magic",
      "Archon Ultra"
    ],
    "newCategory": "Video Games",
    "question": "Which of these is not the title of an actual PC game?",
    "questionId": "fc01837858dc8ca6cefc825794be3714",
    "questionType": "multiple-choice"
  },
  {
    "answer": "Valkyrie",
    "category": "video-games",
    "choices": [
      "Valkyrie",
      "Black Knight",
      "Witch",
      "Orc"
    ],
    "newCategory": "Video Games",
    "question": "Which of the following is part of the game Archon Ultra?",
    "questionId": "d6a224d94247a8c9053207db3761295d",
    "questionType": "multiple-choice"
  },
  {
    "answer": "False",
    "category": "video-games",
    "newCategory": "Video Games",
    "question": "In the Last Half of Darkness series, there is a Last Half of Darkness III VGA.",
    "questionId": "2d81ba43876a5d280547796b33b13144",
    "questionType": "true-false"
  },
  {
    "answer": "Blade",
    "category": "video-games",
    "choices": [
      "The Mist",
      "Alien Trilogy",
      "Blade",
      "Clive Barkers Undying"
    ],
    "newCategory": "Video Games",
    "question": "Which of these horror movie based games isnt a PC game?",
    "questionId": "954d66a72085c0333d7929231f56868b",
    "questionType": "multiple-choice"
  },
  {
    "answer": "X-COM: UFO Defense",
    "category": "video-games",
    "choices": [
      "Heroes of Might and Magic",
      "Planets Edge",
      "Might and Magic",
      "X-COM: UFO Defense"
    ],
    "newCategory": "Video Games",
    "question": "Which of these games was not developed by New World Computing?",
    "questionId": "400f2a84b48acc611b47580a27de8e7a",
    "questionType": "multiple-choice"
  },
  {
    "answer": "Raptor: Call of the Shadows",
    "category": "video-games",
    "choices": [
      "Dragon Lore: The Legend Begins",
      "Raptor: Call of the Shadows",
      "The Nine Lives of the Secret Agent Katt",
      "7th Guest"
    ],
    "newCategory": "Video Games",
    "question": "Which of the following is not an adventure game?",
    "questionId": "e464994eb58908cc29b1722be06ea6fc",
    "questionType": "multiple-choice"
  },
  {
    "answer": "All of these",
    "category": "video-games",
    "choices": [
      "All of these",
      "3D Action game",
      "Mini-game collection",
      "2D Side-scroller"
    ],
    "newCategory": "Video Games",
    "question": "What type of game is Power Rangers Time Force?",
    "questionId": "04fb4554abfb45725d6c21497e835987",
    "questionType": "multiple-choice"
  },
  {
    "answer": "William R. Fisher III",
    "category": "video-games",
    "choices": [
      "Brian Moriarty",
      "Bill Gates",
      "William R. Fisher III",
      "Roberta Williams"
    ],
    "newCategory": "Video Games",
    "question": "Who created the game Last Half of Darkness?",
    "questionId": "b9f5c3d19642e9ce8d66e7e7d4808136",
    "questionType": "multiple-choice"
  },
  {
    "answer": "Last Guardian",
    "category": "video-games",
    "choices": [
      "Albion",
      "Dungeon Master",
      "Last Guardian",
      "Bloodnet"
    ],
    "newCategory": "Video Games",
    "question": "Which of the following is not a real role-playing game?",
    "questionId": "97b5e870c169afc81317fbeaa4d9c461",
    "questionType": "multiple-choice"
  },
  {
    "answer": "Elvarg",
    "category": "video-games",
    "choices": [
      "Elvarg",
      "Delrith",
      "Hector",
      "Verac"
    ],
    "newCategory": "Video Games",
    "question": "What is the name of the evil dragon in RuneScape that players have to kill in the Dragon Slayer quest?",
    "questionId": "eeda668691c1747c55095c1dff5ed795",
    "questionType": "multiple-choice"
  },
  {
    "answer": "Builds a small house around himself",
    "category": "video-games",
    "choices": [
      "Builds a small house around himself",
      "Hammers down nails on a board",
      "Makes a workbench with a saw",
      "Builds a bridge"
    ],
    "newCategory": "Video Games",
    "question": "In the RuneScape game, on the Construction Skillcape emote, the character performing the emote does which of the following?",
    "questionId": "775fc9acc1255cc90bc4ade3441ffab1",
    "questionType": "multiple-choice"
  },
  {
    "answer": "True",
    "category": "video-games",
    "newCategory": "Video Games",
    "question": "To equip Barrows armour and weapons in RuneScape, you must have an attack and defence level 70.",
    "questionId": "6d112c5fcf1fef9d4f15444f91424b34",
    "questionType": "true-false"
  },
  {
    "answer": "false",
    "category": "video-games",
    "newCategory": "Video Games",
    "question": "Is it true that in the RuneScape game, goblins can be found only in Goblin Village and Goblin Cave?:removeme",
    "questionId": "588f0a800cc66f4281f74ccc5f51b53e",
    "questionType": "true-false"
  },
  {
    "answer": "False",
    "category": "video-games",
    "newCategory": "Video Games",
    "question": "In the RuneScape game, you need to have 80 defence to use Guthix armor.",
    "questionId": "e5933f602ff5f287090b8eaf9de15fe3",
    "questionType": "true-false"
  },
  {
    "answer": "a chocatrice cape that turns you into a wrapped egg",
    "category": "video-games",
    "choices": [
      "a chocolate sword that you can eat off of 3 times a day healing 10hp",
      "a chocatrice cape that turns you into a wrapped egg",
      "Easter bunny ears that make your speed increase",
      "a giant cookie"
    ],
    "newCategory": "Video Games",
    "question": "What was the reward in RuneScapes 2008 Easter Seasonal Event?",
    "questionId": "d22b1e1898e7978cd29e2eef9a72adee",
    "questionType": "multiple-choice"
  },
  {
    "answer": "True",
    "category": "video-games",
    "newCategory": "Video Games",
    "question": "In the mime random event in RuneScape, the object is to identify all the mime emotes and get a reward afterwards.",
    "questionId": "8c2c8e17cebee3b8462ad85c4b8b2026",
    "questionType": "true-false"
  },
  {
    "answer": "The Gypsy",
    "category": "video-games",
    "choices": [
      "a dwarf",
      "The Gypsy",
      "Sir Vyrinn",
      "The duke of Lumbridge"
    ],
    "newCategory": "Video Games",
    "question": "To start the Demon Slayer Quest in RuneScape, you must talk to which one of these?",
    "questionId": "b573d4848807947e3447aea0539825e1",
    "questionType": "multiple-choice"
  },
  {
    "answer": "Shield of Arrav",
    "category": "video-games",
    "choices": [
      "Dragon Slayer",
      "Shield of Arrav",
      "Vampire Slayer",
      "Romeo and Juliet"
    ],
    "newCategory": "Video Games",
    "question": "In what RuneScape quest do you have to use a friend from the opposite gang?",
    "questionId": "60b9cb2653876ad38511bf4318324ce0",
    "questionType": "multiple-choice"
  },
  {
    "answer": "9",
    "category": "video-games",
    "choices": [
      "15",
      "9",
      "10",
      "12"
    ],
    "newCategory": "Video Games",
    "question": "In the game Super Mario Kart, how many coins do you receive for placing 1st in a single race?",
    "questionId": "1e5aee67ed6bc4f80ad1f94b60d59f6e",
    "questionType": "multiple-choice"
  },
  {
    "answer": "true",
    "category": "video-games",
    "newCategory": "Video Games",
    "question": "Do players have lives in the racing game Super Mario Kart?:removeme",
    "questionId": "20ba6103e68676de02dce2517cd0a372",
    "questionType": "true-false"
  },
  {
    "answer": "gives the racer a short burst of speed",
    "category": "video-games",
    "choices": [
      "poisons the racer so they cant steer correctly",
      "gives the racer a short burst of speed",
      "makes the racer large to run over other racers",
      "slows the racer so they dont go as fast"
    ],
    "newCategory": "Video Games",
    "question": "In the game Super Mario Kart, what does the mushroom item do to the racer?",
    "questionId": "52dcbdec2f638311a1f506d553ef0952",
    "questionType": "multiple-choice"
  },
  {
    "answer": "Lightning cup",
    "category": "video-games",
    "choices": [
      "Star cup",
      "Mushroom cup",
      "Special cup",
      "Lightning cup"
    ],
    "newCategory": "Video Games",
    "question": "All of the following cups are in the game Super Mario Kart, except which one of these?",
    "questionId": "f8cb08e0aa241e4b1b3fc6dc54495d2d",
    "questionType": "multiple-choice"
  },
  {
    "answer": "True",
    "category": "video-games",
    "newCategory": "Video Games",
    "question": "The feather item in the game Super Mario Kart helps the racer by jumping.",
    "questionId": "9f3d92bafbb01b8ff015d61e4e181585",
    "questionType": "true-false"
  },
  {
    "answer": "Choco Island",
    "category": "video-games",
    "choices": [
      "Donut Plains 2",
      "Choco Island",
      "Koopa Beach 1",
      "Mario Circuit 1"
    ],
    "newCategory": "Video Games",
    "question": "In the Flower cup, in the game Super Mario Kart, on which track do you start?",
    "questionId": "1c1efeb54a6b3f78e310cbb24699d301",
    "questionType": "multiple-choice"
  },
  {
    "answer": "False",
    "category": "video-games",
    "newCategory": "Video Games",
    "question": "In Super Mario Kart, the green shell is a heat-seeking missile.",
    "questionId": "8774e35648a6f63131e5452b09b89bef",
    "questionType": "true-false"
  },
  {
    "answer": "True",
    "category": "video-games",
    "newCategory": "Video Games",
    "question": "In the game Super Mario Kart, for the Super Nintendo, it is possible to fall off the track.",
    "questionId": "3f8ab48f1a5b1a2a08b2092d36e98db1",
    "questionType": "true-false"
  },
  {
    "answer": "blue shell",
    "category": "video-games",
    "choices": [
      "coins",
      "banana peel",
      "ghost",
      "blue shell"
    ],
    "newCategory": "Video Games",
    "question": "All of the following are items used in the game Super Mario Kart, for the Super NES, except which one of the following?",
    "questionId": "362f545fe0533604fc1ae0f4558aa966",
    "questionType": "multiple-choice"
  },
  {
    "answer": "Koopa Troopa",
    "category": "video-games",
    "choices": [
      "Princess Peach",
      "Koopa Troopa",
      "Donkey Kong",
      "Yoshi"
    ],
    "newCategory": "Video Games",
    "question": "On the Nintendo 64 version of Mario Kart, Wario replaced which of the following playable characters from the Super NES version?",
    "questionId": "37032c8d080dc63418f26b8fb94fdf5d",
    "questionType": "multiple-choice"
  },
  {
    "answer": "False",
    "category": "video-games",
    "newCategory": "Video Games",
    "question": "There is a PC port in the first three Timesplitters games.",
    "questionId": "832858c4082d1bbe427e6dacfedd1c72",
    "questionType": "true-false"
  },
  {
    "answer": "5",
    "category": "video-games",
    "choices": [
      "5",
      "4",
      "2",
      "1"
    ],
    "newCategory": "Video Games",
    "question": "How many of the following Power Rangers games are for PC: Power Rangers; Power Rangers: Lightspeed Rescue; Power Rangers: Super Legends; Power Rangers Zeo Versus the Machine Empire; Power Rangers: Ninja Storm Double Pack?",
    "questionId": "ea102b31e6486925b74e571e4c4a9223",
    "questionType": "multiple-choice"
  },
  {
    "answer": "11",
    "category": "video-games",
    "choices": [
      "11",
      "9",
      "10",
      "7"
    ],
    "newCategory": "Video Games",
    "question": "Excluding collections, how many Might and Magic games were released from 1986 to 2002?",
    "questionId": "729134a99cfb2f23fbe39393253440d7",
    "questionType": "multiple-choice"
  },
  {
    "answer": "Dragon",
    "category": "video-games",
    "choices": [
      "Vampire",
      "Dark Elf",
      "Knight",
      "Dragon"
    ],
    "newCategory": "Video Games",
    "question": "In Might and Magic 8, which of these classes are unselectable for the main character?",
    "questionId": "21c9a310e5db92810995aaae26d1ca0f",
    "questionType": "multiple-choice"
  },
  {
    "answer": "True",
    "category": "video-games",
    "newCategory": "Video Games",
    "question": "Joe Satriani was given a special thanks in B.A.T. II.",
    "questionId": "a89c176f1c42cf0cc0dd3e15260e545f",
    "questionType": "true-false"
  },
  {
    "answer": "Shadowcaster",
    "category": "video-games",
    "choices": [
      "Marvel: Ultimate Alliance",
      "Quest for Glory",
      "Freedom Force",
      "Shadowcaster"
    ],
    "newCategory": "Video Games",
    "question": "In which of these games does the player take the role of Kirt?",
    "questionId": "d48c2f17e21dc3047ad81c147659a90f",
    "questionType": "multiple-choice"
  },
  {
    "answer": "Ancient Domains of Mystery",
    "category": "video-games",
    "choices": [
      "Neverwinter Nights",
      "Baldurs Gate",
      "The Elder Scrolls 4 Obvilion",
      "Ancient Domains of Mystery"
    ],
    "newCategory": "Video Games",
    "question": "Which of these games is rogue-like?",
    "questionId": "0e86b956c194faba6f47aca4ffd2d681",
    "questionType": "multiple-choice"
  },
  {
    "answer": "8",
    "category": "video-games",
    "choices": [
      "12",
      "7",
      "8",
      "6"
    ],
    "newCategory": "Video Games",
    "question": "How many races are there in Star Wars: Galactic Battlegrounds? (With expansion)",
    "questionId": "c4ee6fe266b12575937581bd6c23a8e1",
    "questionType": "multiple-choice"
  },
  {
    "answer": "Weretiger",
    "category": "video-games",
    "choices": [
      "Werewolf",
      "Werebear",
      "Weredragon",
      "Weretiger"
    ],
    "newCategory": "Video Games",
    "question": "What do you transform into in stage 4 of Altered Beast?",
    "questionId": "cbd9d20ed7b01b151e6ceedd43d06dbf",
    "questionType": "multiple-choice"
  },
  {
    "answer": "Grand Theft Auto",
    "category": "video-games",
    "choices": [
      "Grand Theft Auto",
      "Kings Quest: Mask of Eternity",
      "The Nine Lives of the Secret Agent Katt",
      "The Adventures of Maddog Williams"
    ],
    "newCategory": "Video Games",
    "question": "Which of these games isnt an action/adventure hybrid?",
    "questionId": "9190a0029af0927a813b46fc42923b39",
    "questionType": "multiple-choice"
  },
  {
    "answer": "Caleb",
    "category": "video-games",
    "choices": [
      "Ellen Ripley",
      "Hugo",
      "Blake Stone",
      "Caleb"
    ],
    "newCategory": "Video Games",
    "question": "Who is the protagonist of the PC game Blood?",
    "questionId": "c2e3c10a73690bf30a876f6f58d300e1",
    "questionType": "multiple-choice"
  },
  {
    "answer": "Hugos Castle of Death",
    "category": "video-games",
    "choices": [
      "Hugos Castle of Death",
      "Hugos House of Horror",
      "Nightmare 3D",
      "Whodunit?"
    ],
    "newCategory": "Video Games",
    "question": "Which of these isnt a game from the Hugo series?",
    "questionId": "331b17082b60a3fea6197f7474a85797",
    "questionType": "multiple-choice"
  },
  {
    "answer": "Archon",
    "category": "video-games",
    "choices": [
      "The Terminator",
      "Doom",
      "Twilight 2000",
      "Archon"
    ],
    "newCategory": "Video Games",
    "question": "Name the odd game.",
    "questionId": "3ab40e466ffe8308f8375e9f181a7991",
    "questionType": "multiple-choice"
  },
  {
    "answer": "Hammer of the Gods",
    "category": "video-games",
    "choices": [
      "Blackthrone",
      "Diablo",
      "The Lost Vikings",
      "Hammer of the Gods"
    ],
    "newCategory": "Video Games",
    "question": "Which of these games was not developed by Blizzard?",
    "questionId": "79980c48deb4bab91834cd9040cef32b",
    "questionType": "multiple-choice"
  },
  {
    "answer": "Planets Edge",
    "category": "video-games",
    "choices": [
      "Pizza Tycoon",
      "Planets Edge",
      "Blackthrone",
      "One Must Fall 2097"
    ],
    "newCategory": "Video Games",
    "question": "Which of these games was developed by New World Computing?",
    "questionId": "a59cff49e26161e7b7aef6deaf252f6b",
    "questionType": "multiple-choice"
  },
  {
    "answer": "Sega Genesis Collection",
    "category": "video-games",
    "choices": [
      "Sega Genesis Collection",
      "Sonic 3 and Knuckles",
      "Sega Smash Pack",
      "Sonic Adventure DX: Directors Cut"
    ],
    "newCategory": "Video Games",
    "question": "Which of these isnt a Sega collection for PC?",
    "questionId": "951ba4d6ded2fdc6757d16b8558f2224",
    "questionType": "multiple-choice"
  },
  {
    "answer": "Bess",
    "category": "video-games",
    "choices": [
      "Jenny",
      "Beth",
      "Bess",
      "Tess"
    ],
    "newCategory": "Video Games",
    "question": "In the Nancy Drew conputer games, Nancy Drews trusty sidekicks are cousins George Fayne and this slightly plump blonde.",
    "questionId": "4f0ffe70fc5ff26d0854e2060346d60f",
    "questionType": "multiple-choice"
  },
  {
    "answer": "Frank and Joe",
    "category": "video-games",
    "choices": [
      "Frank and Joe",
      "Frank and Moe",
      "Fred and Joseph",
      "None of these"
    ],
    "newCategory": "Video Games",
    "question": "These two detective brothers appear several times in the Nancy Drew computer games to help Nancy solve mysteries.",
    "questionId": "39c717d94b4f8fd2209d6a028f7459be",
    "questionType": "multiple-choice"
  },
  {
    "answer": "Secrets Can Kill",
    "category": "video-games",
    "choices": [
      "Treasure in the Royal Tower",
      "Secrets Can Kill",
      "Message in a Haunted Mansion",
      "Secret of the Old Clock"
    ],
    "newCategory": "Video Games",
    "question": "What was the very first Nancy Drew computer game?",
    "questionId": "cf9dfab82f4b2c3a2311f09240f9378a",
    "questionType": "multiple-choice"
  },
  {
    "answer": "A shark tooth",
    "category": "video-games",
    "choices": [
      "A piece of glass",
      "A bat wing",
      "She did not find anything along with the note.",
      "A shark tooth"
    ],
    "newCategory": "Video Games",
    "question": "What did Nancy Drew find along with a message in the computer game Message in a Haunted Mansion?",
    "questionId": "d2e5786746b97482418aabab0bbafb64",
    "questionType": "multiple-choice"
  },
  {
    "answer": "Ghost of Blackmoor Manor",
    "category": "video-games",
    "choices": [
      "Creature of Kapu Cave",
      "Secrets Can Kill",
      "She never had a nightmare.",
      "Ghost of Blackmoor Manor"
    ],
    "newCategory": "Video Games",
    "question": "In which of these computer games did Nancy Drew wake up in the middle of the night because of a nightmare?",
    "questionId": "5267a12af6017079187a17dc7cc0f618",
    "questionType": "multiple-choice"
  },
  {
    "answer": "Molly McOwens",
    "category": "video-games",
    "choices": [
      "Rick Arlen",
      "None of these",
      "Molly McOwens",
      "Sally McDonald"
    ],
    "newCategory": "Video Games",
    "question": "Which of these characters appears in the Nancy Drew computer game Lights, Camera, Curses!?",
    "questionId": "fa17dc9f3abba4c0db53782c1b59e7bc",
    "questionType": "multiple-choice"
  },
  {
    "answer": "Mr. Mingles, the cat",
    "category": "video-games",
    "choices": [
      "Mr. Mingles, the cat",
      "A butterfly with you and your roommates names in it",
      "it was blank",
      "The Waverly Academy crow"
    ],
    "newCategory": "Video Games",
    "question": "In the computer game Warnings at Waverly Academy, what was pictured on Nancy Drews cabin door?",
    "questionId": "aba29881bf6f933965cf51787e20709b",
    "questionType": "multiple-choice"
  },
  {
    "answer": "In a briefcase",
    "category": "video-games",
    "choices": [
      "His picture never appears in another game",
      "In a briefcase",
      "In a bottle",
      "In a bedside picture frame"
    ],
    "newCategory": "Video Games",
    "question": "Rick Arlen is known as an arrogant television star from Stay Tuned for Danger, but his picture appears in what place in another Nancy Drew game?",
    "questionId": "ee80b21abcd0848b39dcfd854c00d70f",
    "questionType": "multiple-choice"
  },
  {
    "answer": "True",
    "category": "video-games",
    "newCategory": "Video Games",
    "question": "The wolf in the computer game White Wolf of Icicle Creek was named Isis.",
    "questionId": "6e85af360600d99ecaf0a8650f5d4823",
    "questionType": "true-false"
  },
  {
    "answer": "True",
    "category": "video-games",
    "newCategory": "Video Games",
    "question": "In the computer game The Final Scene, a flashing ring gave Nancy Drew the opportunity to save a friend.",
    "questionId": "e17d5dff0062e158e7a916dae23a9156",
    "questionType": "true-false"
  },
  {
    "answer": "Smith",
    "category": "video-games",
    "choices": [
      "Smith",
      "Wilkinson",
      "Madison",
      "His last name was never revealed"
    ],
    "newCategory": "Video Games",
    "question": "In the Nancy Drew computer game Ghost Dogs of Moon Lake, what is the rangers last name?",
    "questionId": "ec975eb40337898ff9b67f7bfe494482",
    "questionType": "multiple-choice"
  },
  {
    "answer": "On a ship",
    "category": "video-games",
    "choices": [
      "On a ship",
      "On an island",
      "On a dock",
      "In a volcano"
    ],
    "newCategory": "Video Games",
    "question": "When you first start Wonderland Online, where do you find yourself?",
    "questionId": "61cd3d491760c75771c391f2d81be2f6",
    "questionType": "multiple-choice"
  },
  {
    "answer": "Starter Beach",
    "category": "video-games",
    "choices": [
      "Beginners Island",
      "Tutorial Ridge",
      "Starter Beach",
      "Newbie Point"
    ],
    "newCategory": "Video Games",
    "question": "When your raft gets washed up, what is the place it lands (for the first time) in the game Wonderland Online?",
    "questionId": "f54b730f59882b41745334ccfe21079f",
    "questionType": "multiple-choice"
  },
  {
    "answer": "Pear",
    "category": "video-games",
    "choices": [
      "Pineapple",
      "Pear",
      "Kiwi",
      "Grape"
    ],
    "newCategory": "Video Games",
    "question": "Which one of these is not a jelly monster you can find on North Island in the game Wonderland Online?",
    "questionId": "26bbf8907f77a7bed9a9551b735ba887",
    "questionType": "multiple-choice"
  },
  {
    "answer": "Killing monsters",
    "category": "video-games",
    "choices": [
      "Killing monsters",
      "Fishing",
      "Setting up shops",
      "Compounding items"
    ],
    "newCategory": "Video Games",
    "question": "In Wonderland Online, which of these makes your level go up?",
    "questionId": "db4d385cde288bee3debe87eb5e1046a",
    "questionType": "multiple-choice"
  },
  {
    "answer": "True",
    "category": "video-games",
    "newCategory": "Video Games",
    "question": "You can ride beasts that you capture in the game Wonderland Online.",
    "questionId": "a8096e46a64445d8202f201e09e1ae3b",
    "questionType": "true-false"
  },
  {
    "answer": "True",
    "category": "video-games",
    "newCategory": "Video Games",
    "question": "In Wonderland Online it is possible to have a dinosaur as a pet.",
    "questionId": "e0d43448c2688b38fca28ee7caad6726",
    "questionType": "true-false"
  },
  {
    "answer": "Reaction",
    "category": "video-games",
    "choices": [
      "Operation",
      "Situation",
      "Conversation",
      "Reaction"
    ],
    "newCategory": "Video Games",
    "question": "What game starts when you talk to some fierce rabbits at Kelan Village in Wonderland Online?",
    "questionId": "c5f7591dfebf9423e87d59ea32d7d714",
    "questionType": "multiple-choice"
  },
  {
    "answer": "A shell",
    "category": "video-games",
    "choices": [
      "Her true love",
      "Her will",
      "A message in a bottle",
      "A shell"
    ],
    "newCategory": "Video Games",
    "question": "What does a mermaid at North Island ask you to fetch for her as a quest in the game Wonderland Online?",
    "questionId": "6d23325f0bce488b6dad524d4f5a2f14",
    "questionType": "multiple-choice"
  },
  {
    "answer": "3",
    "category": "video-games",
    "choices": [
      "none",
      "3",
      "2",
      "4"
    ],
    "newCategory": "Video Games",
    "question": "How many characters in Super Smash Bros Brawl have the Final Smash Attack of Landmaster?",
    "questionId": "20ba450cc23e1419f2f0d95ca79f238e",
    "questionType": "multiple-choice"
  },
  {
    "answer": "20",
    "category": "video-games",
    "choices": [
      "19",
      "15",
      "21",
      "20"
    ],
    "newCategory": "Video Games",
    "question": "How many characters are there at the beginning of Super Smash Bros Brawl?",
    "questionId": "3915999c8b19f0140489ef8f77d460b1",
    "questionType": "multiple-choice"
  },
  {
    "answer": "5",
    "category": "video-games",
    "choices": [
      "6",
      "5",
      "4",
      "3"
    ],
    "newCategory": "Video Games",
    "question": "How many Super Smash Bros Brawl characters have 2+ characters in their team?",
    "questionId": "912663d662c326d359e0c5b27e98858b",
    "questionType": "multiple-choice"
  },
  {
    "answer": "8",
    "category": "video-games",
    "choices": [
      "10",
      "9",
      "8",
      "5"
    ],
    "newCategory": "Video Games",
    "question": "How many bosses are there in Subspace Emissary in Super Smash Bros Brawl?",
    "questionId": "897f9de59c45ea5a4ab66724bd548390",
    "questionType": "multiple-choice"
  },
  {
    "answer": "Ridley, Kraid, Mother Brain",
    "category": "video-games",
    "choices": [
      "Alpha Metroid, Gamma Metroid, Zeta Metroid, Omega Metroid, Queen Metroid",
      "Ridley, Mother Brain, Queen Metroid",
      "Ridley, Kraid, Mother Brain",
      "Ridley, Kraid, Queen Metroid"
    ],
    "newCategory": "Video Games",
    "question": "What are the bosses in the first Metroid game?",
    "questionId": "9ee3290abb66136706260b6e3a27654e",
    "questionType": "multiple-choice"
  },
  {
    "answer": "Omega Metroid",
    "category": "video-games",
    "choices": [
      "Omega Metroid",
      "Queen Metroid",
      "Mother Brain",
      "Aurora Unit 313"
    ],
    "newCategory": "Video Games",
    "question": "Chronologically what is the last boss Samus has faced in the Metroid series?",
    "questionId": "71e2efe6104d838a31f81a1984782df1",
    "questionType": "multiple-choice"
  },
  {
    "answer": "Generator Shaft",
    "category": "video-games",
    "choices": [
      "Elevator Shaft",
      "Generator Shaft",
      "Ventilation System",
      "Garbage Disposal"
    ],
    "newCategory": "Video Games",
    "question": "In Metroid Prime 3: Corruption Samus fights Meta Ridley while falling down which of the following?",
    "questionId": "e617d99a0c9447029feaaf0c9803fb37",
    "questionType": "multiple-choice"
  },
  {
    "answer": "His eye is the only thing that connects him to the material world.",
    "category": "video-games",
    "choices": [
      "He will run away if blinded.",
      "His eye is the only thing that connects him to the material world.",
      "His eye is his only weapon.",
      "It is unknown."
    ],
    "newCategory": "Video Games",
    "question": "Why is Phatoons eye his weak point in the Metroid series?",
    "questionId": "a94d8ad98d4cdff942d7e83707ce523d",
    "questionType": "multiple-choice"
  },
  {
    "answer": "Omega Pirate",
    "category": "video-games",
    "choices": [
      "Berserker Lord",
      "Berserker Knight",
      "Omega Pirate",
      "Elite Pirate"
    ],
    "newCategory": "Video Games",
    "question": "The Pinnacle of Project Helix is what kind of Phazon Infused Space Pirate?",
    "questionId": "84013e35403852fa96a1db1a085209be",
    "questionType": "multiple-choice"
  },
  {
    "answer": "False",
    "category": "video-games",
    "newCategory": "Video Games",
    "question": "In the Metroid series, the Vorashs weak point is its eyes.",
    "questionId": "c7c68f370f4bac7eec794dc4bdd7aeea",
    "questionType": "true-false"
  },
  {
    "answer": "False",
    "category": "video-games",
    "newCategory": "Video Games",
    "question": "The final boss of Metroid Other M on hard mode is Phantoon.",
    "questionId": "c02f8fe2d79c1d80be1952da71ce6d61",
    "questionType": "true-false"
  },
  {
    "answer": "Multi-laser system",
    "category": "video-games",
    "choices": [
      "Gravity Manipultain Device",
      "Phazon Cannons",
      "The ability to create hallucinations",
      "Multi-laser system"
    ],
    "newCategory": "Video Games",
    "question": "What is Nightmares main weapon in the Metroid series?",
    "questionId": "923c7b124d2c89d7f76e0f8c4cd1d9a1",
    "questionType": "multiple-choice"
  },
  {
    "answer": "True",
    "category": "video-games",
    "newCategory": "Video Games",
    "question": "The Berserker Lord is fought twice in the Metorid series.",
    "questionId": "4ee090927419e182b9ce56d923f6db14",
    "questionType": "true-false"
  },
  {
    "answer": "Lingshan Islands",
    "category": "video-games",
    "choices": [
      "Mars",
      "Caribbean Islands",
      "Lingshan Islands",
      "North Korea"
    ],
    "newCategory": "Video Games",
    "question": "Where does the first game of the Crysis series take place?",
    "questionId": "454c2f6b2db5f6b30414ed81d988e202",
    "questionType": "multiple-choice"
  },
  {
    "answer": "Alcatraz",
    "category": "video-games",
    "choices": [
      "Psycho",
      "Alcatraz",
      "Aztec",
      "Prophet"
    ],
    "newCategory": "Video Games",
    "question": "Of the Crysis characters below, who is not a member of Raptor Team?",
    "questionId": "c3e20da3e6e8106dbd37a0bcedef93ae",
    "questionType": "multiple-choice"
  },
  {
    "answer": "Jacob Hargreave",
    "category": "video-games",
    "choices": [
      "Jacob Hargreave",
      "Dr. Gould",
      "Tara Strickland",
      "Major Lockhart"
    ],
    "newCategory": "Video Games",
    "question": "What Crysis character founded C.E.L.L?",
    "questionId": "a87ab3914da45bbd9f3e53aa805f77ab",
    "questionType": "multiple-choice"
  },
  {
    "answer": "Paris",
    "category": "video-games",
    "choices": [
      "London",
      "Paris",
      "Cairo",
      "Hawaii"
    ],
    "newCategory": "Video Games",
    "question": "Which city is not a Ceph point of interest in the Crysis game series?",
    "questionId": "84789e33d55764d780c93d029b3a5063",
    "questionType": "multiple-choice"
  },
  {
    "answer": "True",
    "category": "video-games",
    "newCategory": "Video Games",
    "question": "In the Crysis games Ceph Organisms are nicknamed Stalkers.",
    "questionId": "b5340277e1bf54227948fd655702b7fd",
    "questionType": "true-false"
  },
  {
    "answer": "500 Rounds Per second",
    "category": "video-games",
    "choices": [
      "500 Rounds per minute",
      "720 Rounds per second",
      "None, the Typhoon fires a beam that you must focus on the target",
      "500 Rounds Per second"
    ],
    "newCategory": "Video Games",
    "question": "What is the Typhoons Rate of Fire in the Crysis games?",
    "questionId": "c16bbdad9c54dc6a528be225eafa7a41",
    "questionType": "multiple-choice"
  },
  {
    "answer": "False",
    "category": "video-games",
    "newCategory": "Video Games",
    "question": "You can not destroy a round from the Gravity Bomb Launcher in the Crysis games.",
    "questionId": "2388ad2808c84f0d92a68f7203a9c02f",
    "questionType": "true-false"
  },
  {
    "answer": "True",
    "category": "video-games",
    "newCategory": "Video Games",
    "question": "Prophet dies at the beginning of Crysis 2 .",
    "questionId": "2366419d0cacd47c7f51a9d556d32b20",
    "questionType": "true-false"
  },
  {
    "answer": "False",
    "category": "video-games",
    "newCategory": "Video Games",
    "question": "In the Crysis games, Pingers do not fire at Alcatraz when he is cloaked.",
    "questionId": "24e7ffce7361fcb577f0269a4d614ba6",
    "questionType": "true-false"
  },
  {
    "answer": "1896",
    "category": "video-games",
    "choices": [
      "1967",
      "1896",
      "2001",
      "1919"
    ],
    "newCategory": "Video Games",
    "question": "What year was Crysis character Jacob Hargreave born?",
    "questionId": "b9ab91281ff6fb3bc58644a760727259",
    "questionType": "multiple-choice"
  },
  {
    "answer": "Ragnarok",
    "category": "video-games",
    "choices": [
      "Exile",
      "Haven",
      "Vortex",
      "Ragnarok"
    ],
    "newCategory": "Video Games",
    "question": "Which map is considered as a remake of the much loved Halo 3 map Valhalla?",
    "questionId": "d5bcc6de5dfea54dad900ce6cc6844f6",
    "questionType": "multiple-choice"
  },
  {
    "answer": "False",
    "category": "video-games",
    "newCategory": "Video Games",
    "question": "The plasma rifle is the first covenant weapon to be unlocked in the multiplayer mode of Halo 4.",
    "questionId": "f7bb2ab5546b7e8e8bb446501cbd7c73",
    "questionType": "true-false"
  },
  {
    "answer": "Gravity Hammer and Energy Sword",
    "category": "video-games",
    "choices": [
      "Gravity Hammer and Energy Sword",
      "Sniper Rifle and Binary Rifle",
      "Rocket Launcher and Incinerator Canon",
      "Storm Rifle and Supressor"
    ],
    "newCategory": "Video Games",
    "question": "What are the only two weapons you can use in Grifball in Halo 4 Multiplayer?",
    "questionId": "d0639a52e969f0a8fd68329c8a795e2e",
    "questionType": "multiple-choice"
  },
  {
    "answer": "Gravemind",
    "category": "video-games",
    "choices": [
      "Hunter",
      "Gravemind",
      "Floodifier",
      "Flood Master"
    ],
    "newCategory": "Video Games",
    "question": "What is the award you get for infecting every player in Flood mode in Halo 4 Multiplayer?",
    "questionId": "2c81680ff0fa10b9dd830e422249b0ee",
    "questionType": "multiple-choice"
  },
  {
    "answer": "None",
    "category": "video-games",
    "choices": [
      "Adrift",
      "None",
      "Ragnarok",
      "Longbow"
    ],
    "newCategory": "Video Games",
    "question": "Which Halo 4 Multiplayer map has a Mantis being constructed in the center of the map?",
    "questionId": "6b6d3a3d7b85073c0428fb2529cef740",
    "questionType": "multiple-choice"
  },
  {
    "answer": "True",
    "category": "video-games",
    "newCategory": "Video Games",
    "question": "You can drop weapons of your choice in Halo 4.",
    "questionId": "fa52f9ca9d639a6000e0c0d549aae423",
    "questionType": "true-false"
  },
  {
    "answer": "UNSC Infinity",
    "category": "video-games",
    "choices": [
      "UNSC Pillar of Autumn",
      "UNSC Infinity",
      "UNSC Spirit of Fire",
      "None"
    ],
    "newCategory": "Video Games",
    "question": "On what ship does the Halo 4 Multiplayer take place?",
    "questionId": "a332f3ff90e9b1a720a6882ed714cf50",
    "questionType": "multiple-choice"
  },
  {
    "answer": "False",
    "category": "video-games",
    "newCategory": "Video Games",
    "question": "The Binary Rifle in Halo 4 can only kill someone with a headshot.",
    "questionId": "72312e728258d557dfb47a8ebb3c44c1",
    "questionType": "true-false"
  },
  {
    "answer": "Boltshot",
    "category": "video-games",
    "choices": [
      "Hardlight Pistol",
      "Plasma Pistol",
      "Light Pistol",
      "Boltshot"
    ],
    "newCategory": "Video Games",
    "question": "What is the Promethean pistol called in Halo 4?",
    "questionId": "593402e2c45fe1d69053777cc9486b9c",
    "questionType": "multiple-choice"
  },
  {
    "answer": "Promethean Vision",
    "category": "video-games",
    "choices": [
      "Advanced Vision googles",
      "Promethean Vision",
      "X-ray Vision",
      "Heat Scanner"
    ],
    "newCategory": "Video Games",
    "question": "Which armor ability allows the user to see through walls in Halo 4?",
    "questionId": "ff87067922beb818449930081b99c3e5",
    "questionType": "multiple-choice"
  },
  {
    "answer": "The Grim Reaper comes to claim your body.",
    "category": "video-games",
    "choices": [
      "You burst into flames of different colors.",
      "The Grim Reaper comes to claim your body.",
      "Saradomin reincarnates your body after you die.",
      "nothing"
    ],
    "newCategory": "Video Games",
    "question": "What happens when you die in the 2006 Runescape Halloween Event?",
    "questionId": "de3d49187efd3c5f01e32c8712d774ad",
    "questionType": "multiple-choice"
  },
  {
    "answer": "False",
    "category": "video-games",
    "newCategory": "Video Games",
    "question": "Jagex Ltd released RuneScape 3 in 2004.",
    "questionId": "d4cc309eee5ed02bf1eefd266d51f542",
    "questionType": "true-false"
  },
  {
    "answer": "True",
    "category": "video-games",
    "newCategory": "Video Games",
    "question": "In Runescape a chicken is a level 1 monster.",
    "questionId": "07bf6775a332e6ca7f95df82ac10b1a5",
    "questionType": "true-false"
  },
  {
    "answer": "False",
    "category": "video-games",
    "newCategory": "Video Games",
    "question": "Zezima is the name of a Runescape player who was first ranked number 1 in 2003.",
    "questionId": "509a7e739b5cbbef5b11da74160bcc35",
    "questionType": "true-false"
  },
  {
    "answer": "January 2001",
    "category": "video-games",
    "choices": [
      "September 2001",
      "January 2001",
      "May 1997",
      "January 1997"
    ],
    "newCategory": "Video Games",
    "question": "When were Runescape Bots introduced?",
    "questionId": "8d1d343ba42892326768f8f193abce78",
    "questionType": "multiple-choice"
  },
  {
    "answer": "10",
    "category": "video-games",
    "choices": [
      "six",
      "91",
      "5",
      "10"
    ],
    "newCategory": "Video Games",
    "question": "How many sub-quests are there in the quest Recipe for Disaster?",
    "questionId": "b3c01c0f555018830f2274b1d532b607",
    "questionType": "multiple-choice"
  },
  {
    "answer": "The Kalphite Queen",
    "category": "video-games",
    "choices": [
      "Mithril Dragon",
      "Dust Devil",
      "None of these",
      "The Kalphite Queen"
    ],
    "newCategory": "Video Games",
    "question": "The King Black Dragon was the highest level monster in Runescape until 7 September 2004, when it was replaced by which of the following?",
    "questionId": "cacf2d94bcd79e9f3a7ba09de237e295",
    "questionType": "multiple-choice"
  },
  {
    "answer": "false",
    "category": "video-games",
    "newCategory": "Video Games",
    "question": "Did any Runescape player manage to kill the Corporal Beast by themselves without abusing a glitch during the first year of the Beasts release?:removeme",
    "questionId": "c6ee97a203c71d3145e44e0eae0ce071",
    "questionType": "true-false"
  },
  {
    "answer": "True",
    "category": "video-games",
    "newCategory": "Video Games",
    "question": "On Tutorial Island of RuneScape you get runes from a male character.",
    "questionId": "4e2f82184b9d1b540aefd572d16c4692",
    "questionType": "true-false"
  },
  {
    "answer": "Ahrims staff",
    "category": "video-games",
    "choices": [
      "Ancient staff",
      "Sardomin staff",
      "Iban staff",
      "Ahrims staff"
    ],
    "newCategory": "Video Games",
    "question": "Which of these RuneScape weapons is the most powerful?",
    "questionId": "4b064683c6d1da3744207568a5c20859",
    "questionType": "multiple-choice"
  },
  {
    "answer": "Dragon",
    "category": "video-games",
    "choices": [
      "Rune",
      "Granite",
      "Barrow",
      "Dragon"
    ],
    "newCategory": "Video Games",
    "question": "Which of these is the best type of RuneScape weapon for non members?",
    "questionId": "9c0cc7e252414b3d48a1cda3edb8c21e",
    "questionType": "multiple-choice"
  },
  {
    "answer": "Monkey Madness",
    "category": "video-games",
    "choices": [
      "Final Showdown of Death",
      "Prince Ali Rescue",
      "Monkey Madness",
      "Dragon Slayer"
    ],
    "newCategory": "Video Games",
    "question": "Which of these RuneScape quests is the most difficult?",
    "questionId": "b8a5b1027f55f9a98fb0d16401fbe44d",
    "questionType": "multiple-choice"
  },
  {
    "answer": "False",
    "category": "video-games",
    "newCategory": "Video Games",
    "question": "Christopher Greenfield is the creator of the RuneScape game.",
    "questionId": "16a242ad92f211f11c0b050af827ff97",
    "questionType": "true-false"
  },
  {
    "answer": "True",
    "category": "video-games",
    "newCategory": "Video Games",
    "question": "The creator of RuneScape was helped by his cousin in developing the game.",
    "questionId": "ab2367a891e3881f11306a315997006a",
    "questionType": "true-false"
  },
  {
    "answer": "false",
    "category": "video-games",
    "newCategory": "Video Games",
    "question": "Is is true that in RuneScape, the Corporeal Beast is level 311, the highest level?:removeme",
    "questionId": "54669096de2e5e96680215a962b823f9",
    "questionType": "true-false"
  },
  {
    "answer": "Duel Wars",
    "category": "video-games",
    "choices": [
      "Bounty Hunter",
      "Duel Wars",
      "Castle Wars",
      "Clan Wars"
    ],
    "newCategory": "Video Games",
    "question": "Which of the following is not a place in RuneScape?",
    "questionId": "2460b09593e86f7a04655ab7d315b223",
    "questionType": "multiple-choice"
  },
  {
    "answer": "Zoey",
    "category": "video-games",
    "choices": [
      "Marylin",
      "Zoey",
      "Roxanne",
      "Mimi"
    ],
    "newCategory": "Video Games",
    "question": "Name the female character and one of the four survivors in LFD1.",
    "questionId": "5a6ffcd9f9352088b74ebb76664eaae5",
    "questionType": "multiple-choice"
  },
  {
    "answer": "In LFD1 there are no melee weapons like the ax or the machete.",
    "category": "video-games",
    "choices": [
      "In LFD2 you can use a flame thrower.",
      "In LFD1 there are no melee weapons like the ax or the machete.",
      "In LFD1 there are no pipe bombs.",
      "In LFD2 you can throw hand grenades."
    ],
    "newCategory": "Video Games",
    "question": "What is the main difference between LFD1 and LFD2 in regard to use of weapons?",
    "questionId": "178056f7fa4bbe2f4429afd259772a02",
    "questionType": "multiple-choice"
  },
  {
    "answer": "False",
    "category": "video-games",
    "newCategory": "Video Games",
    "question": "Setting off a car alarm scares off the zombies in LFD.",
    "questionId": "1337e6db3da63467280df56256bce758",
    "questionType": "true-false"
  },
  {
    "answer": "False",
    "category": "video-games",
    "newCategory": "Video Games",
    "question": "A pipe bomb is an ideal weapon to destroy LFD zombies because it is a silent weapon and they wont hear it when you throw it among a group of them.",
    "questionId": "e5f6fd8ba562f2b03e0cad7538a0e2f4",
    "questionType": "true-false"
  },
  {
    "answer": "True",
    "category": "video-games",
    "newCategory": "Video Games",
    "question": "Unlike in other video or PC games you cannot save a game in LFD and then come back later to play it from where you left off.",
    "questionId": "563b7903c569874299e241e5ef2b98f2",
    "questionType": "true-false"
  },
  {
    "answer": "CEDA",
    "category": "video-games",
    "choices": [
      "CEDA",
      "UNSC",
      "PETA",
      "USAA"
    ],
    "newCategory": "Video Games",
    "question": "Name the fictional government agency or organization that was supposed to fight the infection and evacuate people from infected areas in LFD.",
    "questionId": "cfac30b95a8cef183b901a8c5acfa1a1",
    "questionType": "multiple-choice"
  },
  {
    "answer": "New Orleans",
    "category": "video-games",
    "choices": [
      "Savannah",
      "Miami",
      "Atlanta",
      "New Orleans"
    ],
    "newCategory": "Video Games",
    "question": "In LFD2 the Parish campaign takes place in this city.",
    "questionId": "e2bdf9cbf8621862f76fad64ff38a603",
    "questionType": "multiple-choice"
  },
  {
    "answer": "The Midnight Riders",
    "category": "video-games",
    "choices": [
      "The Runarounds",
      "The Rockabillies",
      "Stagnant Water",
      "The Midnight Riders"
    ],
    "newCategory": "Video Games",
    "question": "What is the name of fictional band featured in LFD2?",
    "questionId": "ec813780e13a9d317eea84aa720099da",
    "questionType": "multiple-choice"
  },
  {
    "answer": "The green flu",
    "category": "video-games",
    "choices": [
      "Swines disease",
      "The mutant virus",
      "Nuclear malaria",
      "The green flu"
    ],
    "newCategory": "Video Games",
    "question": "What pestilence or disease caused people to turn into zombies and deformed some of them into super mutants in LFD?",
    "questionId": "99b76d42ed0809c6c8cd80588e5d77a7",
    "questionType": "multiple-choice"
  },
  {
    "answer": "Jimmy Gibbs Jr.",
    "category": "video-games",
    "choices": [
      "Hank Buffet",
      "Speedy Weedy",
      "Jimmy Gibbs Jr.",
      "Herb Gonzales"
    ],
    "newCategory": "Video Games",
    "question": "What is the name of the race car driver encountered in the Dead Center campaign of LFD2?",
    "questionId": "75e1afc2e18b86cbddaea8c9009bdabd",
    "questionType": "multiple-choice"
  },
  {
    "answer": "Sneaking past all Witches in a campaign without disturbing one",
    "category": "video-games",
    "choices": [
      "Not interrupting a fellow survivor when he is busy shooting at one of the zombies",
      "Not waking up your fellow survivors while they are sleeping in the safehouse",
      "Not disturbing a zombie while its eating someone",
      "Sneaking past all Witches in a campaign without disturbing one"
    ],
    "newCategory": "Video Games",
    "question": "In LFD1 the achievement known as Do Not Disturb is awarded for which of the following?",
    "questionId": "c6bef0f0cf5483881e0fe185652394c1",
    "questionType": "multiple-choice"
  },
  {
    "answer": "Killing 100 Common Infected with the chainsaw",
    "category": "video-games",
    "choices": [
      "Tying up one of the special infected with some chain",
      "Using a chainsaw to cut through some dense brush",
      "Killing 100 Common Infected with the chainsaw",
      "Whipping one of the zombies with a piece of chain"
    ],
    "newCategory": "Video Games",
    "question": "In LFD2 the achievement known as the CHAIN OF COMMAND is awarded for which of the following?",
    "questionId": "c2f711d8f2f7df8c288c8d65f695bf9d",
    "questionType": "multiple-choice"
  },
  {
    "answer": "True",
    "category": "video-games",
    "newCategory": "Video Games",
    "question": "You can add more maps and campaigns in LFD1 and LFD2.",
    "questionId": "f09cb0a23651ca6147923848a9aca54e",
    "questionType": "true-false"
  },
  {
    "answer": "False",
    "category": "video-games",
    "newCategory": "Video Games",
    "question": "In both LFD1 and LFD2, accumulating more cash than the other survivors will give you an advantage.",
    "questionId": "9406a58c531eaac8dc5c075b06961550",
    "questionType": "true-false"
  },
  {
    "answer": "Time Shadow",
    "category": "video-games",
    "choices": [
      "Time Shadow",
      "Last Time",
      "Time Knight",
      "Dark Time"
    ],
    "newCategory": "Video Games",
    "question": "What unique Zord do the Time Force Rangers have?",
    "questionId": "4167e07fdfc66bacc429a2812e67daba",
    "questionType": "multiple-choice"
  },
  {
    "answer": "The princess",
    "category": "video-games",
    "choices": [
      "The main villain",
      "The old lady",
      "The princess",
      "The elfin hero"
    ],
    "newCategory": "Video Games",
    "question": "Zelda, featured in The Legend of Zelda series of video games, is what kind of character?",
    "questionId": "7ddd424150fff8edb212214eb1c0a133",
    "questionType": "multiple-choice"
  },
  {
    "answer": "Rupees",
    "category": "video-games",
    "choices": [
      "Coins",
      "Triangles",
      "Rings",
      "Rupees"
    ],
    "newCategory": "Video Games",
    "question": "What is the currency used in the Legend of Zelda video game series?",
    "questionId": "dd27b61d31fb366671d4a44657424208",
    "questionType": "multiple-choice"
  },
  {
    "answer": "Hobbit",
    "category": "video-games",
    "choices": [
      "Zora",
      "Hylian",
      "Hobbit",
      "Rito"
    ],
    "newCategory": "Video Games",
    "question": "Which of these is not a race featured in the Legend of Zelda video games?",
    "questionId": "8c8073a39c36c35c07630009e511bab4",
    "questionType": "multiple-choice"
  },
  {
    "answer": "Boomerang",
    "category": "video-games",
    "choices": [
      "Boomerang",
      "Wand of Gamelon",
      "Hookshot",
      "Magic cape"
    ],
    "newCategory": "Video Games",
    "question": "Which of these items is always in Links arsenal in the Legend of Zelda games?",
    "questionId": "23ba9bbdcd248ef723619a4db52b668e",
    "questionType": "multiple-choice"
  },
  {
    "answer": "Wisdom",
    "category": "video-games",
    "choices": [
      "Power",
      "Wisdom",
      "All of them",
      "Courage"
    ],
    "newCategory": "Video Games",
    "question": "In The Legend of Zelda series of video games Zelda possesses which piece of the Triforce?",
    "questionId": "221ff4147edef59dc5b9267b8e7ddc59",
    "questionType": "multiple-choice"
  },
  {
    "answer": "false",
    "category": "video-games",
    "newCategory": "Video Games",
    "question": "Is there a game called Super Mario Tennis?:removeme",
    "questionId": "4417820ecbc76acd3fdf2ca6d783f1f3",
    "questionType": "true-false"
  },
  {
    "answer": "True",
    "category": "video-games",
    "newCategory": "Video Games",
    "question": "There are Mario games featuring racing, baseball, soccer, tennis, and golf.",
    "questionId": "74a65cf8f988dda274e62fe4b5ad9986",
    "questionType": "true-false"
  },
  {
    "answer": "Paratroopa",
    "category": "video-games",
    "choices": [
      "Paratroopa",
      "Birdo",
      "Toad",
      "Hammer bros."
    ],
    "newCategory": "Video Games",
    "question": "Which of the following characters is NOT a sidekick in Super Mario Strikers?",
    "questionId": "d3d185782d96efdc550e7d42a2d2d2c6",
    "questionType": "multiple-choice"
  },
  {
    "answer": "A star",
    "category": "video-games",
    "choices": [
      "A heart",
      "A fire flower",
      "A star",
      "A credit"
    ],
    "newCategory": "Video Games",
    "question": "In Mario Superstar Baseball what do you have to you use to unleash your characters super pitch?",
    "questionId": "0d0ae1c9df8d0e088b17233a6f072d34",
    "questionType": "multiple-choice"
  },
  {
    "answer": "False",
    "category": "video-games",
    "newCategory": "Video Games",
    "question": "In Mario Kart, characters are classified as either heavy or light.",
    "questionId": "8c3d84d84f4a7205e897eb4501bdd6cb",
    "questionType": "true-false"
  },
  {
    "answer": "A hammer",
    "category": "video-games",
    "choices": [
      "He sucks the ball with a vacuum.",
      "He jumps really high and slams the ball.",
      "A hammer",
      "A super big tennis racket"
    ],
    "newCategory": "Video Games",
    "question": "What is Luigis power shot in Mario Power Tennis?",
    "questionId": "77825584493782c0ad136947e58ff1cf",
    "questionType": "multiple-choice"
  },
  {
    "answer": "True",
    "category": "video-games",
    "newCategory": "Video Games",
    "question": "In Mario Power Tennis, Bowsers racket has spikes on it.",
    "questionId": "313997371d377a7fd39720723b319b1d",
    "questionType": "true-false"
  },
  {
    "answer": "Peach Dome",
    "category": "video-games",
    "choices": [
      "Mario Mansion",
      "Peach Palace",
      "Peach Dome",
      "Mario Yard"
    ],
    "newCategory": "Video Games",
    "question": "What is the most basic court in Mario Power Tennis?",
    "questionId": "e6db6957c94ec1ce51ab8e5b915b594c",
    "questionType": "multiple-choice"
  },
  {
    "answer": "False",
    "category": "video-games",
    "newCategory": "Video Games",
    "question": "Sonic the Hedgehog is the protagonist of a video game, released by Nintendo.",
    "questionId": "1024a8f536670806c23d6c0538bbcf50",
    "questionType": "true-false"
  },
  {
    "answer": "snes",
    "category": "video-games",
    "choices": [
      "Playstation",
      "None of these",
      "snes",
      "Xbox"
    ],
    "newCategory": "Video Games",
    "question": "Which one of these game systems was released by Nintendo?",
    "questionId": "b401c5ef23c13de6ce785e602cfe5b7f",
    "questionType": "multiple-choice"
  },
  {
    "answer": "false",
    "category": "video-games",
    "newCategory": "Video Games",
    "question": "Does Nintendos mascot Mario wear a red and black hat?:removeme",
    "questionId": "ccc996909bba3e3bef983db1fb686fbb",
    "questionType": "true-false"
  },
  {
    "answer": "true",
    "category": "video-games",
    "newCategory": "Video Games",
    "question": "Is it true that Kirby, the protagonist of the Kirby game series, is pink?:removeme",
    "questionId": "0ba23f2376a94b0e878636f17ded286e",
    "questionType": "true-false"
  },
  {
    "answer": "False",
    "category": "video-games",
    "newCategory": "Video Games",
    "question": "Captain Falcon, from the F-Zero video games, is a pirate.",
    "questionId": "7d88b2f9bd3b182c32250667bf45e1cb",
    "questionType": "true-false"
  },
  {
    "answer": "Assassins Creed",
    "category": "video-games",
    "choices": [
      "Warioware",
      "Mario Galaxy",
      "Assassins Creed",
      "Star Fox"
    ],
    "newCategory": "Video Games",
    "question": "Which of these games was not released by Nintendo?",
    "questionId": "48e4d3c40ea786515b2839cd7ab9c099",
    "questionType": "multiple-choice"
  },
  {
    "answer": "Falco",
    "category": "video-games",
    "choices": [
      "Falco",
      "Jigglypuff",
      "Roy",
      "Mr. Game and Watch"
    ],
    "newCategory": "Video Games",
    "question": "Which Super Smash Bros. Melee character can be unlocked by defeating the 10-minute melee?",
    "questionId": "2269d0405af2d893b7ff68e9dc2cd395",
    "questionType": "multiple-choice"
  },
  {
    "answer": "Mr. Game and Watch",
    "category": "video-games",
    "choices": [
      "Luigi",
      "Falco",
      "Mr. Game and Watch",
      "Roy"
    ],
    "newCategory": "Video Games",
    "question": "Which character in Super Smash Bros. Melee can be unlocked by beating the game with every character?",
    "questionId": "dbbddda13892efa34008d26a2a31ba89",
    "questionType": "multiple-choice"
  },
  {
    "answer": "Zelda",
    "category": "video-games",
    "choices": [
      "Zelda",
      "Young Link",
      "Link",
      "Samus"
    ],
    "newCategory": "Video Games",
    "question": "Which character in Super Smash Bros. Melee did not have a grapple ability?",
    "questionId": "243ee1eae8a240c4396f2b6d5cfddd9b",
    "questionType": "multiple-choice"
  },
  {
    "answer": "Pichu",
    "category": "video-games",
    "choices": [
      "Mewtwo",
      "Jigglypuff",
      "Pichu",
      "Pikachu"
    ],
    "newCategory": "Video Games",
    "question": "Which Pokemon character in Super Smash Bros. Melee damages itself by using its B button moves?",
    "questionId": "e55574ad5d0a96b6fd3209a76b969564",
    "questionType": "multiple-choice"
  },
  {
    "answer": "Master Hand",
    "category": "video-games",
    "choices": [
      "Poorly Coordinated Hand",
      "Crazy Hand",
      "Master Hand",
      "Power Hand"
    ],
    "newCategory": "Video Games",
    "question": "Which character in Super Smash Bros. Melee is the final boss of the normal game (Classic Mode)?",
    "questionId": "927dcaedd203500a0f2d3870d45915f2",
    "questionType": "multiple-choice"
  },
  {
    "answer": "Kirby",
    "category": "video-games",
    "choices": [
      "Peach",
      "Meta Knight",
      "Kirby",
      "Yoshi"
    ],
    "newCategory": "Video Games",
    "question": "Which character in Super Smash Bros. Melee could jump more than once in midair?",
    "questionId": "06189368c8b79997041b07088fc62aed",
    "questionType": "multiple-choice"
  },
  {
    "answer": "Roy",
    "category": "video-games",
    "choices": [
      "Falco",
      "Mewtwo",
      "Roy",
      "Captain Falcon"
    ],
    "newCategory": "Video Games",
    "question": "Which character in Super Smash Bros. Melee is unlocked by beating the game with a character from the same game?",
    "questionId": "c02936b8c1132ed726bf6df71b21b659",
    "questionType": "multiple-choice"
  },
  {
    "answer": "Donkey Kong",
    "category": "video-games",
    "choices": [
      "Ganondorf",
      "Donkey Kong",
      "Bowser",
      "Mario"
    ],
    "newCategory": "Video Games",
    "question": "Which character in Super Smash Bros. Melee had the ability to pick up other characters and walk with them?",
    "questionId": "184e3f2535c3e5808f66f41edcee4855",
    "questionType": "multiple-choice"
  },
  {
    "answer": "Mario",
    "category": "video-games",
    "choices": [
      "Zelda",
      "Mario",
      "Star Fox",
      "Pokemon"
    ],
    "newCategory": "Video Games",
    "question": "Which of the following game series featured the most Super Smash Bros. Melee characters?",
    "questionId": "9eb74315bfcef3cc63b27a4934f9a8c0",
    "questionType": "multiple-choice"
  },
  {
    "answer": "Yoshi",
    "category": "video-games",
    "choices": [
      "Yoshi",
      "Bowser",
      "Dr. Mario",
      "Peach"
    ],
    "newCategory": "Video Games",
    "question": "Which character in Super Smash Bros. Melee does not have a saving Up B button move?",
    "questionId": "0ceb5bb7b3062cf2b65e8e1ee3e063c0",
    "questionType": "multiple-choice"
  },
  {
    "answer": "Marcus Fenix",
    "category": "video-games",
    "choices": [
      "Marcus Fenix",
      "Lt. Kim",
      "Dominic Santiago",
      "Baird"
    ],
    "newCategory": "Video Games",
    "question": "What is the name of the main character in the 2006 third-person shooter Gears of War?",
    "questionId": "5dfd97bbf01abac57b66a92b457ea10e",
    "questionType": "multiple-choice"
  },
  {
    "answer": "Wretches",
    "category": "video-games",
    "choices": [
      "Wretches",
      "Drones",
      "Corpsers",
      "Theron Guards"
    ],
    "newCategory": "Video Games",
    "question": "In video game Gears of War, these creatures let loose loud piercing shrieks when they attack but are generally easy to kill.",
    "questionId": "810882f2af7c6a90718962c94e8e4385",
    "questionType": "multiple-choice"
  },
  {
    "answer": "False",
    "category": "video-games",
    "newCategory": "Video Games",
    "question": "In Gears of War, if you stay in the dark and walk slowly, the mutant race Kryll wont attack you.",
    "questionId": "c47a1979563f1da49d5f0c16c29e2eee",
    "questionType": "true-false"
  },
  {
    "answer": "Berserker",
    "category": "video-games",
    "choices": [
      "Drone",
      "Corpser",
      "Berserker",
      "Wretch"
    ],
    "newCategory": "Video Games",
    "question": "In Gears of War, which of these creatures is blind, walks upright and hunts by smell?",
    "questionId": "42da75ffaddb0d60606c2bec779cd25f",
    "questionType": "multiple-choice"
  },
  {
    "answer": "false",
    "category": "video-games",
    "newCategory": "Video Games",
    "question": "In the third-person shooter Gears of War, can you kill the Corpser in the Locust tunnels by using the Hammer of Dawn?:removeme",
    "questionId": "eff5bc457e1a8bebe55c0c34767b05da",
    "questionType": "true-false"
  },
  {
    "answer": "Hoffman",
    "category": "video-games",
    "choices": [
      "Raam",
      "Cole",
      "Hoffman",
      "Santiago"
    ],
    "newCategory": "Video Games",
    "question": "What is the name of the Colonel who is in command according to the scenarios in Gears of War?",
    "questionId": "475ddb628b56665ff0b54ed799263f0d",
    "questionType": "multiple-choice"
  },
  {
    "answer": "Cole",
    "category": "video-games",
    "choices": [
      "Cole",
      "Baird",
      "Rojas",
      "Kim"
    ],
    "newCategory": "Video Games",
    "question": "In the Gears of War game, which member of Alpha Team is first found fighting in a small courtyard, alone and taunting the Locust?",
    "questionId": "778c2ecd49fd39bdccc7e813d84c05b8",
    "questionType": "multiple-choice"
  },
  {
    "answer": "Insane",
    "category": "video-games",
    "choices": [
      "Normal",
      "Casual",
      "Insane",
      "Hardcore"
    ],
    "newCategory": "Video Games",
    "question": "Which difficulty setting can only be unlocked by completing Gears of War once on any difficulty?",
    "questionId": "fda35afa503036ba1c843c44450c111b",
    "questionType": "multiple-choice"
  },
  {
    "answer": "True",
    "category": "video-games",
    "newCategory": "Video Games",
    "question": "General RAAM is protected by the mutant race Kryll when you try to kill him on the train at the end of Gears of War.",
    "questionId": "d5a85c17eb3bc1745d800d096b4dc506",
    "questionType": "true-false"
  },
  {
    "answer": "Black Dragon",
    "category": "video-games",
    "choices": [
      "Red Dragon",
      "Blue Dragon",
      "Black Dragon",
      "Green Dragon"
    ],
    "newCategory": "Video Games",
    "question": "Which of these dragons is the strongest in the Runescape game?",
    "questionId": "68c6dac58c87092b67eb482f91b1281a",
    "questionType": "multiple-choice"
  },
  {
    "answer": "Chaos Elemental",
    "category": "video-games",
    "choices": [
      "Mithral Dragon",
      "King Black Dragon",
      "Chaos Elemental",
      "Calphite Queen"
    ],
    "newCategory": "Video Games",
    "question": "Which of these Runescape creatures drops a Dragon 2H Sword?",
    "questionId": "aef15d9d6c2fce5f4c846abe72282a01",
    "questionType": "multiple-choice"
  },
  {
    "answer": "Zanaris",
    "category": "video-games",
    "choices": [
      "Falador",
      "Zanaris",
      "Catherbys",
      "Camalot"
    ],
    "newCategory": "Video Games",
    "question": "What is the name of the city in Runescape that you unlock after the Lost City Quest?",
    "questionId": "817fe494d00a06780058142cd7bba8fc",
    "questionType": "multiple-choice"
  },
  {
    "answer": "RPDT",
    "category": "video-games",
    "choices": [
      "NYER",
      "LPOG",
      "LAPD",
      "RPDT"
    ],
    "newCategory": "Video Games",
    "question": "Which of these is the postal service in Runescape?",
    "questionId": "c29b65cd32dc5109810271236dcddc0a",
    "questionType": "multiple-choice"
  },
  {
    "answer": "False",
    "category": "video-games",
    "newCategory": "Video Games",
    "question": "In the Runescape game you get a fishing skillcape in the Legends Guild.",
    "questionId": "255a7474861f231511c440436d1e7470",
    "questionType": "true-false"
  },
  {
    "answer": "2",
    "category": "video-games",
    "choices": [
      "5",
      "4",
      "2",
      "3"
    ],
    "newCategory": "Video Games",
    "question": "How many forms does the Calphite Queen have in the game Runescape?",
    "questionId": "7c6f0543950e863b48c4794ff9e93141",
    "questionType": "multiple-choice"
  },
  {
    "answer": "Kitten",
    "category": "video-games",
    "choices": [
      "Hamster",
      "Kitten",
      "Dog",
      "Bird"
    ],
    "newCategory": "Video Games",
    "question": "Which of these pets can you own in Runescape?",
    "questionId": "f5514a2fab4bf5a6248b2cfae967c567",
    "questionType": "multiple-choice"
  },
  {
    "answer": "True",
    "category": "video-games",
    "newCategory": "Video Games",
    "question": "You can own a pet rock in the Runescape game.",
    "questionId": "adf02bfa63a8e62d5013ca203e4714eb",
    "questionType": "true-false"
  },
  {
    "answer": "True",
    "category": "video-games",
    "newCategory": "Video Games",
    "question": "In the action/adventure game Killer7, the name of the assassin who can change between seven deadly personalities is Harman Smith.",
    "questionId": "2d8ead9bf360b435cae4a2a371217934",
    "questionType": "true-false"
  },
  {
    "answer": "Kaede",
    "category": "video-games",
    "choices": [
      "Harman",
      "Con",
      "Dan",
      "Kaede"
    ],
    "newCategory": "Video Games",
    "question": "Which persona from the Killer7 game is the one with the Scope on his/her Automatic?",
    "questionId": "35bb7010e1a97c771f8a31ec49b4f04a",
    "questionType": "multiple-choice"
  },
  {
    "answer": "14",
    "category": "video-games",
    "choices": [
      "17",
      "14",
      "It is not stated.",
      "25"
    ],
    "newCategory": "Video Games",
    "question": "In Killer7, what is the character Con Smiths\u2019 age?",
    "questionId": "baa5ea2045586cd2542da3871290e362",
    "questionType": "multiple-choice"
  },
  {
    "answer": "Tara Strong",
    "category": "video-games",
    "choices": [
      "Debby Derryberry",
      "Tara Strong",
      "Lacey Chabert",
      "E.G Daily"
    ],
    "newCategory": "Video Games",
    "question": "Which voice-over actress, who has also done voices for Nickelodeon, is the voice of Kaede in Killer7?",
    "questionId": "c958ed2096d4b35449446be25926e436",
    "questionType": "multiple-choice"
  },
  {
    "answer": "Mizaru",
    "category": "video-games",
    "choices": [
      "Mizaru",
      "None of the above",
      "Mizaro",
      "Mizari"
    ],
    "newCategory": "Video Games",
    "question": "What is the name of character Iwazarus ex-wife in the action/adventure game Killer7?",
    "questionId": "67c1893804d43a6a1f017bc7d0103013",
    "questionType": "multiple-choice"
  },
  {
    "answer": "Samantha",
    "category": "video-games",
    "choices": [
      "Susan",
      "Suzie",
      "Polly",
      "Samantha"
    ],
    "newCategory": "Video Games",
    "question": "In the game Killer7, what is the name of Harmans maid?",
    "questionId": "cb9c4070ba7c81b34e8c66714d7d0efc",
    "questionType": "multiple-choice"
  },
  {
    "answer": "Maid uniform",
    "category": "video-games",
    "choices": [
      "Tight black overall",
      "Normal clothing",
      "Evening gown",
      "Maid uniform"
    ],
    "newCategory": "Video Games",
    "question": "The only time you can use the save feature in Killer7 is when character Samantha is in what costume?",
    "questionId": "50a96b9eb01424875ea8e2c86aba9068",
    "questionType": "multiple-choice"
  },
  {
    "answer": "Professional wrestler",
    "category": "video-games",
    "choices": [
      "Costume artist",
      "Professional boxer",
      "Bodyguard",
      "Professional wrestler"
    ],
    "newCategory": "Video Games",
    "question": "What was Mask De Smith\u2019s profession before coming apart of the killers\u2019 team in Killer7?",
    "questionId": "6117f47fad798c31fba71cfd908b891e",
    "questionType": "multiple-choice"
  },
  {
    "answer": "Christopher Mills",
    "category": "video-games",
    "choices": [
      "Kun Lan",
      "Christopher Mills",
      "Heaven Smile",
      "Travis"
    ],
    "newCategory": "Video Games",
    "question": "In the action/adventure Killer7, who is the only informant able to contact the Killer7 team?",
    "questionId": "be200de4928921315e950bead217a3f1",
    "questionType": "multiple-choice"
  },
  {
    "answer": "Imoen, Jahiera, Minsc",
    "category": "video-games",
    "choices": [
      "Imoen, Jahiera, Minsc",
      "Aerie, Jahiera, Jan",
      "Khalid, Jahiera, Minsc",
      "Valygar, Jahiera, Minsc"
    ],
    "newCategory": "Video Games",
    "question": "Besides your Avatar, what other characters can you get at the beginning of the game Baldurs Gate II: Shadows of Amn?",
    "questionId": "27139f1fd07a6371a5914fdec602eca4",
    "questionType": "multiple-choice"
  },
  {
    "answer": "The Planar Sphere",
    "category": "video-games",
    "choices": [
      "The Shadow thieves cellar",
      "The Temple ruins",
      "The Planar prison",
      "The Planar Sphere"
    ],
    "newCategory": "Video Games",
    "question": "Where can you get the gauntlets of ogre power in the game Baldurs Gate II: Shadows of Amn?",
    "questionId": "76bb411ec574a3c6ba5895865f5ab86f",
    "questionType": "multiple-choice"
  },
  {
    "answer": "Merella",
    "category": "video-games",
    "choices": [
      "Merella",
      "Valygar",
      "Minsc",
      "Drizzt"
    ],
    "newCategory": "Video Games",
    "question": "What ranger can you save in the game Baldurs Gate II: Shadows of Amn by defeating the Shadow lord in the ruin temple?",
    "questionId": "b462238ff6fbd51d28356122fa97af29",
    "questionType": "multiple-choice"
  },
  {
    "answer": "The Cowled Wizards",
    "category": "video-games",
    "choices": [
      "The Athkatla Guard",
      "The Emerald warriors",
      "The Shadow Thieves",
      "The Cowled Wizards"
    ],
    "newCategory": "Video Games",
    "question": "What organization takes Imoen from you, after you escape the first level in the game Baldurs Gate II: Shadows of Amn?",
    "questionId": "21db4f5cb191e58f7e53c64b580e6f8d",
    "questionType": "multiple-choice"
  },
  {
    "answer": "Isaea Roenal",
    "category": "video-games",
    "choices": [
      "Isaea Roenal",
      "Jon Irenicus",
      "Corieg Axehand",
      "Stumpy Ironfoot"
    ],
    "newCategory": "Video Games",
    "question": "Who kidnaps Nalia in the game Baldurs Gate II: Shadows of Amn?",
    "questionId": "9e9869d8c0325a4e7ea98559058c4b30",
    "questionType": "multiple-choice"
  },
  {
    "answer": "A chicken suit",
    "category": "video-games",
    "choices": [
      "An egg that you eat that brings you up one level",
      "A chicken suit",
      "A bunny suit",
      "A ring that transforms you into an egg"
    ],
    "newCategory": "Video Games",
    "question": "In the 2007 RuneScape Easter special, what item or items do you earn by helping the Easter bunny?",
    "questionId": "4d2a7ad168e7c4466f13cf0a0797133d",
    "questionType": "multiple-choice"
  },
  {
    "answer": "special tree logs and special locations",
    "category": "video-games",
    "choices": [
      "rainbow boots and fighting boots",
      "special money and no extra lands",
      "special tree logs and special locations",
      "you can kill demons and go to the barbarian village"
    ],
    "newCategory": "Video Games",
    "question": "What two special benefits do RuneScape members get?",
    "questionId": "373218738342e3eedf8a0fd956022646",
    "questionType": "multiple-choice"
  },
  {
    "answer": "True",
    "category": "video-games",
    "newCategory": "Video Games",
    "question": "In the RuneScape game, it is illegal to use a macroer.",
    "questionId": "bf7f7f7536f5140e8b1d607f2653237d",
    "questionType": "true-false"
  },
  {
    "answer": "True",
    "category": "video-games",
    "newCategory": "Video Games",
    "question": "In the RuneScape game, the woodcutting skillcape lets you save a bird from a tree.",
    "questionId": "ec8653b5e79bb424602743a2b63a2a5e",
    "questionType": "true-false"
  },
  {
    "answer": "1",
    "category": "video-games",
    "choices": [
      "3",
      "6",
      "1",
      "4"
    ],
    "newCategory": "Video Games",
    "question": "On a non-member world in RuneScape, how many places can you travel to on the ship in Port Sarim?",
    "questionId": "ec685a7e75c794d94d1bff4558aae7c5",
    "questionType": "multiple-choice"
  },
  {
    "answer": "wolf",
    "category": "video-games",
    "choices": [
      "polar bear",
      "wolf",
      "reindeer",
      "penguin"
    ],
    "newCategory": "Video Games",
    "question": "What animal is Santa on the 2005 RuneScape Christmas special?",
    "questionId": "32655b7f0f445013ac8bf6f90c5d0dcf",
    "questionType": "multiple-choice"
  },
  {
    "answer": "Daisy",
    "category": "video-games",
    "choices": [
      "Butter",
      "Jesse",
      "Daisy",
      "Katie"
    ],
    "newCategory": "Video Games",
    "question": "What is the name of the dog the main character is trying to save in the Dogs Life video game?",
    "questionId": "0e5c19880ab940b17be7355e0ac1cd19",
    "questionType": "multiple-choice"
  },
  {
    "answer": "his collar",
    "category": "video-games",
    "choices": [
      "his attitude",
      "the markings on his coat",
      "his collar",
      "his leash"
    ],
    "newCategory": "Video Games",
    "question": "What changes on the dog every time you go to a different Poodle Parlour in the video game Dogs Life?",
    "questionId": "d43092a4b56b248029f9ca7f0537c682",
    "questionType": "multiple-choice"
  },
  {
    "answer": "Village center",
    "category": "video-games",
    "choices": [
      "Boom City Park",
      "Lake Minniwahwah Cafe",
      "Village center",
      "Farmhouse"
    ],
    "newCategory": "Video Games",
    "question": "At what location do you first have to run away from the dog catcher in the Dogs Life video game?",
    "questionId": "b0446e217c91ab13b47ec19f98461478",
    "questionType": "multiple-choice"
  },
  {
    "answer": "Barking competition",
    "category": "video-games",
    "choices": [
      "Marking territory",
      "Barking competition",
      "Digging holes",
      "Doing tricks"
    ],
    "newCategory": "Video Games",
    "question": "When you pick up scents in the game Dogs Life, which of the following is not part of a competition with another dog?",
    "questionId": "1f7f0a0553bc16b1b761e36b11eff82b",
    "questionType": "multiple-choice"
  },
  {
    "answer": "Wayne and Dwayne",
    "category": "video-games",
    "choices": [
      "Wayne and Dwayne",
      "Bob and Rob",
      "Ryan and Bryan",
      "John and Ron"
    ],
    "newCategory": "Video Games",
    "question": "What are the names of Miss Peaches henchmen in the Dogs Life game?",
    "questionId": "28ab2f21cf078f180f21205800bc5d4a",
    "questionType": "multiple-choice"
  },
  {
    "answer": "Collect them all before time runs out",
    "category": "video-games",
    "choices": [
      "Obtain more territory than the other dog",
      "Dig holes faster than the other dog",
      "Collect them all before time runs out",
      "Get all the food before the other dog does"
    ],
    "newCategory": "Video Games",
    "question": "In the Dogs Life video game, what challenge do the purple scents start?",
    "questionId": "24214c73c9354ecb34cce8f9a9254825",
    "questionType": "multiple-choice"
  },
  {
    "answer": "bones",
    "category": "video-games",
    "choices": [
      "bones",
      "washing",
      "people",
      "collars"
    ],
    "newCategory": "Video Games",
    "question": "What improves your speed, stamina, and health in the game Dogs Life?",
    "questionId": "c3d4a07b1348405dc7e52fee6e3aee4d",
    "questionType": "multiple-choice"
  },
  {
    "answer": "shaver",
    "category": "video-games",
    "choices": [
      "scissors",
      "shower head",
      "shaver",
      "a sponge"
    ],
    "newCategory": "Video Games",
    "question": "Which of the following is NOT found at the grooming parlour in the video game Dogs Life?",
    "questionId": "93aa41d64c55ec981fec0cfa23ee7747",
    "questionType": "multiple-choice"
  },
  {
    "answer": "3",
    "category": "video-games",
    "choices": [
      "3",
      "5",
      "50",
      "7"
    ],
    "newCategory": "Video Games",
    "question": "How many places can you go to by train in the Dogs Life game?",
    "questionId": "8002d97efb525bbee103fc5dce90430d",
    "questionType": "multiple-choice"
  },
  {
    "answer": "The Loud Brothers Live",
    "category": "video-games",
    "choices": [
      "Lake Minniwahah Chat",
      "Miss Peaches Radio Show",
      "Blues, Smooths, and Clues Live",
      "The Loud Brothers Live"
    ],
    "newCategory": "Video Games",
    "question": "What is the name of the radio show in the game Dogs Life?",
    "questionId": "bd3106262ec679638a6c936781587e87",
    "questionType": "multiple-choice"
  },
  {
    "answer": "Circle",
    "category": "video-games",
    "choices": [
      "Cross",
      "Square",
      "Triangle",
      "Circle"
    ],
    "newCategory": "Video Games",
    "question": "What button do you press to dig in Dogs Life (PS2)?",
    "questionId": "b463b6fc05d25c2b4b83db00e6d2c230",
    "questionType": "multiple-choice"
  },
  {
    "answer": "Orange",
    "category": "video-games",
    "choices": [
      "Orange",
      "Brown",
      "Blonde",
      "Black"
    ],
    "newCategory": "Video Games",
    "question": "What color is Miss Peaches hair in the video game Dogs Life?",
    "questionId": "3cc789e55fc6cc5ee6ebba6a0938d4e8",
    "questionType": "multiple-choice"
  },
  {
    "answer": "Lake Minniwahwah Cafe",
    "category": "video-games",
    "choices": [
      "Lake Minniwahwah Slopes",
      "Lake Minniwahwah Hotel",
      "Lake Minniwahwah Mountain Top",
      "Lake Minniwahwah Cafe"
    ],
    "newCategory": "Video Games",
    "question": "Where is the Lucky 7s Machine located in the game Dogs Life?",
    "questionId": "f57dd16c7be98b3f8fbe78b8f5e34bc7",
    "questionType": "multiple-choice"
  },
  {
    "answer": "The Sleeping Bandits",
    "category": "video-games",
    "choices": [
      "The Sleeping Bandits",
      "The Danger Bandits",
      "The Ruthless Bandits",
      "The Masked Bandits"
    ],
    "newCategory": "Video Games",
    "question": "In the Dogs Life video game, what is the name of the group of bandits at Boom City?",
    "questionId": "b225ad651fbc1103b022b07f3adb25c8",
    "questionType": "multiple-choice"
  },
  {
    "answer": "yellow",
    "category": "video-games",
    "choices": [
      "black",
      "white",
      "yellow",
      "red"
    ],
    "newCategory": "Video Games",
    "question": "What color is the jacket the girl wants you to get from the ski slopes in the video game Dogs Life?",
    "questionId": "73ce444751c0dc3003eb1b8c31240d66",
    "questionType": "multiple-choice"
  },
  {
    "answer": "a scarf",
    "category": "video-games",
    "choices": [
      "a scarf",
      "a hat",
      "twigs",
      "coal"
    ],
    "newCategory": "Video Games",
    "question": "In the Dogs Life video game, what does the girl NOT ask you to bring to make her snowman?",
    "questionId": "1c0187b2c632a37fb8386631ceda9c08",
    "questionType": "multiple-choice"
  }
]